[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever dared
to imagine! This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!
Maniac!
No!
[USOPP] Why? Why won't
anyone believe me?!
They are coming and they're
gonna level this town.
What am I supposed to do then?
[grunts]
[USOPP] They'll think I'm
lying if I try to warn them.
It's my home and
I love everyone in it!
So, you wanna
little help or what?
All right, fine, I'm scared!
Why shouldn't I be?!
They're Captain Kuro's men!
They mean business!
We're not laughing at you.
You really think we'd
risk our lives out of pity?
[LUFFY] "Clash with
the Black Cat Pirates!
The Great Battle on the Slope!"
[USOPP]
Okay.
At daybreak, the pirates
will be landing at this shore
to begin their attack.
But the only way that they'll
be able to get to the village
is to go up this slope.
The rest of the shoreline
is sheer cliffs,
so they have to
come through here.
If we can fight them
while they're funneled
into that narrow pass,
their numbers
won't mean anything
and the village
will be protected.
All right, sounds pretty easy.
[USOPP] Talking about it is, but
victory depends on our strength.
What is it that you guys can do?
I cut.
I stretch.
I steal.
I hide.
Well, this time
you'd better fight!
Just making a funny.
C'mon, calm down!
[MERRY]
Ah, Klahadore. Welcome back.
[KURO]
How is she?
[MERRY] She's resting just now.
She was quite exhausted.
[KURO] I leave town for a few
hours to tend to some errands,
and everything falls to pieces.
That Usopp certainly knows how
to cause trouble, doesn't he?
[MERRY]
Yes.
And on top of everything
else he's done today,
he claimed you were a pirate.
Ha! I can't think of
a more outrageous lie!
[laughing]
Indeed.
What's this here?
Well, that's a
present of course.
From Miss Kaya
to you, Klahadore.
It's been three years since
you came to this mansion,
and this gift is to say
thank you for your hard work.
It's a commemoration of sorts.
How nice.
The glasses you're wearing
are always slipping and you
have to push them back up.
So, the lady of the house custom
ordered a new pair for you.
Isn't she just the most
thoughtful young woman
you've ever met?
[KURO chuckles]
How appropriate.
Tomorrow will be a day
worth commemorating.
[MERRY]
Eh?
[KURO]
It's a crescent moon tonight.
[MERRY]
Huh?
[KURO] It's on nights like
these that I truly feel alive.
My heart races, and my
blood boils in my veins.
[MERRY]
Ah!
Klahadore, what're you doing?!
Why would you do such a thing
to Miss Kaya's present?
Oh, I'll be receiving
a gift all right.
But it won't be glasses.
It'll be her entire estate.
[gasping]
[MERRY]
What're you saying?!
I suppose there's no reason
to carry on the act any longer.
In a few hours,
the village will be mourning
the unforeseen tragedy.
[yelps]
Three long years I've
quietly waited for this.
[MERRY] Miss! You have
to get out of here! Run!
[PIRATE A]
Captain Jango!
Captain Jango, it's almost
daybreak, it's time get moving!
[PIRATE B]
Good morning, Captain.
[PIRATE C]
Good morning, sir.
You idiots.
Only the sun can wake me up
and live to tell about it.
Do I make myself clear?
He's in a really bad mood.
Mornings are the worst.
[JANGO]
Just look,
the moon is still up, so the
sun couldn't have woken me.
Now, which one of you did it?
[PIRATES] Our apologies, sir!
We're very sorry, sir!
[JANGO]
Well, in that case.
Good morning, gentlemen.
[PIRATE D]
Wait, what's goin' on here?
He was mad just a second ago.
So what? He's in a
better mood now
and that's all that matters
so keep your big trap shut!
[PIRATE D]
It's confusing!
[PIRATE E] Oh yeah, well,
your face is confusing!
[PIRATE D]
Hm?
Attention, men!
Let's set sail!
[PIRATES yelling]
Yep, I'm a genius.
There's no way they'll be able
to make it up this slope now.
All this oil we put here
should keep them occupied
while we go to work on 'em.
They're gonna be busy
slipping and sliding around
like a bunch of idiots,
then we show up and beat
the crap out of 'em!
Wow, so that's your plan, huh?
That's right.
I'm going to defend the village
no matter what it takes.
[NAMI] Let's just hope none
of us slip on that oil
and end up down there with them.
Because that would be like
sliding into a meat grinder.
Usopp, I gotta hand it to you,
you're pretty good
at fighting dirty.
Of course I am!
There isn't anyone alive who
can best me with a sling shot,
or beat me at the art
of fighting dirty!
[ZORO]
It's almost daybreak.
They're coming.
[chuckles]
[PIRATE A]
We're here!
[JANGO] All right, men!
You know what to do!
Go ashore! Trash the village!
Head for the mansion!
[PIRATES]
Aye, sir!
[PIRATE F] Captain, there are
already two boats here!
[JANGO]
What?!
[PIRATE F]
Shall I investigate?
[JANGO]
Leave 'em for later.
They don't look like
treasure ships to me
and we have a schedule to keep.
Understood, sir.
What're you waiting for?!
It's time to move out!
[PIRATES yelling]
Where are they?
I thought we were gonna fight.
The sun's up. What's the deal?
[ZORO] Huh...
Maybe they over slept.
[USOPP]
No.
They're gonna show up all right.
And lots of them.
Wait a minute.
Maybe I'm hearing things,
but it sounds like battle
cries from somewhere.
[PIRATES yelling]
Yeah, I definitely hear them.
No, it can't be.
What can't be?
There's a shore just
like this to the north!
They went...
We're at the wrong
shore?! That's not good!
[USOPP] Well, this is where
they had their secret meeting
so I just assumed okay?!
[groans]
We need to hurry!
Before they make it to
the village! Where is it?!
You have to head
directly north from here.
If you run you, could
make it in three minutes.
The terrain there is
almost exactly the same,
so all we need to do
is stop them at the slope.
Don't you worry,
we're gonna stop 'em.
[NAMI gasps]
Oh no!
If those filthy pirates
are at the north shore,
then they've already
seen our boats!
They'll take our treasure!
I'll be there in 20 seconds!
Aw, man!
My brilliant oil strategy
was all for nothing!
My precious treasure...
[ZORO]
Hey!
What're you doing?
Let's get outta here.
[NAMI]
Yeah.
[NAMI screaming]
[ZORO yelps]
Help! I'm gonna fall!
Let go, you moron!
Sorry!
Hello.
See ya there!
[yelping]
Sorry, but you understand,
the treasure's in danger.
That oil won't be a
problem for you, right?!
That girl's gonna pay!
I swear on my life, they'll
never set foot in my village!
That Luffy sure is
a good runner.
He's so far ahead, I can't
even see him anymore.
[LUFFY] Run straight north!
Run straight north!
Those mongrels
are in big trouble
if they so much as
look at my treasure!
[PIRATES yelling]
It's an ambush!
Somebody's up there!
We meet again.
[USOPP] I am the legendary
Captain Usopp!
I've been waiting for you!
All my men and I are ready
to fight to the death!
Turn back now if you
value your lives!
[USOPP] I wasn't supposed
to be the first one here.
He was running way ahead of me.
I can't handle these guys alone.
[ZORO]
Crap!
How am I supposed
to get past this stuff?!
[LUFFY] The village...
That can't be right.
He said run north and I ran
in a cold-ish direction
so I should be at the shore.
It's you. I remember.
You're one of the troublesome
brats who overheard our plan.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm warning you!
Leave here while you still can!
If you don't,
my 100 million crewmen
will massacre all of you!
100 million?
Are we really supposed
to believe that?
No way! 100 million! Incredible!
[PIRATE I]
Captain! He's obviously lying!
[PIRATE J] Then it's time
to call his bluff.
[USOPP]
They saw through it!
[PIRATE K] That guy seriously
thought he could fool us.
What's that?! You've been
lying to us this whole time?!
[PIRATE L] Captain Jango,
take a look at this.
Oh no, is it bad?
[PIRATE L]
No, sir! It's good!
We searched those other ships
and found a huge
load of treasure!
It's hard to say how much,
but I bet it's around
five million berries!
What?
[gasps]
Five million berries?
How in the world did those guys
get ahold of so much treasure?
[USOPP]
I see you found my loot!
Well, you can have it!
[PIRATE K] You're just gonna
let us take your treasure?
[USOPP]
That's right!
Just turn around and
forget all about this place
and the treasure is yours!
I didn't think people that
stupid actually existed.
At this point, he's just
embarrassing himself.
Okay, do you know
what a pirate is?
We're going to
take this treasure
and there's nothing
you can do about it.
And there is no way
we're turning back
until we get what we came for.
Well, yeah, that makes sense.
[JANGO]
All righ, then.
On the count of "one, two,
Jango," you'll let us by.
[gasps] It's that strange
weapon from before.
[JANGO]
One, two!
Jan--!
Don't you ever try to give
my-hard earned treasure away!
My head!
--Hey! Who is this crazy girl?!
--Captain!
This isn't the time to be
hypnotizing yourself,
we got a mission to
carry out, remember?!
[NAMI]
That treasure boat is mine
and I'm not gonna let
you have a single berry.
Do ya hear me? In fact
you better clear out,
'cause I'm coming down
there to get it back!
That really hurts!
[NAMI] Who said you could
give them my treasure?!
You got what you deserve!
[USOPP]
I didn't give them the treasure,
I just said I would
give it to them!
That's the same thing!
And I just saved your life.
I guess I forgot to
mention it to ya earlier,
don't ever watch
his ring routine.
That weirdo's a hypnotist.
Hypnotist?
So, where's Luffy?
He's a fast runner, I thought
he'd be here way ahead of you.
I don't know. He either got lost
or he chickened out
at the last minute.
[sighss] The only thing that
could keep him from a fight
is getting lost.
Right when we need him, too.
[USOPP] I'll go ahead
and take command here.
I think it's about time
you go 'n kick their butts!
[NAMI] What?! Me?!
What about you?!
I can't take on a boatload
of vicious pirates by myself!
That's just suicide!
What? Like I'm gonna
do any fighting?
Beneath this calm exterior lies
the abject terror of a coward.
Oh, so you think you're scared?!
Well, I'm so scared I am
literally about to cry!
[USOPP] Please! Your eyes
are completely dry!
You'll have to do
better than that.
Liars can smell their own.
[NAMI]
That's just your upper lip!
[USOPP]
I got beat up by...
[JANGO] We don't have
time for this nonsense.
All right, men,
let's get to work!
Crush them and
move to the village!
--[PIRATES yelling]
--[BOTH gasp]
Here they come.
Wait! I know!
I have some caltrops!
Those are just what
the doctor ordered!
Lemme have some!
Your gonna love this!
Caltrop!
[BOTH]
Hell!
[ZORO yells]
Nami...
...if your still alive
when I get outta here,
I'm gonna kill you!
[growling]
[ZORO]
Take that, oil!
[ZORO yelling]
[ZORO panting]
Now... how do I get to
the north shore from here?
Run straight north!
Run straight nor--!
But which way is north?
[PIRATES yelling]
Yes! We got 'em!
Check it out! Here comes...
...the Lead Star!
Bastard!
Way to go! You're quite
the warrior after all.
Looks like you got this handled
so I'll just take a break.
But you haven't
done anything yet!
[NAMI yelps]
Uh, what is it?
There are caltrops behind us.
Idiot! You dropped those
things behind us, too?!
[PIRATE M yelling]
Get outta the way!
Ha. Don't tell me
you really thought
you were going to
stop us down there.
[gasps]
Let's go, fellas!
Captain Kuro hates waiting!
[PIRATES yell]
[PIRATE M gasps]
[PIRATE M]
You again.
Let go of me, you jackass!
You want some more?!
Here! Have some!
Have a little more!
[USOPP]
I will never...
...let you step foot
in that village!
All I did was lie
like I always do.
[USOPP groaning]
See...
Today will be like every other
day in that sleepy little town,
'cause you and your cronies
will never set foot in it!
[PIRATE O]
Shut up!
[PIRATE I]
Stupid girl!
[NAMI yelps, screams]
[groans] Treasure...
[USOPP]
Are you--?
Shut up! I won't
tell you again!
[grunts]
[JANGO] We've wasted enough
time playing pirates!
Quit bothering with them
and move to the village!
Or have you forgotten that this
is Captain Kuro's operation?
And he doesn't look favorably
on his well laid plans
being ruined by idiots!
He'll kill us all!
You understand that,
you cretins?!
He's right!
Yeah! Let's get to the village!
[PIRATES yelling]
[USOPP]
Don't go any further.
I said stop!
Turn back. Don't take
another step.
[PIRATE F]
Get off me!
[USOPP groans]
[USOPP]
Please, don't kill them.
Just leave this village alone.
They're good people.
They don't deserve this.
I love this place.
Please!
[PIRATE G]
What is this, Captain Jango?
[PIRATE M] Nobody told us
that killers like those
were gonna be here!
It's about time.
Is that the best those
pirates can dish out?
Yeah, I was hopin'
for a challenge.
And you!
After leaving me down there,
you're lucky I'm not
kickin' your butt too!
Ussop, you big bonehead!
You never told me which
direction was north!
Who are these guys?
[KURO]
They're late.
I don't appreciate
tardiness. Not one bit.
They know full well
what happens to those
who are foolish enough
to upset my plans.
[KURO] Do they think they
can take their sweet time?
Well, if they have
forgotten the consequences
of disappointing me...
I'll kill them all.
It looks like the butler
from Kaya's mansion.
But it's so early
in the morning.
Why is he walking to the shore?
As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...
[LUFFY]
Is this the place?
[ZORO]
I'm gonna get you, Nami!
How dare you leave
me down there!
[NAMI]
Crap! Zoro's really mad!
[ZORO]
Now your gonna pay!
[NAMI]
Oh, I know!
By the count of
"one, two, Jango,"
you'll fall deeply asleep.
[ZORO] You wish!
Hey, Luffy! Wake up!
[NAMI]
Oh, look at that guy's hand!
[ZORO]
Don't change the subject!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Terrifying Duo!
Meowban Brothers vs. Zoro!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!