[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit of
dreams greater than they've
ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!
[SANJI] Here's something
for your captain.
[GHIN]
Thank you, Sanji.
Thank you!
[SANJI gasps]
[KRIEG yells]
[SANJI groans]
[SANJI grunts]
This is a pretty good ship...
I believe that I'll take it.
[CARNE gasps]
R-Right... I see...
Here comes the
Meat Ball of Doom!
[KRIEG whimpers]
[PATTY, CARNE gasp]
[COOKS gasp]
So die!
[COOKS scream]
[gasps]
You cooks should
not have defied me!
When I give you
slime balls an order...
You will follow it
down to the last letter!
Don't you ever disobey me!
This is about a hundred meals...
Now take it to your
men right away.
[COOKS]
No, Owner Zeff!
You're... Red Foot Zeff.
[LUFFY] "Protect Baratie! The
Great Pirate, Red Foot Zeff!"
Wha-What're you doing?!
You can't be serious!
[COOK T] If all of those
pirates get their strength back,
the restaurant will be
completely taken over!
[ZEFF]
That would be true...
...if they still had
the will to fight.
[COOKS gasp]
[ZEFF]
Tell me...
Did your will survive defeat?
That... can't be...
The great Don Krieg
was defeated?
Whoa... Not even he could do it.
A pirate fleet with
50 ships couldn't
make it on the Grand Line!
The Grand Line?
[KRIEG]
It is you, isn't it?
You're Red Foot Zeff!
[KRIEG]
So, you are alive.
The unrivaled pirate captain
who was also the ship's cook.
Yes, that's right,
I'm still alive...
But what has any of this
got to do with you?
I haven't been a pirate
for many years now.
I chose the life of a cook.
[laughs]
"Chose the life of a cook," huh?
Yeah, right.
You didn't have
a choice, old man.
You live as a cook because
the only thing you
can be now is a cook.
He was known far and wide...
Red Foot Zeff was a
master of deadly kicks
who never used his
hands in battle.
It was said that
with his mighty legs,
he could crush bedrock to sand,
and leave footprints
on solid steel.
"Red Foot" referred to his
boots which became soaked
in the blood of his enemies
as he kicked them down.
You know, it really is a pity
that you no longer have
that precious leg of yours.
I heard that rumor
some time ago.
How unlucky for you to have
such an accident at sea.
Now that your greatest weapon
has been sacrificed to the sea,
you're defenseless,
completely unable to fight.
[ZEFF]
I don't need to fight anymore.
I'm a cook.
And as long as I have
my two hands for that,
I'll be just fine.
Enough chitchat,
let's get to the point.
What do you want from me?
[KRIEG chuckles]
Red... Foot...
You're the man who
sailed the perilous waters
of the Grand Line and
came back unscathed...
Impressive.
There should be a logbook
detailing your tactics,
a full year of your
journey there...
Give it to me... now!
[ZEFF grunts]
Whoa! So is he sayin'
you've been to the
Grand Line too, Pops?
Yeah.
My logbook, huh?
You're right, I do indeed
have a record of my travels.
But I will never
hand it over to you.
[KRIEG]
Huh?
You ignorant brute...
That logbook is sacred to me.
It's the pride of the
crewmen that I sailed with.
It's far too important
to give to you.
All right... I'll take it.
Yes... It's true that
the Grand Line beat me.
Still... I will
never give up on it!
I am Don Krieg!
In the end, it's
just another ocean.
I had enough weapons...
...and men...
...and ambition!
[KRIEG] Regrettably, the only
thing I lacked was information.
I just didn't know enough.
But now, I'll fix all that.
Once I have your logbook,
I'll form another pirate fleet
and seize the
legendary One Piece.
Then, I will stand as ruler
of this great pirate era!
[LUFFY]
Now, hold on!
It's me who's gonna be
King of the Pirates!
--[COOKS gasp]
--[COOK U] Chore Boy?
Wait! Don't be such an idiot!
You better back off, Chore Boy!
No way, not from this.
Did you say something, kid?
I won't allow that kind
of stupidity again.
Oh yeah, well, stupid or not...
I'm just stating the
facts like they are.
This isn't a game.
Yeah, I know...
I'm still gonna conquer
the Grand Line.
[KRIEG growls]
No, you won't!
It's true that we didn't have
the information we needed;
but my fleet of five
thousand men was wiped out
in just seven days, you brat!
That sea is hell!
What?! One week?!
Don Krieg's ships were
wiped out in seven days?!
[COOK KK]
What happened out there?
Unfortunately, I don't find your
smart-assed remarks
very amusing.
If you insist on
this foolish behavior,
I'll crush you right
here and right now.
Go ahead, if you can.
[KRIEG growls]
[KRIEG]
I can, and I will.
It would be my pleasure to
send you to an early
grave, you cocky runt.
[COOKS gasp]
[KRIEG growls]
What's going on, Luffy?
You need a hand?
If you don't need help,
that's okay, too!
[KRIEG]
Huh?
Oh, hey, guys.
Appreciate the offer...
But I think I can
handle this clown.
Aw, too bad!
But if you say you don't need
any help, who am I to argue?
Us awesome fighters are
just gonna sit this one out.
Holler if you need us!
[USOPP groans]
[USOPP]
What'd you do that for Zoro?!
[ZORO]
Shut up already, you weirdo!
[KRIEG laughs]
Are those two guys your "crew"?
That's a pretty small
group you got there, kid.
Well, that's not all...
I got two more!
I'm not a part of your crew!
[KRIEG growls]
[KRIEG]
I'll deal with you later.
Right now, I'm going
to go feed my men.
Those of you who
don't wish to die,
can leave the restaurant
now and escape that fate.
The only things I'm after are
the logbook and this ship.
[KRIEG] However, if you wish
to stay and be slaughtered...
I have no problem burying every
last one of you at sea...
Know that.
It just got really quiet.
If Big Bro Zoro is in there...
Then, everything should be fine.
[YOSAKU]
Yeah, I know...
But what if it's not?
[JOHNNY]
Good point...
Big Sis Nami!
Should we go in there, too?
Whaddya think?
Big Sis?
[YOSAKU, JOHNNY yell]
[YOSAKU, JOHNNY groan]
[smooch]
[YOSAKU, JOHNNY gag]
Hey... Are you okay?
[NAMI]
Hm?
Yeah, I'm fine!
Is something wrong?
[YOSAKU, JOHNNY]
Huh?
[GHIN groaning]
[COOKS murmuring]
I'm... so sorry, Sanji...
I never thought it
would be this way.
[ZEFF] You have nothing
to apologize for, sailor.
[PATTY gasps]
[ZEFF]
Every cook at this restaurant
did what they thought was right.
That's all there is
to say about that.
But, Boss!
Why are you acting as if
you're taking Sanji's side?!
This mess is his fault!
[COOK V]
He's right!
Sanji is responsible for
this whole damn thing!
Yeah, Boss! That man's gonna
put your precious restaurant
out of business!
You fools don't know what
you're talking about!
None of you have any
idea what it's like
to be on the brink
of starvation...
To have no food or water
on the open ocean...
There is no way you could
possibly understand
what a terrifying
prospect that is!
It's the most difficult
situation a man can ever face!
What?
I don't know what you're
talkin' about, Chef Zeff.
[ZEFF] The difference
between all of you and Sanji,
is that Sanji knows.
[COOK A]
What's the boss trying to say?
[COOK C] Yeah, what's he
saying that Sanji knows?
[ZEFF grunts]
[ZEFF] If all you're gonna
do is stand around grumbling,
--then leave this place
--[COOKS gasp]
and never come back.
[PATTY] I, for one,
am gonna stay and fight!
I couldn't live with myself
if I accepted defeat!
[COOK W]
I'm staying, too!
After all, this is our
restaurant, isn't it?!
That's right, and this place
is all I've got, too!
[COOKS chattering]
[GHIN gasps]
What are you doing?!
You saw how powerful
Don is, right?!
[SANJI]
Hey, Ghin!
Listen up because I'm only
going to say this once.
Feeding someone who's hungry
is my sacred moral duty.
But...
Now that your crew is well fed,
I have no obligation to them.
With a clean conscience,
I can beat every last one
of them to a bloody pulp.
If anyone tries to
take the restaurant...
...they're dead.
I'll kill them without a
moment's hesitation.
Got that?
[GHIN gulps]
[PATTY] Hah! You're a
real head-case, Sanji.
Letting him live, then
threatening to kill him?
Can it, cook.
[LUFFY]
See? This guy's awesome, huh?
Who cares how awesome he is?!
We gotta get out
of here right now!
Easy there, Luffy...
It is Don Krieg, but he's
in pretty sad shape.
[LUFFY]
Hm. Hey, Ghin!
You said you didn't know
anything about the Grand Line...
But I thought you'd been there.
That doesn't make any sense...
[GHIN gulps]
Nothing makes any sense now.
What happened to us
on the seventh day
of our journey through
that cursed sea...
I don't know if
it was a dream...
...or reality.
I saw things that I can't
bring myself to believe.
I know in my heart that
it's impossible...
...for that entire
50 ship fleet...
...to be completely
eradicated by a single man.
[COOKS gasp, whimper]
[USOPP screams]
[LUFFY gasps]
[COOKS]
What?!
[KRIEG grunting]
[GHIN]
It all happened so fast...
As soon as this man appeared,
he began to systematically sink
our ships one after another.
[GHIN] If that raging storm
hadn't come upon us when it did,
then that monster would have
destroyed our flagship as well.
[GHIN] I don't know if a
single other ship made it out.
It all seems like a terrible
nightmare burned into my memory!
I just want to forget!
His eyes...
They were like a hawk's,
sharp and murderous.
His gaze alone felt like
the cold hand of death!
[ZORO gasps]
[USOPP]
Huh?
[ZORO]
What did he just say?!
[GHIN growling]
[ZEFF]
Well then...
That can only be the one
--known as Hawk-Eye.
--[COOK B] What?
[ZEFF] Your description
of his heartless gaze
isn't proof of his identity
in and of itself...
But the way he so easily
decimated your fleet
confirms without a
doubt, that it's him.
Hawk-Eye Mihawk.
So you know him, Zoro?
Yeah, I do...
He's the man I've
been looking for.
Hawk-Eye is the whole
reason I set out to sea.
[LUFFY]
Hmm...
[SANJI] Could that man
have had some kind of score
to settle with you guys?
[GHIN]
We didn't do anything to him!
[ZEFF] Perhaps you
disturbed him during a nap.
Stupid cook!
Why would he destroy an entire
fleet for something so trivial?!
[ZEFF chuckles]
There's no reason to shout...
It's just an example.
I thought you might like
a little friendly advice
on what kind of a place
the Grand Line is.
And what kind of place is that?
He probably means that
anything can happen there.
[USOPP sobs]
Hey, Luffy! Do we really,
really have to go there?
Luffy?
[ZORO, USOPP]
Hm?
[USOPP]
Hey... Luffy...?
[LUFFY laughs]
That's so awesome!
This is gonna be such a blast!
Don't you understand
the concept of "danger"?!
[ZORO]
Finally, my life's goal will
be achieved on the Grand Line.
What...?!
My rival...
He's out there somewhere,
and I'm gonna find him.
[SANJI]
Are you that stupid?
It's idiots like you
guys that end up dead.
[ZORO]
That may be true...
But lay off the name-calling.
I devoted my entire life to
becoming the world's
greatest swordsman.
I made my choice,
so I'm the only one who
gets to call me stupid.
Hey! What about me?!
Me too, right?! I mean,
it only seems fair.
Shut up, stupid.
[SANJI sighs]
What morons.
[PATTY]
Enough!
Do any of you maggots understand
the current situation?!
That enormous galleon moored
in front of our dear little
restaurant is none other
than Don Krieg's flagship!
So why don't we check back into
reality and deal with this?!
[PIRATES cheering]
Yeah! We're saved!
[PIRATE A]
I can't believe it! We're alive!
[PIRATE B]
It's like a dream!
[PIRATE C]
Nightmare's finally over!
[PIRATE D] We sailed into
the pirate graveyard,
but we came back alive!
That's right... And I'm
glad you all made it
because I'll need a healthy crew
to go back to the Grand Line.
[PIRATES gasp]
Hey... Why the long faces?
Sir... Why are we
going back there?
[gunshot]
Point taken... Are there
any other objections?
[PIRATES]
Uhh...
[PIRATES cheer]
[KRIEG] First, we need to take
over that floating restaurant.
Then, we can abandon the wreck
we're on before it falls apart.
Don't worry about the enemy;
they're just a bunch
of prissy cooks.
It won't take much
to crush them.
--Attack!
--[PIRATES yell]
Hear that?! They're
gonna be here soon!
[COOK C]
The restaurant is ours!
And I'll fight to the
death to keep it that way!
[PIRATES yelling]
[KRIEG]
Huh?
[PIRATES gasp]
[PIRATES screaming]
[COOKS gasp]
[USOPP whimpers]
What the--?!
[ZEFF]
Huh?
What's going on?!
[PIRATE LL]
Don Krieg!
The main ship... It was cut!
It was cut?! What
do you mean "cut"?!
Something sliced
up this galleon?
No way... It can't be!
That's impossible!
[COOKS gasp, scream]
Raise the anchor!
Or we'll sink along with them!
[COOK H]
Yes, sir!
[LUFFY grunts]
Wait... Nami and the guys are
still on our ship out there!
[USOPP gasps]
[USOPP groans]
I hope it's not too late!
[LUFFY pants, gasps]
[LUFFY gasps]
[USOPP screams]
Hey! Big Bro!
[YOSAKU]
Big Bro!
[LUFFY]
Yosaku! Johnny!
Are you okay?!
[ZORO]
What happened to the ship?!
Where's Nami? Is she okay?
[YOSAKU]
I'm sorry, Big Bro...!
I don't know how to say
this, but... she's gone!
[NAMI] See ya! Oh, and
make sure to tell them...
Big Sis Nami!
[NAMI] If it's meant to be,
I'll see them real soon!
She took all the treasure
and sailed away!
[ALL gasp]
[ALL]
She did what?!
[ZEFF gasps]
That man is...
[ZORO]
Huh?
[ZORO grunts]
No... That bastard!
He followed us back!
[heartbeat thumps]
It's him... He's here...
Hawk-Eye!
As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...
[LUFFY]
Who's that?
[ZORO] That's the man
I've been searching for.
I never thought I'd
see him this soon.
[LUFFY]
You gonna fight him?
[ZORO] Yeah, that's the whole
reason I set out to sea.
[USOPP]
Hey, Zoro, what's wrong?
[ZORO] So this is the
world's greatest swordsman?
Am I really this
much weaker than him?
[LUFFY, USOPP]
Zoro!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
"Hawk-Eye Mihawk! The Great
Swordsman Zoro Falls At Sea!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!