[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever dared
to imagine! This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[LUFFY grunts]
This time crush his head
into the ground, Richie!
Gum-Gum...
Hammer!
--[MOHJI gasps]
--[LUFFY growls]
[LUFFY yells]
[NAMI] You're going to
go too? You're wounded!
Heh! Are you gonna
join our crew or what?
Huh? Come on!
[LUFFY gasps]
I suppose we could team up...
...in order to achieve
our common goal.
[BUGGY]
All right! Fire!
[BOODLE gasps]
[BOODLE grunting]
So be it. [gasps]
[LUFFY]
"Epic Showdown!
Swordsman Zoro vs.
Acrobat Cabaji!"
[LUFFY]
I'm here to kick your ass.
Just like I promised
I would, Buggy!
[BUGGY grunts]
[LUFFY laughs]
[BUGGY laughs]
Damn you, Straw Hat!
[BOODLE coughing]
[BUGGY growls]
How dare you!
You can't just waltz up to
me and treat me like this!
I'm Captain Buggy
and I won't stand for it!
Listen to me, all I
want is the chart
and the treasure then I'm
out of here, you got it?
Yeah, I got it.
[BOODLE coughs]
Get outta here.
Why'd you follow me?
You're outsiders, leave
this to me. [groans]
This is my fight
that I need to be the
one to protect my town!
[BOODLE grunts]
Buggy is my fight!
[NAMI gasps]
[BUGGY]
Huh?
[BOODLE groans]
What the hell do you
think you're doing?!
Why'd you knock out the mayor?!
Because.
[NAMI gasps]
That's not a bad idea.
If the old man had continued
to fight he would have died.
That's for the best.
You didn't have to hit him!
I'm sure we could have
thought of a more humane way
to deal with the situation!
[BUGGY snorts]
Here, goes... [inhales]
Big Nose!
[HENCHMEN gasp]
That's the worst thing you
could have said to him!
[BUGGY]
Ohh... You damn flashy idiot!
I won't stand for this.
Take aim and fire
the Buggy Ball!
Why'd you have to say that?
Come on Luffy, we gotta go!
You go ahead.
Time to die!
I'm fine.
Just watch!
Gum-Gum Balloon!
[NAMI gasps]
[HENCHMEN gasping]
What is he?
Did he catch the Buggy Ball?!
--[HENCHMEN screaming]
--[CLOWN HENCHMAN] Run for it!
He coulda warned me.
[BUGGY, HENCHMEN screaming]
All right! I got 'em!
What the hell kinda
monster are you?
I think you freaked her out.
[NAMI]
I knew that something was weird
after you survived
the fight with that lion.
No human being
can do what you do!
Now explain yourself!
What the hell was the
balloon inflatey thing that
you did just now?!
That was the Gum-Gum Balloon.
I don't care what you call it,
just tell me how you did it!
What are you,
some kind of freak?
[BUGGY groans]
[BUGGY] How dare you
try to flashily do me in?
Unreal...
Using his men as a shield.
[MOHJI groaning]
[MOHJI]
Hm?
What in the world
just happened here?
[MOHJI grunts]
No! It's you!
Hi!
[MOHJI screaming]
It's that damn Straw Hat!
Captain Buggy!
We have to be careful!
He has Devil Fruit powers, too!
He's a rubber person!
I saw it myself!
What?
Rubber person?
Yeah... See?
[NAMI yelps]
A Devil Fruit.
That explains how he bounced
that Buggy Ball back at us.
[MOHJI]
Huh?
[CABAJI] How do you plan
to respond to this insult...
...Captain?
Oh, Cabaji...
...I don't know.
I'm too angry to even fart.
Put him down, Cabaji!
What the hell did
you do to my Richie?!
[CABAJI]
This cat?
I used it as a shield, to keep
my clothes from getting dirty.
[MOHJI]
Richie!
No, Richie!
Say something, please!
Richie!
--[RICHIE whimpers]
--[MOHJI] Richie?!
Damn you, you bastard!
[MOHJI yells]
[MOHJI screams]
Out of my way!
How about...
...Outta my way!
[MOHJI yells, grunts]
[LUFFY grunts]
[CABAJI]
Captain Buggy?
Yes, Cabaji?
[CABAJI] Allow me to
repay their disrespect.
Fine. But, make it a
good show for everyone.
[CABAJI laughs]
--[NAMI gasps]
--[LUFFY] Ooh!
[CABAJI]
You may call me Acrobat Cabaji.
Captain Buggy's Chief of Staff.
You will pay for your insolence!
[LUFFY gasps]
[ZORO]
I'll clash swords with you.
[CABAJI]
It's an honor, Roronoa Zoro.
As a swordsman myself, I relish
this chance to slay you.
[CABAJI]
Hm.
Hey Zoro?
You really should get some rest.
Let me handle this guy.
[ZORO]
Just stay back.
[CABAJI] That's the stab wound
the Captain inflicted on him.
The fool...
Arsonist... Technique!
[ZORO grunting]
[LUFFY gasps]
[NAMI yelps]
[yells]
[CABAJI]
What's wrong?
I didn't kick you that
hard, now did I?
He fights dirty!
Going after his
injury like that!
[BUGGY chuckles]
[CABAJI]
Acrobat Technique...
Murder at the Steam Bath!
Acrobat my ass. That's just
an ordinary dust cloud!
[ZORO gasps]
[CABAJI grunts]
[yelling]
He did it again!
[ZORO grunting]
[CABAJI]
What's this?
It's such a disgraceful sight
to see a grown man moaning.
I suppose now you
can see how foolish
it was to make an enemy
of the Buggy Pirates.
To keep fighting with
such a bad injury...
...he's crazy!
He's hurt so bad.
I don't know how he's
managing to stay in the fight.
Why are you just standing
there watching him?!
He's gonna get himself
killed, you know!
[ZORO grunting]
Roronoa Zoro... is finished!
You annoying little bastard.
You havin' fun
pokin' at my wound?
Then go ahead!
[CABAJI gasps]
[NAMI gasps]
Ouchie!
[CABAJI]
Huh?
Uh... Why didn't you
dodge his attack?
[ZORO] Is that enough
of a handicap for ya?
And now let me show you,
just how superior my
skills are to yours.
[CABAJI gasps]
Yeah, Zoro! Get 'em!
You fool, You've made
a vast error in judgement.
I won't be mocked.
[ZORO] My swords aim to
be the world's greatest.
I refuse to lose even once
to anyone who calls
himself a swordsman.
[CABAJI]
I see.
A strong resolve keeps
you going. But have no fear.
Wounds as bad as yours
will be more than
enough of an excuse.
[CABAJI]
For losing to me!
[ZORO]
To hell with that.
If I lose to someone like you,
even with these
minimal injuries,
then I don't have a very
bright future ahead of me do I?
[CABAJI]
Why you...
Alright! Yeah!
[gasps]
I won't stay and watch this.
You pirates can stand
around for the rest of time
and kill each
other for all I care.
I mean it doesn't matter to me
whether you guys win or lose!
I'm gonna take this opportunity
to swipe their treasure
and get outta here.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
Maybe we can team up again
if we ever get the chance.
See ya!
Good luck with the fight!
Yeah, thanks! See ya!
[CABAJI] Here's a taste of
my ultimate acrobatic move!
[CABAJI]
Acrobat Technique...
The Dance of a Hundred
Kamikaze Tops!
They're not normal.
Both Luffy and Zoro
are completely crazy.
If I join up with them,
I can tell that nothing
good will come of it!
[BUGGY laughs]
[banging]
[NAMI grunts]
[NAMI]
Here we are!
Now I steal their
treasure and their chart
and get the hell outta here.
[ZORO grunting]
Acrobat Technique...
A Hike in the Mountains!
[ZORO]
Huh?
[CABAJI] Fireworks in
the Cool Summer Breeze!
Whoa! That's high!
[CABAJI]
Sting of the Unicycle!
Ground-Hugging...
Chop-Chop Cannon!
Cabaji, I'll hold him!
Then you finish him off!
Done!
[ZORO]
Damn it!
[yells]
Luffy...
[BUGGY yelling]
You bastard!
If you wanna fight someone...
...how about me?
[NAMI giggles]
Look at all this stuff!
And every last bit of
it is mine! [laughs]
[gasps]
[HENCHMAN] What do you think
you're doin' with our treasure?
[NAMI]
Oh, crap!
He woke up!
[HENCHMAN growls]
By order of Captain Buggy,
anyone who gets near
the treasure will, uh...
There should be...
more in there [groans]
[NAMI]
Heh.
Oh, It hurts!
Hey, you...
...alright?
My chest just started
hurting real bad [groans]
What? Your chest?
[DRUNK HENCHMAN]
Ooh...
[NAMI]
Hm.
[NAMI grunts]
[HENCHMAN grunts]
[NAMI laughs]
[gasps]
[NAMI]
Yes!
The chart of the Grand Line!
[BUGGY gumbles]
[ZORO panting]
[CABAJI laughs]
I assure you
I don't need my Captain's
help to finish you off.
Enough... I'm tired of this.
[CABAJI laughing] So you've
finally given up, have you?
I must say, I'm quite
impressed that you lasted
that long with such
serious injuries.
[ZORO]
I think you misunderstood.
I'm tired of watching your
boring little side show.
[CABAJI gasps]
So sorry to have
disappointed you.
How about...
[CABAJI grunts]
My real swordman skills!
[LUFFY gasps]
[BUGGY]
Heh!
[CABAJI]
Die, Zoro!
[ZORO]
Oni...
Giri!
[CABAJI gasps]
Cabaji!
I can't believe the
Buggy Pirates...
...were defeated
by petty thieves.
[ZORO] We aren't petty
thieves... [grunts]
We're pirates!
Luffy, I'm goin' to sleep!
Good.
I'm looking forward to this.
[BUGGY grumbles]
[NAMI grunts]
[NAMI]
Heh!
I scored an impressive
haul from the Buggy Pirates.
But hauling treasure is tiring.
I guess it's worth
the effort though.
[NAMI]
Hm...
Anyway, I gotta find a
way off this island ASAP.
[snoring]
[BUGGY]
You guys are pirates?!
[LUFFY]
Yeah!
We're searching
for the Grand Line!
Ha! That's not an easy
voyage, you know?
And I don't think
that two halfwits
the likes of you can handle it.
And what will you do if,
by some miracle,
you manage to make it there?
Go on a sightseeing tour
or something? [laughs]
Be King of the Pirates!
[BUGGY groans]
You can't be serious, you idiot!
If you were King
of the Pirates,
then that would make me God!
There's only one who can
be King of the Pirates
and obtain all this
world's treasures,
and that's gonna
be me, you got it?!
[LUFFY]
You're annoying.
Let's go ahead and settle this!
[BUGGY] Seeing that straw hat
brings back memories of him,
and that really gets
my blood boiling.
So bring it on,
you wannabe pirate!
You remind me of him.
That damn cheeky
red-haired pirate!
What did you say?
The red hair...
Wait, are you saying you
knew my old friend, Shanks?
[BUGGY] That's right.
I knew Shanks once.
Do you know where he is now?
[BUGGY]
I don't know...
I guess that depends, Straw Hat.
Maybe I do and maybe I don't.
What are you talking about?
Did you forget?
No, I didn't forget, you moron!
But I'm not just gonna
tell you where he is
outta the kindness of my heart.
You have to work for that info!
Fine! I'll make you tell me!
[BUGGY laughs]
You can give it your best shot,
but I don't like your chances.
I doubt rubber can
bounce back from a blade!
You're right.
[NAMI grunts]
[BUGGY]
Chop-Chop Rice Cracker!
Can't move in midair, can you?
Too bad!
[BUGGY laughs]
No, you're wrong!
[LUFFY grunts]
[BUGGY]
Ha. Ha. Oh, how interesting!
You're not so bad either,
but here comes...
Gum-Gum Pistol!
They're neat
abilities all right,
but they leave
you wide open.
I'll carve you up!
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
Chop-Chop Quick Escape!
[LUFFY]
Sickle!
[BUGGY]
Ha!
[BUGGY laughs]
Not good enough, Gum-Gum!
[LUFFY groans]
[LUFFY]
Hm!
[LUFFY] Damn, you keep
breaking into pieces!
[BUGGY laughs]
What?
They're still going at it?
I can't believe these guys.
Uh, hey, Did you see that?
You dumbass, Pretend
you're still knocked out.
If you get yourself caught
in the middle of that,
Then there's no way you'll
ever make it out alive.
Chop-Chop Canon!
[LUFFY grunts]
Separate!
[BUGGY laughs] So, runt,
you wanna give up yet?
You bastard!
How's that?
Was I not supposed to scratch
your face or something?
Bastard...
No one damages my lucky hat
and walks away from it alive!
[BUGGY]
Heh?
This hat is my
only treasure!
And anyone who so much as lays
a finger on it is gonna pay!
Yeah...
I made a solemn promise.
I promised the guy
who gave me this hat
that I'd form a crew and become
the greatest pirate ever.
And I didn't think
that there was anything
that could faze him.
But look at him.
He's getting so
upset about a hat.
[LUFFY growls]
[BUGGY] Hm...It seems that
hat has a history to it.
[LUFFY]
That's right!
[BUGGY]
Is it really all that special?
[LUFFY gasps]
If that's the case,
you should protect it!
[LUFFY gasps]
[LUFFY gaspsing]
[LUFFY screaming]
[LUFFY]
But Shanks...
Your arm!
Your Arm!
[LUFFY sniffing]
[SHANKS]
I'll leave this hat to you.
It means more to me than
anything in the world,
so you better take
good care of it.
You hear me?
[LUFFY whimpering]
[SHANKS] I want you to bring
this hat back to me someday.
in good condition.
And only once you've
become a great pirate.
That's our promise, Luffy.
[LUFFY grunts]
How is this old, tattered
hat a treasure? [laughs]
Treasure refers to sparkling
gold, silver, and jewels.
And all those things reflect
their owner's grandeur.
You really consider
this worthless
dirty straw hat a treasure?
You need to grow
up, boy. [laughs]
Shut up.
When Shanks gave me that,
I made a promise!
[BUGGY]
What?
So you're telling me that
this used to be Shanks' hat?
No wonder it looked so familiar.
He always wore it
when I knew him.
[LUFFY gasps]
So you and Shanks were members
of the same pirate crew?
Yeah, back when we were
pirates in training.
We were fellow comrades.
That damn detestable,
red-haired bastard!
[LUFFY growls]
Shanks is a much better
man then you'll ever be!
You don't have the right
to call him comrade!
And don't you ever
bad-mouth him again!
Time for my Chop-Chop
Quick Escape! [laughs]
[LUFFY yells]
[BUGGY groaning]
I don't want you to ever mention
Shanks' name to me
again, you bastard!
[BUGGY gasping, coughing]
I can say whatever the hell
I want about Shanks! [coughs]
Tell me, what happened
between you and Shanks,
and where can I find him now?
[BUGGY grunting]
[LUFFY]
Damn it!
How dare you tear up my
treasured straw hat!
[BUGGY coughs]
[BUGGY]
Do you really wanna know?
He's the one person
that I loathe.
I'll curse his name
for the rest of my life!
As long as there's
breath in my body, Shanks.
I will never...
...forgive you.
As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...
[LUFFY]
Get ready, Buggy!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
[NAMI]
Yeah! Get him, Luffy!
[LUFFY]
You'll pay for damaging
the hat that Shanks
entrusted to me.
[NAMI]
Enough talk, just do it!
Finish this clown and
protect my treasure!
[LUFFY]
Huh? That doesn't sound right...
[NAMI]
It's basically the same thing!
Don't sweat it!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
"Who is the Victor?
Devil Fruit Power Showdown!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!