[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever dared
to imagine! This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!
How appropriate.
Tomorrow will be a day
worth commemorating.
I swear on my life, they'll
never set foot in my village!
[LUFFY] Run straight north!
Run straight north!
Those mongrels
are in big trouble
if they so much as
look at my treasure!
[ZORO] How am I supposed
to get past this stuff?!
Get outta the way!
[USOPP]
I will never...
...let you step foot
in that village.
All I did, was lie
like I always do.
Today will be like
every other day
because you and your cronies
will never set foot in it!
[KURO]
They're late.
I don't appreciate
tardiness. Not one bit.
They know full well
what happens to those
who are foolish enough
to upset my plans.
I'll kill them all.
[LUFFY]
"The Terrifying Duo!
Meowban Brothers vs. Zoro!"
[PIRATES groaning]
Well, it's about time.
Wow.
That was great. You guys
are really that strong?
[LUFFY]
Mh-hm.
Could you have been slower?
What took you so long?
[grunts] You're the
one who pushed me down
that oil slick so
you could get out!
It was an accident.
I slipped, you fell.
At least one of us
made it outta there.
That's better than both of us
being stuck at the bottom.
It shoulda just been you!
"Run straight north!" he says.
That's just great!
I mean, how am I
supposed to know
which way north even
is out here, huh?
Shut up. You're the one who
ran away so sure of yourself,
ready to take on anyone.
Well, I just got so excited,
I started running, you know?
[JANGO] The sun rises
high in the sky now.
And that means, Captain
Kuro grows very impatient.
[whimpers]
Men, don't just lie there.
You can't tell me you're
going to let them win.
They're just a couple of idiots.
[JANGO]
The fact, is we don't have time
to lollygag around
here any longer.
If our enemy is strong, then we
must become stronger than them.
Here, stare deeply
into this ring.
Now, I will count "one, two,
Jango" and after that,
you will all begin
to grow stronger.
Your wounds will heal and
you will grow stronger still.
So, what is he doing?
It looks weird.
Looks like hypnosis.
He's trying to convince them
they're stronger than they are.
Like that'll work.
[JANGO]
Stronger. Stronger!
[LUFFY]
Uhh...
[JANGO]
One... Two...
Jango!
[PIRATES shouting]
No way.
[PIRATES cheering]
[ZORO] That one guy
completely destroyed the cliff!
Now that's what I call power.
I always thought hypnotizing
people was a buncha crap.
That was just one of them.
Imagine what the
whole crew can do.
[JANGO]
Now go!
And strike down all
who stand in your way!
[PIRATES cheering]
Hey, you guys, you
might wanna move.
Luffy. You and I will
take it from here.
[PIRATES snarling]
All right then, what now?
--[LUFFY growling]
--[ZORO] Uhh... Luffy?
[growling]
[yelling]
Don't tell me you let
that freak hypnotize you too!
[LUFFY yelling]
Ugh. He really is
a simple-minded idiot.
[LUFFY]
Gum!
Gatling!
[PIRATES yelping]
[JANGO]
Damn you, Captain Kuro.
You made one hell
of a miscalculation.
These are not your
average village idiots.
[LUFFY growls]
[ALL yelling]
[yelling]
[ZORO]
Where's he going?
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY grunting]
[PIRATE B]
Uh...
What is he doing?
[LUFFY yelling]
That's right! Tear it down!
[PIRATE B] Ah! He's gonna
destroy our ship!
[PIRATES gasping]
Oh no!
[PIRATE B] He's gonna crush
us with it! Everybody run!
[PIRATES yelling]
[PIRATE C]
Captain, do something!
[JANGO grunts]
[JANGO] I suppose watching
him isn't helping anything.
One, two, Jango,
you will fall asleep!
[yelling]
[JANGO]
One... Two...
Jango!
[ZORO, NAMI]
Huh?
[LUFFY snoring]
[ALL yelling]
[PIRATES groaning]
[JANGO whimpering]
[LUFFY snoring]
[PEPPER] What? You saw
Klahadore heading to the shore?
[ONION] Yeah, and he had this
weird, scary look on his face.
[PEPPER]
What about Kaya? Is she okay?
[ONION]
We'll find out.
The Usopp Pirates are off!
Carrot, would you wake up?!
Come on. It's way
too early for this.
This is no time for laziness.
Horrible things could be
happening right now!
[ONION] I still think the
pirates are gonna attack soon.
I know our Captain
said that was a lie,
but I think he was
the one that was lying!
Yeah, you're probably right!
It was weird.
He seemed off yesterday.
The Captain wasn't
his usual self.
Where is she?
[ALL grunting]
Captain used to always
come through here!
It's useless. The thing's stuck.
Let's find another way.
[groaning]
Rotten woman!
How dare you try to make a fool
of the great Captain Usopp!
Insulting me for having
the blood of a pirate.
Please, you don't have
to do this, Usopp.
[screaming]
[KAYA]
Klahadore.
Klahadore, are you there?
[coughing]
Hello, Klahadore?
No. Merry!
[KAYA]
Merry!
What's going on?!
What happened to you?!
Please, wake up! Merry!
Please, don't die!
Oh, thank goodness. You're
still alive. I was worried.
Merry.
[MERRY groaning]
[KAYA yelps]
[KAYA] You have to tell me
who did this to you.
Klahadore. That's who.
He attacked me.
[gasps]
He's a... He's a pirate.
He's never been anything else.
[KAYA]
But... how could that be?
[MERRY] He got close to you just
so he could steal your fortune.
That's all he's ever wanted.
[KAYA]
It can't be.
No! You're lying!
I'm telling you the truth!
[KAYA] Then... what Usopp spoke
about yesterday was the truth.
That's right. And that's
what is most tragic.
When he learned the truth,
he tried his hardest
to get us to hear him out,
but we were all
too shallow-minded,
too confident in the closed off
world we've lived in for so long
to listen to a single word.
Quick! Run, Kaya!
They're gonna kill you!
I promise, this'll all
make sense tomorrow.
[MERRY] In our blind protection
of the villain in our midst,
we drove away the one brave
lad whose desperate resolve
he enacted for
the sake and safety
of every person of this village,
including you and I.
[MERRY coughs]
[KAYA]
Someone! Anyone! Help!
Merry needs help!
[MERRY]
No, miss. It's of no use.
The entire staff is on leave.
No one has been here
since yesterday.
[KAYA]
What?!
Then I just-- I'll find--
[MERRY] You cannot let yourself
get flustered, miss.
We know the attack has yet
to begin, so be calm
and think clearly about
what it is you have to do next.
[MERRY] Because if
Klahadore is the thief
we understand him to be
and his goal is your fortune
and your mansion,
then by all means,
let him have it.
None of this is worth
sacrificing your life over.
[KAYA]
Yes.
It's a cruel truth,
but you are the only one who
can stop Klahadore now, Kaya.
Can you do it?
I know... this is not... your
burden but still I must ask.
Yes, I understand.
And I will do it.
This isn't a situation
I can run away from.
I know what consequences I face.
I will find Klahadore
and I will finish this.
[KIDS grunting, groaning]
What're you doing up there?
You have to hold on
tighter, idiot!
[ONION]
But the poles are slippery!
And my hands are sweaty!
Who cares? We still
gotta get over it.
[PEPPER]
Aren't you worried about Kaya?!
Oh, no. Someone's coming out.
[ALL yelp]
[CARROT grunts]
[ONION]
It's Kaya. She's all right.
Looks like something's
got her really bothered.
Yeah, walking around outside
by herself doesn't seem right.
Something's goin' on.
Something really weird.
[LUFFY snoring]
Looks like those guys are
probably down for the count,
don't ya think?
I guess.
Maybe, but Luffy's still trapped
underneath that cat. Just look.
Relax, he's fine. You should
really worry about your
own injuries by the looks of it.
[JANGO grunts]
[JANGO]
Damn that little brat.
Now our whole
plan's shot to hell.
What am I gonna
do with this mess?
Captain Kuro sees this
and he'll kill us!
[whimpers]
[SIAM]
Butchie! Come check this out!
There's some bad
stuff going down.
[BUTCHIE]
What the hell?!
I forgot we still have
our trump card.
Come forth, Meowban Brothers!
Yes, Captain?
Did you call for us?
Well, did you?
[SIAM]
Siam!
And Butchie!
[BOTH] Together we
are the Meowban Brothers.
At your service!
[BOTH]
Uhh...
[ZORO]
Hm?
Butchie. Siam.
We absolutely must
get up this hill,
but as you can plainly
see our path is blocked.
If you would be so kind
as to remove this obstacle.
Immediately.
[BOTH whimper]
No way! We couldn't do that!
He looks too strong.
Right, Butchie?
Oh yeah, he's strong.
Way stronger than us.
[ZORO]
Huh?
[yelps] Besides we just guard
the ship, not fight people.
He's got a point.
We're really not the guys
you want to send into battle.
So, they're a couple of pansies.
I guess they're not
the trump card after all.
Siam, just do it already.
[screams] What?! Please, not me!
And hurry!
Okay, I'll go.
Just stop yelling.
The guy's crying like a baby.
What are they doing down there?
[screaming]
[NAMI]
Of all people, why force
--[NAMI] that guy into a fight?
--I'm gonna tear you up
with these claws,
you just wait and see!
I'm a vicious killing machine!
And I'm coming for you,
you bad people!
You come any closer and
I'll cut you in half!
I'm not joking! I'll do it!
[screaming]
Not likely.
[ZORO]
Bastard!
[SIAM]
Too bad.
It seems you fell
for my little ruse.
I'm impressed you blocked me.
Considering what a
brilliant performance I gave.
Don't let the tiny
bit of skill you have,
cause you to underestimate
Siam of the Meowban Brothers.
Are you missing something?
Not that I would know
anything about it.
There it is.
Cat Burglar.
[ZORO]
Give me my swords back.
Your swords?
But you already have a sword,
how greedy can you be?
Say goodbye, swords.
Goodbye!
Now, I feel lighter.
[ZORO] You should take care
with other people's things!
[SIAM groaning]
[SIAM]
You really have to be faster.
'Cause I'm agile as a cat.
Butchie, you're up! Get in here!
Sure thing, Siam!
Cat--!
[BOTH gasp]
[BUTCHIE]
'Tastrophe!
Damn, Butchie.
He got away from you.
No, he's right there!
Now hold him tight this time!
Careful, he's strong.
Stronger than I thought he'd be,
even without all his blades.
[ZORO] This is getting
worse by the second.
If Tubby there
woulda landed on me,
I'da been pounded into the dust.
We'll get him
for sure this time.
You got that right.
One-Sword Technique's not my
forte fellas, but what the hell.
Let's go, Butchie!
Right, Siam! Let's do it!
[BUTCHIE, SIAM]
Pussy Willow March!
[BUTCHIE, SIAM yell]
This isn't good. They got
him on the defensive.
What are you doing, Usopp?
There's no way that Zoro
can gain any ground
if he's too busy blocking their
attacks. I'm gonna help him.
Take this.
Lead Star!
[grunts]
[gasps]
This is our chance!
[ZORO groans]
You're supposed to shoot
at the bad guys, you idiot!
[USOPP]
But I did.
It was... It was like he moved
in front of my shot on purpose.
But why would he do that?
[gasps]
[ZORO groaning]
You dumbass. Don't help me.
You wanna die?
[whimpers]
[ALL grunting]
[NAMI]
It's just a thought, but--
Maybe it's the two of us
who just got saved.
If you had actually hit
one of those guys,
they would've come
after us instead.
And we wouldn't have a chance
of holding up against that.
What a guy.
All this time he
was worried about us.
[ZORO]
If I just had one more sword,
I could take these guys!
I'm gonna get the swords.
If I can get them back to Zoro,
there'll be no way he can lose.
Let me get the swords!
Don't push yourself.
You can barely even
stand up on your own.
Nami!
[gasps]
--[thud]
--[gasps]
Nami!
[JANGO]
What do you need swords for?
[screams]
[SIAM, BUTCHIE scream]
No. I'm sorry. I can...
explain all of this.
[KURO]
The night has long since passed.
So why is it that you seem
to have made no
progress on the plan?
Captain... Kuro... No!
He'll-He'll kill us all!
It's all over.
[groaning]
[snoring]
What the hell is going on?!
As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...
[ZORO]
What do you mean?
Did they have a falling out?
[NAMI] He's handling those
two like they were nothing.
[ZORO]
I can't find Kuro anywhere.
[NAMI, ZORO]
Kaya, look out!
[ZORO]
What's she doing here?
Where's Luffy?
[NAMI]
Still asleep! Ugh!
[ZORO, NAMI]
Wake up already!
[LUFFY]
I-I'll protect the meat shop.
On the next One Piece:
"Luffy Back in Action!
Miss Kaya's
Desperate Resistance!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!