[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit of
dreams greater than they've
ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!
[KURO]
Jango!
Uh, sir!
I can handle the boy.
You take care of Miss
Kaya like we planned.
Have her write her butler
into her will. Then kill her!
[USOPP whimpering]
[USOPP]
Stay away from her.
Usopp Pirates!
Protect Kaya.
[ZORO]
Luffy!
Me and Usopp are gonna chase
down that hypno freak.
Is that a problem?
[LUFFY]
No. Hurry!
Usopp, Zoro! Get going!
You cocky jerk!
[LUFFY yelps]
Yeah. That's Captain
Kuro for ya'.
[PIRATES cheering, laughing]
Shut up. Don't call
me that! You fools.
This whole plan was devised
so that I may be rid of
that name once and for all.
Concocting plans everyday for
a bunch of barbarians who care
only about havoc and mayhem!
Relentlessly attacked
by government dogs
and bounty hunters.
I am sick and tired of
that entire cursed life!
[LUFFY grunting]
No, this can't be!
[LUFFY] I've been toughening
myself up to be a pirate!
[LUFFY grunts]
[KURO groans]
Ya know what?
Don't want a reputation?
Then don't be a pirate!
[LUFFY chuckles]
You're just greedy, Kuro.
But I have ambition!
"Protect Kaya! The Usopp
Pirate's Great Efforts!"
[PEPPER, ONION, CARROT panting]
Onion, is that weird hypnotist
guy still behind us?!
I don't know I can't
see him anymore.
Let's make sure and
lose him for good!
There's no way that nut job
could catch up to us
in our own forest!
[ONION]
Don't you worry, Miss Kaya!
The Usopp Pirates are gonna
keep you safe and sound!
[PEPPER] That's right! The Usopp
Pirates stand by their word!
[KAYA]
Thank you so much.
[ALL panting]
[ALL gasp]
[JANGO]
Well, they're not there.
Fools, I'm coming to get you!
Do you really think
you can run from me?!
[JANGO]
We could do this the easy way,
or I could just level
this entire forest!
[CARROT]
Whoa! That guy is really mad.
[PEPPER] And he can do a lot
more than just hypnotize people!
Where have you gone?
[PEPPER, ONION sigh]
--[CARROT] Ah-ah-ah...!
--[PEPPER, ONION gasp]
[ALL sigh]
[JANGO] Come out, come
out, wherever you are!
Go east! Hey, I said go east!
So go east already!
This is the wrong direction!
[ZORO] Fine, east.
Is that left or right?!
[USOPP]
Turn right!
[ZORO]
But that's where we came from!
[KAYA grunts]
[PEPPER, ONION, CARROT gasp]
Miss Kaya!
[KAYA] I'm sorry.
You should go on with out me.
[CARROT]
What are you talking about?!
We are under strict
orders to protect you!
[ONION] Oh no!
She's got a really bad fever!
[CARROT]
What?! Hang in there Kaya!
A doctor! We need a doctor!
[PEPPER] You idiot!
We don't have time for that!
Someone's tryin' to kill her!
[ONION] But it's dangerous
for her to run anymore!
[PEPPER]
Yeah but--
[JANGO]
Show yourselves, you runts!
[ALL gasp]
[KAYA]
Thank you... for helping me.
Just the thought is more than
enough. Now go, all of you.
Where did you brats go?!
It's no use running!
Come on out!
[PEPPER, CARROT, ONION whimper]
[PEPPER] If we left Kaya
and ran away right now,
we would probably
survive, right?
[ONION]
Yeah. Probably.
[CARROT] And our Captain
always said to run
with your tail between your legs
if you think you're gonna lose.
[JANGO] Those brats
think they can mock me?!
[panting]
Then again, our
captain is a liar.
But even he didn't
take his own advice.
He tried so hard to protect us.
He risked his life for us!
[CARROT sighs]
I swore to protect Kaya!
[PEPPER] All right then! Prepare
yourselves, Usopp Pirates!
[ONION]
We gotta fight him!
[CARROT]
Let's do it!
Stop this! You're no match
for him, you're only kids!
You mustn't put your life
on the line for my sake!
If we don't wanna die, we
have to fight for our lives!
[KAYA]
Uh?!
[CARROT] Just like our
captain always said.
[PEPPER, ONION]
Mm.
Gotcha.
Wait! He just--
He just broke Captain
Kuro's "cat claw".
[KURO grunting]
[LUFFY] That leaves only five
more of those weird swords.
[LUFFY chuckles]
[PIRATE A] Don't worry guys!
He can still fight plenty!
[PIRATE G] Yeah! He still
has that other claw!
You can do it! Rip that guy
to shreds, Captain Kuro!
[PIRATE Z]
Don't use that name anymore.
He doesn't like it, remember?
I think in this village his
name is Klaha... something.
Klaha-something?
Yeah! Klaha-something!
Get him good!
[KURO]
Shut your mouths! All of you!
Soon enough I'll deal with you
in the only
appropriate manner...
Extermination! I'll also
kill that fool Jango!
But, why kill us, Captain?!
C'mon please don't joke around
like that Captain Kuro!
[PIRATE O]
It's still not too late
for us to attack
the village, right?
[PIRATE Z]
Yeah!
And if Captain Jango gets
her to write her will,
then your plan should
still work perfectly!
This plan is no longer
any of your concern.
When all of you are dead,
this village will know who
to blame for this atrocity.
[PIRATES gasp]
[KURO] I never intended
to let any of you mongrels
leave this village alive.
No one... No one who
knows my true identity
can be allowed to live
to tell about it.
No way.
You had already planned to
kill every last one of us
from the very beginning.
[KURO chuckles]
That's right.
Three years ago I planned
to erase Captain Kuro,
and every last person
who ever knew him.
It's all part of
my plan! [chuckles]
[LUFFY]
You guys are dumb.
You're the most uncool
pirates I know.
Huh. We're "uncool", huh?
Pirates are nothing
more than savages,
incapable of rising above
their animal nature.
Without my plans, what could
they possibly accomplish?
A crew is nothing to me. They
are simply a means to an end.
Crewmembers are just
pawns in the Captain's game.
Whether my men live or die
is up to me and me alone.
If I tell them to fight,
they will fight,
and if I order them to die,
they had better do it.
They know the punishment
for disobedience.
Huh?!
[growls]
[KURO]
This is how pirates are!
Don't you dare talk
down to me, boy!
[PIRATES murumur]
[KURO growls]
[LUFFY] You know, no
matter how many hundreds,
or thousands of men follow
you as their Captain.
You will never be
as good as Usopp!
[PIRATES gasp]
You fool. Are you
saying that I am inferior
to a kid pretending
to be a pirate?
That's right!
[laughs] Well aren't you
funny?! Don't get all cocky
just because you snapped
off one of my cat claws!
How exactly is he better
than me?! Let's hear it!
'Cause he's got heart.
[KURO]
He's got what?
[LUFFY] A guy like you doesn't
know what a true pirate is!
[PIRATES stammer]
[PIRATE A]
Impossible!
[PIRATE I] He kept up with
the pussyfoot maneuver!
[KURO]
How insulting.
[KURO] It would appear
that you need a lesson
in what real pirates are like.
It's not pleasant.
Your first lesson
will be about terror.
A lesson I learned well
as I stared down death!
Hey! Should he be
in that stance?!
No, this is bad!
[PIRATE X] Why's he
using that technique?!
[PIRATE DD]
He's only fighting one guy.
There's no reason to use the
Out of the Back Attack!
[PIRATE X]
This isn't a good spot for us!
I mean, he could get us too!
[PIRATE M] Yeah. He did say he
was gonna kill us all earlier.
[PIRATE DD] Please Captain Kuro!
Anything but that technique!
[PIRATE G]
We'll do anything, Captain!
[PIRATE X]
Please, Captain Kuro!
What's the big deal? He's just
wobbling back and forth.
[PIRATES begging]
[gasps]
We're begging you,
Captain! Let us live!
[PIRATES chattering]
[KURO]
Out of the Back Attack!
[NAMI grunts]
What a small haul!
You know I really thought they'd
have more treasure than this!
Let's see if the boys have
finished this fight yet.
Huh? What...? Everyone
has stopped... Is it over?
[PIRATE EE screams]
[LUFFY gasps]
What's he doing over there?!
[PIRATES screaming]
[LUFFY gasps]
That guy's everywhere!
[PIRATES groaning]
Don't do this Captain!
Please stop!
We're dead!
We can't reason with him
now that he's started!
His sidestep maneuver is so fast
not even he knows
what he's cutting!
But how could he have killed
so many of us without even--
--[groans]
--No!
[NAMI]
What's happening out there?!
People are just getting
cut to ribbons!
[PIRATES screaming, groaning]
[LUFFY]
Show yourself...
Butler!
[LUFFY growls]
Don't you have any honor?!
Those men are your friends!
Luffy...
[LUFFY groans]
[LUFFY yells]
[LUFFY panting]
I found you.
You bastard.
You should've accepted
your fate like a good boy...
Now look what you've done!
Thanks to you, my little pawns
are still alive, and in misery.
It would have been better to
just let them die in the attack.
[KURO] So, now what?
Do you have something to say?
[LUFFY]
Yeah.
No matter what happens to me...
I will never be like you...
[KURO]
Not "will".
Someone like you...
can't be like me.
[KURO]
You see...
You are going to die here today.
But first, you'll
writhe in agony
as I hack you up like a fish.
I'm going to carve you up...
and I'm going to enjoy it.
Uh!
No you won't!
Out of the Back Attack!
[LUFFY gasps]
[LUFFY grunts]
Come out you brats!
I know you're hiding!
Give yourselves up!
[JANGO]
Huh?
[PEPPER] We surrender!
We'll hand her over to you!
Come over here, and we'll take
you to her! Just don't kill us!
Do you think I'm stupid?
I won't fall for that...
You silly rug rats.
[ONION grunts]
[JANGO]
Oh, dammit...
We got him...! Now!
[ONION yells]
[screams]
[ONION]
Pepper Attack!
[JANGO sneezes]
[CARROT yells]
[JANGO screams]
[JANGO sneezes]
I knew it!
Those worthless brats were
lying to me from the beginning!
[ALL grunting]
Push!
[JANGO screams]
[JANGO]
Oww! Oww!
Ow!
[BOYS]
End of the line, hypnotist!
[JANGO]
Huh?
[PEPPER, CARROT yell]
[BOYS groan]
[JANGO] Looks like you bit off a
little more than you could chew.
[PEPPER]
No! We failed!
[JANGO]
Real pirates don't take kindly
to being mocked by
the likes of you!
[BOTH]
Onion!
[JANGO] You pretend pirates
sure got in over your heads,
didn't you?
[CARROT]
Uh!
[PEPPER]
Rich girl, I know you're here!
Listen! Unless you show yourself
I'll execute these
three little lambs...
And I will make sure to do it
in a most painful fashion!
Do not doubt my skill
at such a task!
There you are.
[PEPPER, ONION, CARROT]
Uh.
[ONION]
No!
[PEPPER]
Miss Kaya! Run for your life!
[CARROT]
Run!
--Hey!
--Yeah. That's them all aright.
[ZORO]
They're the other way!
There's no need for that.
Please, leave the children
be. I'll write the will.
No, Kaya!
He's gonna kill you as soon
as you write that will!
I'm sorry...
Silly girl. Don't you know
you can't bargain with me?
Captain Kuro specifically
instructed me
to get rid of everyone.
[KAYA]
No!
[BOYS whimper]
[JANGO]
Wha...?!
If you don't do exactly as I say
then you won't get to kill me,
and, I won't write my will!
[JANGO]
Hold on! Hold on!
Just calm down!
Don't be so hasty!
I absolutely have to get
you to write that will!
Stop! Kaya!
All right! Fine, I'll let
the little brats go...
But, in their condition,
they won't be making
too quick of a getaway.
[CARROT whimpers]
[JANGO]
Here.
Don't forget to sign your name.
[KAYA]
I know.
[BOYS whimper]
This sucks.
[JANGO chuckles] "I leave my
entire fortune to my butler,
Klahadore," Yes...
Very good! This is your will,
all right! Excellent work!
Now remember, we had a deal.
You promised me you
wouldn't kill them.
Just relax. I know I
may not look like it,
but I'm regarded
as an honest man.
[KAYA whimpering]
[PEPPER, ONION, CARROT]
Kaya!
[USOPP]
There!
[BOTH shouting]
Over there!
--[ZORO] Okay! I'll be back!
--[USOPP] What the...!
That's enough of that,
hypno-freak! Let the girl go!
[JANGO] Damnit! Looks
like I was followed!
[KAYA groaning]
[ALL gasp]
I guess I'd better finish off
the rich girl quickly then.
As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...
[ZORO] All finished here!
The rest is up to you!
[LUFFY] I won't lose to someone
who ditches his name
and runs from the sea!
Remember my name for
the rest of your life!
[NAMI]
What are you so mad about?
[LUFFY] I hate him!
That man is scum!
[NAMI]
That's what pirates are like!
[LUFFY] That's not
what friends are like!
On the next One Piece!
Anger explosion!
Kuro vs. Luffy, how it ends!
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!