[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit of
dreams greater than they've
ever dared to imagine!
This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!
[LUFFY]
"Zeff and Sanji's dream!
The Illusory All Blue!"
Ghin!
[GHIN] I don't care how much
of a bad ass he used to be;
now he's just a cook.
I wouldn't have to break a
sweat to kill this old fart.
I'll spare him,
but you have to leave.
Please, don't make this any
harder, Sanji. Just leave.
Don't force me to
kill both of you.
Run away... Not a chance!
[gasps]
[SANJI] You look even dumber
at gunpoint, Old Man.
What kind of example
do you think you're setting
for all the other cooks?
Hah! I don't need a lecture
from a brat like you.
Would you stop
calling me names?!
Quit treating me like a kid!
This is crazy!
Sanji wouldn't abandon
Zeff now would he?
[SANJI]
Ghin, point that gun at me.
[ZEFF grunts]
Hey, but what if you die?!
Shut up.
Sanji, why you?
[PEARL]
Someone's eager to die.
Lucky for you, I'd be
more than happy to oblige.
Allow me...
It would be my pleasure to beat
you to a bloody, lifeless pulp.
[grunts]
[PEARL]
The absolutely natural Pearl...
[SANJI gasps]
[PEARL]
Surprise!
[SANJI grunts]
Sanji!
Why didn't you dodge that?!
[SANJI grunts]
Because if I did,
that rat over there would
pull the trigger on Zeff.
[huffs]
[GHIN]
Why are you doing this?
Just leave the restaurant
peacefully and no one gets hurt.
Please!
This restaurant is
that old man's life!
[SANJI] I've already
taken everything else
that man holds dear.
[SANJI]
His power...
...his dreams...
[SANJI grunts]
So, while I'm around...
...I'm not gonna let anything
else get taken from him!
[ZEFF grunts]
Behind you!
[PEARL]
Pearl... Cymbals!
[CARNE]
Sanji!
[LUFFY grunting]
[SANJI groans]
The All Blue?
[SANJI]
Yeah! It's out there somewhere.
And I'll bet it's even
awesomer than they say it is!
[COOK A]
Stop being a doofus.
That's just a fairy tale
for seafaring cooks.
[COOK B]
Don't get me wrong,
we've all had our little
fantasies about it,
but you gotta remember
that it's just a dream.
A dream? Well I'm
gonna find the All Blue,
then we'll see
who's dreaming.
That's quite the quest.
Good luck!
All right there little man.
Tell me, do you even know what
kind of place the All Blue is?
[SAJNI]
Yeah, I do. I'm not an idiot.
The All Blue is a place where
fish from all four seas live.
There're fish from
East Blue, the West Blue,
the North Blue,
and the South Blue.
To cooks who have
taken to the sea,
it's an irresistible paradise!
I'll find it!
Oh yeah! That place
is a goldmine!
It's got fish and plants
from all over the world!
Any chef would jump at
the chance to cook there!
True. The cooks I know would
risk life and limb to find it.
[COOK A]
Yeah! Well, if it were real.
Oh?
You think a miracle sea like the
All Blue could actually exist?
Think about it kid,
it's impossible.
[COOK C] Ha, ha! I bet
it's probably just a lie
told by some daydreaming cook.
[COOK A] Okay, enough
with the silly stories.
Get out there and collect
some plates, Sanji.
[SANJI]
Hmph.
[COOK A]
Aw man. What a waste!
They left behind
plates and plates
full of this delicious grub.
[COOK C] This one's
barely been touched!
It's pretty good stuff too. I
thought they'd love it for sure.
[COOK B] If you ask me,
the customers these days
are spoiled.
It's way gross to eat
the leftovers of strangers.
You should just let me
throw that stuff away.
That kind of talk proves
you gotta whole lot to learn,
so listen up, shorty.
If you choose life on the high
seas, you gotta be resourceful.
The ocean is a strange
and unpredictable place,
where wasting food
could be a fatal mistake.
So, why don't you
have some? Heh?
No way!
[COOK II giggles]
[PASSENGERS screaming]
Calm down, people!
Panicking won't help!
[SANJI, COOKS]
Hm?
[SAILOR B grunts]
Pirates are here!
[COOKS whimper]
[gasps]
What?
Pirates?
[SAILOR C]
That ship.
It's Red Foot Zeff
and the Cook Pirates!
[SANJI grunts]
[SAILOR B] They're back...
from the Grand Line!
[PIRATES chuckle]
[ZEFF laughs]
I take it you're the
infamous pirate captain
Red Foot Zeff.
So, what do you want?
Steal!
[PIRATES yelling]
[ZEFF] Steal everything
that isn't nailed down!
[PASSENGERS screaming]
[SANJI]
Those bastards!
I refuse to die at the
hands of those animals!
[PIRATE 2]
Whoa, look at this!
Hey, Killer,
if you're not careful,
you might just put
someone's eye out with that.
He got me. Look, I'm bleeding.
Shut up! You mongrels
better stay away from me!
[COOK A yelps]
Sanji!
Stop it! You'll make them mad!
[ZEFF] A bit young
to have a death wish,
but that's no reason
not to grant it.
All right, you jerks!
If I'm dying here, then I'm
takin' some of you with me!
[SANJI gasps]
[SANJI]
Ah!
Sanji!
Wow, good one!
Yeah, that was brutal!
[PIRATES chuckle]
[SANJI grunts]
[SANJI]
I'm not gonna die.
Not here... Ah!
I've got to live...
...so that I can
find the All Blue!
[ALL laughing]
[PIRATE 3]
He said, "the All Blue!"
[PIRATE 4]
Pretty ambitious!
[PIRATE 1]
Oh, that's a good one!
Hey Captain, should we tell the
little tyke it doesn't exist?
[COOKS whimpering]
That fool...
He won't shut up!
[ZEFF growls]
[wood cracking]
[SANJI groaning]
No...
I'm not gonna draw
my last breath
until I've seen the All Blue.
[PIRATE 3]
Captain!
I recommend we
withdraw, immediately!
This storm is way
bigger than expected!
[ZEFF]
All right men, playtime's over.
Let's load up the treasure
and get out of here.
[whimpering]
[ALL yelling]
[gasps]
[SANJI grunts]
[yelling]
Sanji!
[ZEFF grumbles]
[PIRATE 2]
The Captain!
Damn brat!
[PIRATE 5]
Captain!
[PIRATE 3] Why'd he risk
his life for one measly kid?
[PIRATES]
Huh?
[PIRATES screaming]
[ZEFF]
The brat finally wakes up.
You're lucky to
be alive, you know.
[SANJI groans]
You!
[ZEFF]
Moving isn't a good idea.
You're still pretty banged up
from the beating you took.
[SANJI gasps]
[SANJI]
What about the ships?
[ZEFF]
Who knows?
It was terrible storm.
Our ships were most
likely destroyed.
Seems we're the
only survivors.
Washed ashore on
a desolate rock,
without so much as a
coconut tree to give us food.
Sure, there are fish in the sea,
but the rock has been curved
by the waves in such a manner
that we wouldn't be
able to climb back up,
if we ever went down.
Sad, isn't it?
This is all your fault, Old Man!
I hope you die!
[ZEFF] You can whine all
you want, it won't help.
If nobody comes,
we'll just dry up and become
two more skeletons in the sea.
Skeletons?
Really?
[ZEFF] That bag there...
It's your share of it.
Ah!
[ZEFF] It's some of the
food that washed up.
Should be about five days worth.
It's not much, but it's
better than nothin'.
If you ration it out,
it'll last longer,
so use your head when you eat.
Good thing we're
both cooks, huh?
Hey, wait!
Is that bag your
share of the food?!
You got way more than me!
You fat, old pig!
[grunting]
[ZEFF]
Of course I get more food...
I'm a grown man, so I
need more to survive
than a runt like you.
You should be grateful that
I'm sharing any of it with you.
Don't expect any pity
from me, you little brat!
[growling]
Bastard!
[ZEFF] Get to the other side of
this rock and watch for ships.
Let me know as
soon as you see one.
Until then, don't bother talkin'
to me or movin' from your post.
That'll just waste energy,
and we can't afford that.
Good luck.
Screw you, gramps.
I'm not saying anything
if I see a ship.
I'll be fine. I have five
whole days worth of food.
We'll definitely see a ship
or two before I run out.
I'm sure of it.
Just to be extra safe, I'll
divide it up for twenty days.
That's more than enough
time to get rescued.
I guess all I gotta
do now is sit and wait.
Easy! I'll make it
through this thing...
No problem!
[SANJI grunts]
Didn't see a ship today.
That's all right.
It'll only be a few more days.
[SANJI]
I don't wanna die...
[SANJI weakly]
This is it...
One moldy piece of bread.
[COOK A]
Aw man, what a waste.
They left behind
plates and plates
full of this
delicious grub.
[SANJI] It's way gross to eat
the leftovers of strangers.
You should just let me
throw that stuff away.
So, why don't you
have some... huh?
[SANJI]
No way!
--[sniffling]
--[stomach growls]
[SANJI yelps]
[SANJI screams]
[SANJI gasps]
[SANJI]
My last piece of bread.
I wonder...
Is the geezer dead yet?
[SANJI grunting]
[SANJI gasps]
He's alive...
And he's still got food!
A lot of food!
So much.
There's so much left!
I've got to get that food.
It's not fair that he has
so much more than me.
Besides, this is all his fault!
[ZEFF] What're you
doing here, ya' brat?
[gasps]
[ZEFF] Are you here
because ya' saw a ship?
[panting]
I came over here to
steal your food, Old Man.
If you wanna kill
me for it, go ahead.
Soon enough I'll starve, so
it makes no difference to me.
[SANJI panting]
[huffs]
[clattering]
[ZEFF] Didn't I tell you
not to come over here
unless you saw a ship?
[SANJI]
Why?
You said it's... food.
[ZEFF]
Strange, isn't it?
We have all this money and
yet, we're going to starve.
[labored breathing]
It's only treasure...
It's worthless.
[labored breathing]
[SANJI] Hey! What's
going on here, Old Man?
Where's your food?
You had to have eaten something!
Now, where is it?
I'm talking to you!
Answer me!
[SANJI gasps]
What happened to your leg?
[gasps]
[SANJI]
It was then.
So, it wasn't a dream...
In order to save me, you...
[whimpers]
The food...
Did you give me all
of the food you had?
I did.
And you had to have known
that without that leg,
you'd never be a pirate again.
[ZEFF]
That's right.
[gasps] You old fool.
Why'd you help me?
It doesn't make sense to
sacrifice so much for me!
So, why?
Tell me!
[ZEFF]
Because...
For my entire life I've
had the same dream as you.
The All Blue...
But... your men said
that it doesn't exist.
[ZEFF]
Of course it does!
Never mind them.
When the time comes,
head to the Grand Line.
That's where the All
Blue is sure to be.
My days as a pirate are done,
but you have your
whole life to find it.
[ZEFF sighs]
Don't die, now! Get up!
C'mon, Old Man!
Don't you dare give up!
[ZEFF]
I wonder...
How many men have lost their
lives cursing the ocean,
knowing that it will
soon be their grave.
This isn't the first time
I've been hungry enough
to look death in the eyes,
and my thoughts are
the same each time.
It is always my deepest wish
that there be a restaurant
in the middle of the sea.
[SANJI]
A restaurant?
[ZEFF]
Yeah, I was thinking that
if I make it out
of this mess alive,
I'd like to build a restaurant
as my final purpose in life.
Great! And I'll
even help you do it!
So, don't die okay? Ha!
Ha, ha!
A weak little brat like you
couldn't be much
good for anything.
Then, I'll become strong!
[whimpers]
So... Don't die!
[whimpering]
[gasps]
[whimpers]
Hey!
Help!
The geezer needs help!
Over here!
Please help!
Please, please!
Help us!
[ZEFF groans]
[SANJI]
Hey!
Over here! Help us!
This way! Please, please!
Over here! Over here!
Help, help! This way!
Please!
[SANJI]
That old coot...
He gave up his leg
so that I could live!
[ALL gasping]
[SANJI grunts]
There's no way to repay the
old geezer for his kindness,
unless I risk my life for him!
Why? Why are you
standing, Sanji?
Stay down!
'Fraid I can't do that.
It's a little too
much like giving up.
[COOKS gasp]
Idiot! They'll kill you!
[LUFFY grunting]
You little brat!
Ha! That is so very
refined of you!
But, this restaurant
will be closing soon,
and it'll open again
for business...
...as a pirate ship.
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY yells]
No! Don't!
Ghin'll shoot the old man!
[PATTY, CARNE gasp]
[COOK D]
What'd he do?
Now, Gum-Gum!
Battle-Axe!
As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...
[LUFFY] They call themselves
the strongest in the East Blue,
but it's because they
had so many pirates!
[ZEFF]
You sure don't mince words.
[LUFFY] Look, it seems like
Ghin can't defeat Sanji either.
[ZEFF]
Not quite.
[LUFFY] What were those weapons
that look like dumplings?
Wait, he wasn't an underling?
On the next One Piece,
"Coolheaded, Coldhearted Demon!
Pirate Fleet Chief
Commander, Ghin!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!