[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever dared
to imagine! This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!
Say goodbye, swords. Goodbye!
[ZORO]
Huh? Ah!
There it is.
Cat Burglar.
One-Sword Technique's not my
forte fellas, but what the hell.
Let's, go. Butchie!
Right, Siam! Let's do it!
[ZORO] If I just had one more
sword, I could take these guys!
[NAMI] I'm gonna get
the swords back to Zoro!
[NAMI gasps]
[JANGO]
What do you need swords for?
[screaming]
[LUFFY]
"Luffy Back in Action!
Miss Kaya's
Desperate Resistance!"
[snoring]
[ALL whimpering]
[whimpering]
[KURO] To think that these
brats have held you back.
How the Black Cat
Pirates have fallen.
[KURO] What have you got
to say for yourself? Jango!
[JANGO] But... Uh...
Well... I... You said...
Uh, sorry, sir,
but... you said letting the kid
go wouldn't cause any problems.
[JANGO chuckles nervously]
[KURO]
I did say that.
[USOPP]
Huh?
What's your point?
He's an idiot.
I knew no one would
listen to his warnings
and he would come stumbling back
to take a stand against us.
But the one thing I
hadn't taken account for,
was your inexcusable weakness!
Sir. We're not weak.
It's just that--
[grumbles]
[SIAM]
Who are you to call us weak?!
[BUTCHIE] Watch what
you say, Captain Kuro!
[SIAM]
You used to be quite the killer.
But, face it, Kuro,
it's been three years,
and we haven't exactly
been living the good life
waiting on a rich
girl hand and foot.
[BUTCHIE chuckles]
Yeah, that's right!
For three long years, we've
been out sinking pirate ships
and massacring villages!
Very good. Finished?
No! You've done nothing this
whole time! We've been killing!
You butler! There's no way you
can beat the Meowban Brothers!
[ZORO gasps]
Don't! Butchie, Siam, stop!
[BUTCHIE, SIAM yelling]
[SIAM]
You are not our captain anymore!
[SIAM laughing]
[BUTCHIE] So sorry,
but we have to kill you!
[BOTH laughing]
[yelling]
[BOTH yelling]
[ZORO grunts]
What? He's behind 'em?
How the hell'd he--?
And what're those crazy weapons?
[KURO] Who? Who are
you going to kill?
[BUTCHIE, SIAM yelp]
He snuck up!
Right behind us!
[SIAM]
Huh?
[BUTCHIE]
Ah! He-He's gone!
[groaning]
[JANGO]
The... Pussyfoot Maneuver.
[NAMI]
Pussyfoot?
[BUTCHIE, SIAM whimpering]
[KURO]
You know, you're right.
[BUTCHIE, SIAM whimpering]
I do feel... a bit sluggish
after all these years.
[gasps]
[NAMI]
He's handling them like babies.
And, those two
nearly defeated Zoro.
[JANGO]
With his Pussyfoot Maneuver,
Captain Kuro could shred
everyone on this beach
before we drew our next breath.
We wouldn't even see it coming.
There is no escape from a
killing machine like him.
I knew he hadn't grown soft when
I saw that old habit of his,
that strange way of
lifting his glasses
so that he won't cut his face.
It's like he never stopped
wearing those cat claws.
They're almost
a part of his body.
Of course, he hasn't
forgotten how to fight.
[whimpers]
You're very lucky.
I'm feeling somewhat merciful.
Maybe these years on dry
land have made me soft.
[KURO]
I'll give you five minutes.
[KURO] If you can't
deal with the situation here
in five minutes, then I'll
kill every last one of you.
Now, have I made myself clear?
[JANGO whimpers]
Oh, yes.
[laughs nervously]
Yes, of course,
that's perfectly clear!
Thank you for being
so forgiving!
All we have to do is
take care of this one guy!
That's all.
Five minutes will be more
than enough time for them.
[JANGO laughs nervously]
[BUTCHIE] We nearly had
him a few minutes ago!
[SIAM] We won't need one
minute to finish him this time!
We're counting on you!
Kill him! Kill him, dead!
--[footsteps]
--[JANGO] Hm?
Zoro!
What the--?!
Hey! Easy there! You can't just
kick 'em! Those're my swords!
How 'bout a "thanks"?
[ZORO]
Yeah.
Ha. I appreciate it.
[SIAM] You idiot! It won't
matter how many swords you have!
[BUTCHIE] Now you'll die
holding three of 'em!
[ZORO]
Tiger!
[laughing]
You still... don't... get it.
Trap!
The clock is ticking.
[ZORO] Carrying three swords
won't help you at all.
Unless, you know
Three-Swords Style.
Oh no.
This is bad.
[JANGO] He took down the Meowban
Brothers with one attack!
[ZORO laughing]
[ZORO]
Don't worry.
I can promise you. Everything
will be taken care of...
...in less than five minutes.
[chuckles]
Three. Three minutes left.
[JANGO]
Hm?
[gasps]
[BUTCHIE groaning]
[BUTCHIE]
I'll... I'll slaughter him.
[BUTCHIE coughs]
Please... Captain.
I can do it... Hypnotize me!
[BUTCHIE coughs]
Just... do it... Captain!
He's still alive.
You do sloppy work.
[ZORO]
Huh?
So he is. I guess all that
blubber protected his vitals.
[gasps]
[growling]
Butchie! Kill him!
What?! Really?
You back for more?
[ZORO]
This guy means business.
He was trouble when
he was half this size.
[ZORO] Then Jango had to
flip his psycho switch.
[NAMI]
Now's my chance!
I gotta wake that lazy
jerk up while I still can!
[JANGO]
What is that girl up to?
Something tricky I'm sure.
[NAMI] Everyone else is
busy fighting for their lives
and he's just sleeping!
Get up! You bum!
Nami! Look out!
[gasps]
Two minutes. And counting.
Get up! You bum!
Nami! Look out!
[gasps]
[JANGO chuckles]
It was nice knowing you.
Dodge it! Quick!
Hey! Stop it!
[NAMI] I thought it was
just a hypnotic charm,
but it's also his weapon!
Nami! You can not just go around
stepping on people's eyes!
[LUFFY grunts]
No! How is that
twerp still alive?!
That's either the best timing,
or the worst timing in
the world. I can't tell.
[LUFFy grunts]
Uh. Luffy?
[growls]
Luffy!
Owww!
Crap! That guy's
back in the battle!
No! This is terrible!
Five minutes'll
never be enough time!
Uh! That hurts, you jerk!
Why'd you do that?!
Hey, sleeping beauty,
that wasn't me!
It wasn't... me...
You okay? Nami, did you
get hurt? Let me see it.
[NAMI]
Oh, it's nothing. I'm fine.
I've done everything
I can for now.
The rest is up to you.
[groans]
Look, we have to win. We can't
afford to lose this fight.
Do you understand?
Do it... for the treasure!
Well, all right. Sure.
Okay. Go. Win this and
protect my treasure.
[LUFFY] Yeah, yeah,
the treasure, I get it.
One minute. And counting.
Kuro can't be serious!
We can't possibly finish
them in one minute!
C'mon, guys, stop messing
around and end this already!
Butchie! Quickly! There's
no more time to waste!
Kill that three sword bastard!
I'll take care of the
freaky, bendable kid!
[JANGO]
I'm coming for you, Straw Hat!
Hmph. Times up.
You knew the deal.
Now you die.
Hm? Hey, wait. Why is
that shady butler here?
It's that kid. Didn't
he die falling off a cliff?
Nice trick.
[KURO]
Huh?
Don't ever sneak up on me!
[KURO]
Unless you want to die!
Kaya!
No. Ussop. Are you okay?
[USOPP]
Kaya... what are you doing here?
Oh, Usopp. I'm so sorry.
I don't know how
you'll ever forgive me.
I just couldn't believe it...
...that Klahadore is a
scheming, murdering pirate.
[USOPP]
Nevermind that.
Why are you here?
Kaya, your life is in danger.
I told you to run
somewhere safe!
I won't! You're still here
fighting! I won't run!
You fought for me after
I treated you so badly.
Look at you,
you're barely alive,
but you're still so brave.
I just--
[KURO]
This is no place for a lady.
Madam, please leave.
Please. Stop. Don't do this.
Stop! Stop this right
now, Klahadore!
I know what you're up to.
Merry already told me
about everything.
[JANGO] Hm? What's the girl from
the mansion doing down here?
The whole reason
that we're here
is to murder that
little rich girl.
[PIRATE G]
If she's here,
then we don't have
to go to the village.
[PIRATE I] All we gotta
do is kill her, right?
[KAYA]
Klahadore, please.
If you want my fortune,
you can have it.
Take it all and leave
this village right now
I'm begging you.
[KURO] I will gladly accept
your fortune, Miss Kaya.
Thank you.
But I want more.
You see, simply acquiring
wealth isn't enough.
More than anything else.
What I want... is peace.
You want peace?
Yes. Just peace.
Peace of mind.
It's simple really.
I have spent the
last three years
earning the trust of
the entire village,
and, to be honest,
I find this new sense
of peace and tranquility
quite comforting.
When my plan comes to fruition,
I will live with this
sublime peace of mind.
Yes.
The glorious comfort
of a peaceful life
will be mine for
forever and ever.
In short, these
pirates are coming!
And you... will leave your
fortune to me and die.
Miss Kaya, these
things will happen.
No. You can't.
You just can't be.
Run away, Kaya! There's
no use talking to him!
Please! Get out of here!
[KAYA]
You're not Klahadore.
No! You're not!
Kaya...
Leave here, right now!
Never come back!
[KURO]
Oh, you'd point a gun at me?
Stop it! Just leave! Go!
Yes. I see. You're
all grown up now.
So much has happened
in the last three years.
Miss Kaya.
Don't you remember the
things we went through?
We spent so much time together.
Even before your dear sweet
parents passed away.
You were more than my master,
you were my best friend.
So much time.
So many memories.
Together we suffered and
together we rejoiced.
Like family.
Klahadore.
[KURO] I took you on
shopping trips to the city.
I looked after you so
diligently when you were ill.
And we used to talk
for hours and hours.
Kaya, listen to me.
I was devoted to you.
For so long.
For so very long.
I endured it.
I quietly suffered so that
today I could end your life
and take everything
that I deserve.
I, who was once the feared
and respected Captain Kuro,
had to bow and humble myself
before some snot-nosed
little girl.
It went against every
fiber of my being.
Damn you.
[KURO] Can you understand the
depth of these daily insults?
Can you understand the rage
created by those transgressions
against my pride?!
[USOPP]
Kuro!
Thank you for reminding me.
Usopp, I owe you for hitting me.
Let's get even.
Oh no, Usopp!
If I recall, you hit me as
hard as you could, right?
[USOPP]
Huh?
[USOPP yelps]
[groaning]
[LUFFY] If he hates
getting hit that much,
he's about to have
a really bad day!
As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...
[LUFFY]
Usopp! Go save Kaya!
Leave the butler to me!
[ZORO] That guy can't
help but to be evil.
[LUFFY] Too bad.
I had something else in mind.
[ZORO] I'm going
after that hypno freak.
[LUFFY] Kuro! You're not
cut out for this!
I'll show you what a real
pirate looks like!
On the next One Piece:
"Beat Kuro!
Usopp the Man's
Tearful Resolve!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!