[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever dared
to imagine! This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!
What's that?
[USOPP]
Uh?
[LUFFY]
Yahoo!
[yelling]
My goodness, are you okay?
Uhh...Don't mind them Kaya,
this happens to me all the time.
That's just the price of
being a famous adventurer!
They're just new recruits
who heard about me
and came to join
the Usopp pirates!
Nope, not me. I came
here to see you.
I wanted to ask you a favor
A favor? From me?
[LUFFY]
Uh-huh.
I was wondering if
there was any way
--you could help get us a boat.
--[KLAHADORE] You there!
What do you think you're doing?
Klahadore...
[USOPP gasps]
Get out!
I'll have you know that this
is criminal trespassing.
Who's there?
[LUFFY]
The weirdest guy ever!
Jango the hypnotist!
Uh, actually Klahadore,
these people are--
Not now, Kaya.
You can tell me all about this
riff-raff after they've left.
Now get out! All of you.
Leave now, unless you have
some business with me.
Alright! Do you think that you
could help us get a ship?
[KLAHADORE]
Certainly not!
[LUFFY]
Aww...
[KLAHADORE]
Usopp!
[USOPP]
Crap!
[KLAHADORE]
You have quite the reputation.
You are very well
known in the village.
[USOPP]
Eh... He. He. Sure am!
[KLAHADORE] I hear you've
been on many an adventure.
Quite impressive for
someone as young as you.
Usually, people who admire
me so much, call me Captain.
So, it's Captain Usopp to you!
[KLAHADORE]
Captain, huh? [laughs]
Your father also had
something of a reputation.
What?
[KAYA gasps]
Klahadore, please just stop!
You'll never be anything more
than the son of a filthy pirate.
Who knows what sort of
trouble you're up to now?
All I ask is that
you and your kind
leave this respectable
young lady alone.
A filthy pirate?!
[KLAHADORE] You and she are
from completely different worlds
and you know it!
Is it money you're after?
How much do you want?
Cease this at once, Klahadore!
Apologize to him!
Hey, calm down, Kaya.
I don't believe there is
any reason to apologize
to this savage
young man, My Lady.
[USOPP gasps]
[KLAHADORE]
My goal isn't to slander.
I am merely stating the truth.
I sympathize with
your situation.
You must hate your
great, idiot of a father
for abandoning his
family and his village
because of his mindless
lust for treasure!
Klahadore, stop!
Don't you dare insult
my father ever again!
--[USOPP grunts]
--[KAYA gasps] Usopp!
[KAYA gasps]
[USOPP grunts]
[USOPP growls]
Why have you gotten
so worked up Usopp?
It's times like these
when you should do what
you do best and lie.
Tell me about how your father
is really a traveling salesman,
or about how you aren't
really related by blood.
[USOPP]
Enough!
[KAYA gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[USOPP growls]
[KIDS]
Captain!
[KLAHADORE grunts]
Case in point.
He resorts to violence!
I guess the apple never falls
far from the tree, does it?
Shut up!
My father listened to his heart
and chose a life of
risk and adventure!
I am proud to say
that my old man
is a brave warrior of the sea!
You're right, I have been known
to exaggerate from time to time,
but I will never lie
about who my father is!
I refuse to be ashamed
of my heritage!
I am the son of a pirate!
[PEPPER, ONION whimper]
Captain...
[KLAHADORE laughs] Pirates
are brave warriors of the sea,
are they? [laughing]
That's quite a twisted
way of putting things.
You don't seem
to understand that
you are living proof
of his savage blood.
You run around spouting lies
and use violence when
you don't get your way.
To top it off,
you cozy up to the lady of
the house to steal her fortune.
You're wrong! I only--
You're father is a
filthy, no-good pirate!
Treachery is in your blood!
Of course you would hatch
such an evil scheme!
You won't let up, will you?!
Stop it Usopp! Please!
[USOPP grunts]
[KAYA]
No more violence.
I can't take it!
Klahadore isn't a bad person...
He's just...
He's just trying to do what
he thinks is best for me
and sometimes he goes too far.
[USOPP grumbles]
Leave this place.
You are never to
come here again!
Yeah, I get it.
You don't have to
tell me twice, buddy.
This is the last
you'll ever see of me.
[KAYA whimpers]
Usopp...
[KIDS growling]
Hey, you butler jerk!
Our Captain's not
that kinda guy!
Ya stupid jerk-face!
Jerk-face!
Shut up, You don't have
a bone to pick with him.
[KLAHADORE growls]
[KIDS yelling]
[NAMI] What are you doing?
Don't hide behind me!
[LUFFY] Let me go already!
C'mon, Zoro! I'm Serious!
Put me down! Put me down!
I'm going to kick his ass!
[KLAHADORE]
You will all leave immediately!
[KAYA coughing, whimpering]
[door knocking, squeaking]
Your meal is ready
now, Miss Kaya.
[KAYA]
No thank you, I don't want it.
[KLAHADORE sighs]
The cook would be most
upset to hear you say that.
He works his hardest,
day and night, to come up
with delicious meals
that suit your needs.
[silverware clinks]
[KAYA gasps]
[KAYA]
Why were you so cruel to him?
I know I was wrong to talk
to Usopp without telling you.
I will admit that much,
and I'm very sorry for
not being honest with you,
but this situation
did not warrant
that kind of harsh treatment.
May I sit down?
[KAYA]
Go ahead.
[KLAHADORE] It has
been quite some time
since I first arrived
at this house.
Soon it will be three years
that I have been in the
service of your family.
I will never forget
what happened
when I showed up at
your father's door.
[KAYA gasps]
[KAYA whimpers]
[KLAHADORE] My former employers
were brutal, pitiless men.
I'd been kicked off
the ship I worked on
for some small
blunder I had made.
And with no work or money,
I was on the verge of
dying like a beggar.
--[KAYA gasps]
--[GUARD A] Hey you, beat it!
[GUARD B]
Get outta here!
This isn't the place
for the likes of you!
[KAYA gasps]
Huh?
What? But, sir... He...
[GUARD A] Understood! Take
him inside and tend to him.
[KLAHADORE]
As far as I know,
I would've died without
your father's help.
I owe my life to your parents.
And now that they're gone,
I owe my life to you.
[KLAHADORE]
I know that it isn't my place
to interfere with
your friendships.
I wouldn't have taken
such a bold step
unless I thought it
absolutely necessary.
It's just that Usopp
isn't exactly known for
his upstanding character.
You see, If anything
were to happen to you,
it would be my fault for
not seeing to your safety
and I would never be able to ask
forgiveness from your parents!
Do you think ill of me for my
childish behavior earlier today?
No, of course I don't.
I'm thankful to have you
around too, Klahadore,
but I stand by my opinion.
Usopp is one of the
nicest people I know.
[KLAHADORE]
We'll see about that.
Until then, he is still
not welcome here.
Klahadore! You blockhead!
[KLAHADORE]
"Blockhead" will do just fine.
[NAMI]
Hey, Where'd Luffy go?
Who knows? He probably
ran after that captain.
I bet he's at his secret spot!
Yeah, over by the shore.
He always goes there when he's
gonna think something over.
Should we go see?
[ZORO]
Huh? He's fine.
[NAMI] Luffy can
take care of himself,
but where's your other friend?
[PEPPER, CARROT]
Oh yeah, Onion!
Come to think of it, he just
up and disappears a lot.
Yeah! And then he shows up
outta nowhere all freaked out!
[ONION screaming]
Terrible news, guys!
You see?
[ONION]
Listen to me!
Some nut job is on his way here
and he only walks backwards!
[PEPPER, CARROT]
You liar.
It's the truth!
There he is!
[NAMI, PEPPER, CARROT]
Hm?
Now, which one of you people
has the nerve to call me weird?
I'm just a normal guy.
S'that so? You look insane.
[JANGO]
Don't be silly.
I'm just an ordinary,
run of the mill hypnotist.
[ONION]
A hypnotist? Really? Awesome!
[PEPPER]
Show us something!
[CARROT]
Yeah! Do something!
What?!
You fools, what makes you think
that I would want to reveal
my masterful
hypnosis techniques
to a bunch of
roadside strangers?
[JANGO]
Okay, you convinced me.
Now, watch the ring closely.
[ZORO]
What a ham!
So, by the count of "Jango,"
you'll be in a deep sleep.
Alright, are you ready?
[KIDS gasping]
[JANGO]
One...
Two...
Jango!
[KIDS, JANGO snoring]
[ZORO]
Who is this freaky weirdo?!
[LUFFY]
Hi!
[USOPP gasps]
What're you doin' here?
[USOPP]
I came here to be alone,
but I guess that's
not happening!
Did you follow me?
What d'you want?
[LUFFY]
Oh, ya know, nothin.
[LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY]
Oh...Ouch... [laughs]
[USOPP]
I can't believe that butler!
Insulting my old man like that!
[LUFFY]
Yeah, I hate that guy too!
No matter what anyone says,
Yassop was a great pirate.
Yeah! Really!
I've always looked up to my
old man for living everyday
with his life on the line,
out in the open ocean.
He made a brave choice
and I admire him for that!
And then that stupid,
snotty butler
stomped all over my pride.
He's gonna pay for this!
Hey, wait.
Do you know if you're ever
gonna see that girl again?
[USOPP gasps]
I don't know. Eh...
I'll consider it if that
butler apologizes to me
for the things he said.
That butler right there?
Yeah... That's the one, if he--
What in the world is
he doing down here?!
[LUFFY]
What's the big idea?
Hey, Jango.
I specifically ordered you to
keep yourself inconspicuous.
That doesn't mean
sleeping in the road.
Relax man, I've perfected
the skills of the chameleon.
I blend in.
[LUFFY] There's someone else
with him and, man, is he weird!
I've never seen him before.
Who is he?
So, have all the necessary
preparations been made?
But of course.
[JANGO]
We can start anytime...
...on the "Rich
Girl Murder Plan!"
[LUFFY, USOPP gasp]
[USOPP]
Ah! Murder?
[KLAHADORE]
Don't call it murder, Jango.
I don't like the sound of it.
[JANGO]
Oh right, accident.
It's an accident...
that you planned.
Uh, what are those
guys talking about?
Just be quiet.
Maybe if we listen a little
closer, we can find out.
[KLAHADORE]
We can't simply kill her.
It is critical to our plan
that Miss Kaya perishes in
an unfortunate accident.
So don't screw that up!
So basically, on your signal,
the men and I storm the village
and manage to "accidentally"
kill the little rich girl.
Then you get her inheritance
and we all get paid, right?
You moron!
Your ignorance is astounding!
We're not related, so how could
I inherit anything from her?
[JANGO]
You'll work very hard to!
[KLAHADORE]
No Jango, I won't.
Now listen to me, this is
the most important part.
Before you kill her,
you'll use your hypnosis to
make Kaya write her will.
And it will say,
"I leave my entire fortune
to my butler, Klahadore".
[USOPP gasps]
Then, and only then,
will I have undisputed control
of her enormous fortune.
And no one will suspect a thing.
[USOPP whimpers]
[KLAHADORE]
I have spent three long years
gaining the trust of
everyone around me
so that it would be
unsurprising for her
to leave the entirety of
her inheritance to me.
[JANGO] Three years as
a butler for this, huh?
You sure had us scared
back then, Captain Kuro.
Three years ago,
you suddenly said you were
giving up life as a pirate.
In no time at all you set up
someone to be your double.
Then you let the world see
Captain Kuro get executed.
Only now, do I understand
that was just the
beginning of this plan.
You are the "Man of
a Thousand Plans."
Never call me that again.
I abandoned that name years ago.
I now wish to obtain my wealth
without attracting the
attention of the government.
In other words,
I'm a pacifist.
[laughing] Some
pacifist you are!
Murdering an entire family
doesn't exactly
qualify as peaceful.
Hold on, I haven't
murdered an entire family.
The father's death
wasn't planned.
[JANGO] Whatever you say,
it makes no difference to me.
If it's all the same to you,
hurry up and give the word.
The crew is getting bored.
We've been waiting in the waters
near here for over a week,
and the men are growing
more anxious by the minute.
[USOPP] This is horrible!
This is really horrible!
[USOPP grunting]
What are they talking about?
Is it bad guy stuff?
What? Weren't you
listening to any of that?
Those guys aren't
just bad, they're evil!
Captain Kuro is known
to be the most devious,
scheming pirate around!
And though he's
known for his smarts,
he's legendary for
his brutality.
Word had it that
the Marines caught
and executed him
three years ago,
but Captain Kuro
is alive and well,
posing as Klahadore the butler!
And he's had his diabolical
sights set on Kaya's fortune
for the last three years!
[LUFFY]
Hmm...
[VILLAGERS screaming]
[USOPP] First, they'll
attack the village,
then they'll kill Kaya!
[KAYA whimpers]
[KAYA screams]
[USOPP] This is bad!
This is seriously bad!
[USOPP crying]
Hey, get down! They'll see you!
Hey, bad guys! You better
stay away from that girl!
[USOPP groans]
[JANGO]
Who are you?!
You idiot, they've spotted you!
Come on! Hurry up and hide
before they decide you
need a long slow death!
Well now, If it isn't Usopp,
the mischievous town liar.
[screams] Oh, no!
I'm spotted too!
[KURO]
Did you...
...hear anything?
Uh, Nope. Nothing at all.
I don't know what you mean.
We didn't hear a peep.
We just got here,
so we didn't hear
anything about anything!
We heard it all!
Shut up!
[KURO chuckles]
[JANGO]
Well, If you say so.
Pay attention, boys!
And watch this ring closely.
[LUFFY]
Hm? Okay.
Don't you get it? It's some
kind of weapon, we gotta run!
[JANGO] By the count of "Jango,"
you will be in a deep sleep.
Are you ready?
--One... Two...
--[USOPP] Run for cover!
He's gonna kill us!
[JANGO]
Jango!
--[USOPP whimpers] Heh?
--[LUFFY snores]
--[JANGO snoring]
--Jango, you idiot!
I see your still falling
asleep on the job!
--[LUFFY snoring]
--[USOPP] Hey be careful!
You're gonna fall!
[USOPP whimpers]
He had to go and fall
off a cliff, didn't he?
A pity really, I didn't
mean to kill him,
but there's no way
he could've survived.
[USOPP]
This can't be happening!
They killed him!
He's really... dead!
[JANGO]
What about the other one?
Shall I take care of him?
There's no need.
Everything he could say
would sound like, lies.
[USOPP gasps]
[KURO] Jango,
tomorrow at daybreak,
the men are to
attack the village.
Rough up the villagers some
and tear up their homes
a little, for good measure.
And above all, make sure Miss
Kaya's death looks accidental.
Tomorrow...
Just accept it Usopp. There
is nothing you can say or do
to warn the villagers of
this impending tragedy.
[USOPP gasps, screams]
[JANGO]
Are you sure about that one?
[KURO] Of course I am,
my plans are flawless.
[USOPP]
I can't believe this!
This is terrible!
I gotta do something!
Everyone in the village I
grew up with is in danger,
and Kaya's gonna be killed!
[USOPP] I can't let that
happen to the people I love!
[KAYA]
Who are you?
[USOPP] I'm Usopp,
brave warrior of the sea!
[USOPP laughs] I heard you've
been a little down lately,
so I thought I'd tell you
a story to cheer you up!
[KAYA] You would do well
to mind your own business!
Please leave or I'll call
someone who will make you leave!
[KAYA laughs] And then?
What happened after that?
[USOPP]
I fought of course!
And bravely at that!
First, for the giant cat,
I used what else but
a giant cattail plant!
[USOPP, KAYA laughing]
[USOPP panting]
[USOPP]
No!
[KURO laughs]
As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...
[ZORO] Usopp ran by
looking pretty upset.
I wonder what happened?
[LUFFY]
That butler is a pirate!
He told his crew to
attack the village!
[NAMI] Well, now they'll
know and they can run away!
Crisis averted right?
[LUFFY]
Oh, no!
[ZORO]
What is it!
[LUFFY]
We need to stock up on food
before the meat shop
guy runs away!
[ZORO] That's not the
issue at hand here!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
"Expose the Plot!
Pirate Butler Captain Kuro!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!