[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever dared
to imagine! This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!
[KURO] To think that these
brats have held you back.
How the Black Cat
Pirates have fallen.
[BUTCHIE, SIAM]
You're not our Captain anymore,
so we have to kill you!
Zoro!
Ha. I appreciate it.
Tiger Trap!
--[snoring]
--Get up, you bum!
Nami, that's my eye!
[growling]
[KAYA]
Klahadore!
Stop it! Just leave!
Run away, Kaya!
Kaya, listen to me.
I was devoted to you.
For so very long.
I endured it.
I quietly suffered so that
today I could end your life
and take everything
that I deserve.
[USOPP]
Kuro!
[LUFFY] If he hates
getting hit that much,
he's about to have
a really bad day!
[LUFFY]
"Beat Kuro!
Usopp the Man's
Tearful Resolve!"
[PIRATES yelping]
[PIRATE A]
What was that?!
[PIRATE B]
It's sorcery!
[PIRATE C]
Uh! He's a freak!
[PIRATE D]
A magical freak!
[PIRATE E]
He sent Captain Kuro flying!
I'll just leave this to you.
[groans]
I've got treasure to find.
[KIDS]
The Usopp Pirates!
Have arrived!
No! Don't!
Stay away!
[PEPPER]
Say your prayers, butler!
[CARROT]
Take that! And that!
[ONION] Game over,
you lousy, no good pirate!
No! Stop it!
Uh! Those kids!
What're they doin'?!
Those rug rats
have a death wish.
You don't know what
you're doing! Stop!
Stop!
[PEPPER]
All right!
This time, we'll let you off
without any more brutality!
This time.
[whimpers]
Now those stupid kids
have really done it.
Captain Kuro is gonna be so mad.
Those dummy brats!
[CARROT]
Captain!
I knew it. You were fighting!
Gosh that is so totally awesome!
I thought there were no
secrets between us pirates.
Why didn't you tell us?
That right! We're supposed to
tell each other everything!
Who cares about that?!
Look, this is important!
You guys gotta get
outta here! Run!
No way!
We have to stay
and fight with you!
The Usopp Pirates will be
shamed if we run in fear!
[ALL wheezing]
[KIDS screaming]
[USOPP]
You idiots! Don't scream, run!
--[thud]
--[KAYA gasps]
[USOPP groaning]
[KIDS]
Captain!
[KURO]
That hurt.
Hmm. My, my.
That's quite a strange technique
you've developed there.
Tell me something.
Do you have powers from
eating the Devil Fruit?
[chuckles] Yep.
I'm a rubber man.
[PIRATES whimpering, yelping]
[PIRATE D]
Ah! He ate the Devil Fruit!
[PIRATE E]
That guy's dangerous!
[PIRATE F] Those Devil
Fruit people are real!
[PIRATE G]
He's got rubber arms of death!
It all makes perfect sense now.
I didn't just hallucinate his
arms stretching out like that.
[KURO]
Jango!
Uh! Sir!
I can handle the boy.
You take care of Miss
Kaya like we planned.
Have her write her
butler into her will.
Then kill her.
As for the kids,
they're an eyesore.
Eliminate them.
I'm on it.
[ZORO]
Stop right there.
If you wanna get to them,
you'll have to make
it through me first.
[JANGO]
Butchie!
[growling]
[BUTCHIE]
Cat-tastrophe!
Not again.
[PIRATES yelping]
That guy.
He's crazy.
Oh no, Kaya.
Kaya!
[USOPP]
No. Stay away from her.
No. Don't...
No. No!
Usopp Pirates!
[KIDS]
Yes, sir!
[USOPP]
I need you to listen carefully!
Look. We're not running!
Not after they did this to you!
[ONION]
We will avenge you!
Protect... Kaya!
[USOPP] Do as I say.
Don't argue with me.
I'm giving you the
most important task
there is right now.
It's absolutely critical
that you succeed.
Take Kaya, and get
away from here.
You must keep her safe.
This is the reason we
wanted to be pirates.
To protect what's dear to us!
So do as I say...
...and run!
Usopp...
Now go. That's a direct order.
[ALL]
Yes! Captain!
[CARROT]
Kaya, hurry!
[ONION]
This way!
[PEPPER]
C'mon, let's go!
[ZORO] He's sure got
a way with words.
He made running
away sound brave.
[CARROT] I know these woods
like the back of my hand.
[KAYA]
Okay.
Jango.
Yeah! Sorry, I was gawking.
Those fools. Do they really
think that they can escape me?
--[thud]
--[JANGO grunts]
[JANGO screams]
[chuckles] Gotcha.
[JANGO growls] Damn you!
He's not a priority right now!
Yes, sir!
[KURO] Their attempt
at escape is futile.
We know all too well
how weak Kaya is.
There is no way they can
possibly escape Jango.
Now, i you want to
help her, go ahead.
But first, you'll have to get
off this hill alive. Usopp.
[KURO]
Butchie!
[BOTH grunting]
[ZORO] I guess losing to me once
wasn't enough for you, huh?
I told you to get outta my way,
you drooling tub of lard!
Now move!
[BUTCHIE yelling]
[bang]
Wait... What was that sound?
[KURO] That is the
sound of destruction.
Jango's probably tearing
the place apart.
Go ahead. See for yourself
if you can get up.
Heartless bastard! Don't you
even have a shred of pity?
You lived with that
girl for three years!
[KURO]
No. I've told you,
Kaya is nothing more than a pawn
in the game I intend to win.
When she's dead, then
I'll be grateful to her.
[USOPP]
Damn you!
[ZORO]
This guy is hopelessly evil.
[LUFFY] We should put
him out of his misery.
Hey!
Usopp! Go find the others!
Don't worry, we'll
take care of this guy.
Go on.
[USOPP groaning]
[KURO]
Ah.
Very impressive.
You can still move.
[USOPP]
Shut up!
You won't get away with this!
I won't let you!
You betrayed the villager's
trust. Not to mention
you planned to take the life
of a sweet young girl!
This is the last time
you ever get your way!
[USOPP groaning]
Usopp!
It hurts... It hurts
so bad, I can't move.
[laughing]
[KURO]
You really are a riot.
So I betrayed them, you say.
Oh, please! Grow up!
That was all part of the plan.
A village liar who plays
pirates with the local kids
has no place talking
like a real pirate!
Just stay on the ground there.
[JANGO] Hah. Even if you
did somehow catch up to Jango,
he'd end your life
in the blink of an eye.
Staying there is
what's best for you.
[JANGO laughs]
[USOPP]
I don't care.
I don't care that I'm weak.
I'll protect them.
I'm Captain of
the Usopp Pirates.
A brave warrior of the sea who
fights for what he holds dear!
I will protect everyone in
the village if it kills me!
On my word, you will never
set foot in that village!
[PIRATE H]
What's his deal?
[PIRATE I]
He's yellin' about something!
[PIRATE J]
Check it out he's crying!
[PIRATES laughing]
[PIRATES yelping]
What's so funny?!
[ZORO]
Luffy!
Me and Usopp are gonna
chase down that hypno freak.
Is that a problem?
[LUFFY]
No. Hurry!
Hey. Thank you.
I'd be a whole lot faster
if I was going by myself.
But I don't know those woods,
so if we're gonna catch up to
them, I'm gonna need your help.
Hold it you two. Where
do you think you're going?
Who gave you permission
to go anywhere?
[LUFFY]
I did!
Usopp! Zoro! Get goin'!
[LUFFY]
Have another!
Gum-Gum!
Spear!
[LUFFY]
Man, he disappeared again!
The others got away.
That's the most
important thing, really.
[KURO] Before I kill you,
I feel compelled to ask.
What is an outsider like you
butting into this
villages' business for?
[chuckles] Because there's
a man in this village
that I don't wanna let die.
[chuckles] Simple enough.
Are you okay with that
being the reason that you die?
Sure am.
Ha! But I'm not gonna die!
We'll see about that.
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum Whip!
And Pistol!
This is quite boring!
You cocky jerk!
[LUFFY]
Owww.
He nicked me.
Kuro laid him out flat.
Lotta good that
Devil Fruit did him.
Yeah. That's Captain
Kuro for ya.
[PIRATES cheering]
Shut up. Don't call me that!
[PIRATES]
Huh?
[KURO]
You still don't get it.
You fools. This whole
plan was devised,
so that I may be rid of that
name once and for all.
I'm tired of it.
Concocting plans everyday
for a bunch of barbarians
who care only about
havoc and mayhem.
Relentlessly attacked
by government dogs
and bounty hunters.
I'm tired of it.
I am sick and tired
of that entire cursed life!
[explosion]
[KURO]
The Navy, huh?
This is the third
time this week.
Well, can you really blame them?
You're one of the
most famous pirates
sailing the seas right now.
Captain Kuro is a superstar.
[KURO]
You're right.
My infamy is what
draws them to us.
That's why I'm going to
give up being Captain Kuro.
[explosion]
Yeah, wouldn't that be nice.
Except... the Marines
won't stop their pursuit
until Captain Kuro is dead.
[explosion]
[KURO]
I am going to die.
It would seem that the
tumultuous life of a pirate
just isn't for me.
[JANGO]
You can't quit, sir.
You're the ship's captain.
[KURO]
You can be captain now.
I have finally grown
weary of this life.
It's over. I'm killing
myself for all to see.
Sir! Captain Kuro!
Captain!
[KURO]
How many vessels are there?
One! Just one this time.
What should we do, Captain?!
Should we man the cannons?!
We could blast
them to splinters!
[KURO] Lower a small
boat into the water.
[PIRATE S]
What?!
[KURO]
A boat! Now!
[PIRATE S]
Vice Captain Jango!
Captain Kuro just--!
[JANGO]
Yeah, I know.
[PIRATE O]
"Yeah, I know"?
It's too dangerous for him
to go there by himself!
[PIRATE S] Don't tell me
he's turning himself in.
[PIRATES whimpering]
[PIRATE R]
What?!
[PIRATE G]
The cannon fire stopped.
[PIRATE H]
What's goin' on?
[PIRATE I]
This is weird.
[JANGO]
Prepare to board the ship.
[PIRATE T]
But... sir! Shouldn't we--?
I didn't ask for your
opinion. That's an order.
[PIRATE T]
Yes, sir!
[PIRATE R]
Better get ready...
[JANGO] I see.
So that's why you--
--[PIRATE H] On three!
--[PIRATES yell]
You there! Hey!
Uh, Yes, sir! What is it, sir?
Good bye. It was nice
knowing you, sailor.
[PIRATE T]
The Marines.
[PIRATE V]
They've been wiped out.
[KURO]
Now then.
Let's begin this plan.
C'mon, pull yourself together.
I was kind enough to let
you and you alone survive.
Just... do it.
I'm not kneeling to you
Finish me off and
get it over with.
--[thud]
--[MORGAN groans]
You'll be perfect.
If you can still howl this
much with a shattered jaw,
you should do fine.
[chuckles]
Today is the greatest
day of your life.
Today is the day you
captured Captain Kuro.
You should be ever
so grateful to me.
I'm giving you, the
head of Captain Kuro.
[JANGO]
Your name is Captain Kuro.
This atrocity was your doing.
One. Two. Jango!
My name is Captain Kuro.
This atrocity was my doing.
[JANGO]
And you are the brave Marine
who caught the
infamous Captain Kuro.
Return to base and see
that he gets executed.
One. Two.
Jango!
I am the brave Marine who caught
the infamous Captain Kuro!
[PIRATE W] You're doing
it again, Vice Captain.
[KURO]
Perfect.
When my double gets executed,
Captain Kuro will
disappear from the earth
and I will live
the life I deserve.
[KURO]
And when my plan succeeds today,
after three years of planning,
revising, and waiting;
my goal will be achieved
in its entirety.
Wealth and peace of mind
will finally be mine.
Do you understand now, boy?
I will not allow
this perfect plan,
years in the making, to fail!
My plan will not be disrupted
by an urchin like you!
It would seem that you can do
a lot more than just stretch.
[LUFFY]
That's right!
I've been toughening
myself up to be a pirate!
You know what?
Don't want a reputation?
Then don't be a pirate!
[chuckles]
You're just greedy, Kuro.
But I have ambition!
As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...
[NAMI]
I'm worried guys.
Do you think Kaya and
the others got away?
[ZORO]
Relax. Those three are with her,
she should be fine.
[NAMI]
Oh, yeah? So she won't get lost
like someone else I know.
[LUFFY]
Are you talking about me?
[ZORO]
Who else is there?
[LUFFY]
Can it, jerks!
Zoro, you're one to talk!
How much time did you spend lost
while you were bounty hunting?
[ZORO]
Oh yeah, right.
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Protect Kaya!
The Usopp Pirates'
Great Efforts!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!