[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit of
dreams greater than they've
ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!
[seagulls squawking]
--[wings flapping]
--[squawking continues]
--[thud]
--[SAILOR gasps]
[LUFFY]
"I'm Luffy!
The Man Who's Gonna Be
King of the Pirates!"
[orchestra playing]
Of course not. My ship
is much too sturdy and
too heavy to be affected by
such a measly whirlpool.
[MAN A]
Excuse me?
Would the beautiful
lady care to dance?
[GIRL]
[SAILOR B grunts]
--Ugh. I missed again.
--[SAILOR A laughs]
Strike three, pal.
[SAILOR C]
I'd be embarrassed.
You suck!
[SAILOR B grunts] It's heavier
than I thought it'd be!
Maybe it's filled with beer!
[SAILOR A grunts]
Well, I think it's our beer now.
And I'm not sharing
my half. [laughs]
[whimpers]
Ship off the starboard bow!
[SAILORS gasp]
[SAILOR C] And they're
flying a pirate flag!
We've got a pirate
ship in pursuit!
--Enemy raid! Enemy raid!
--[SAILORS scream]
[cannon fire]
[PEOPLE screaming]
[whimpers]
Captain, we've got pirates!
[CAPTAIN]
What?!
--[CAPTAIN screams]
--[PEOPLE screaming]
People! Please stay calm!
Panicking will
only get you hurt!
Just follow my
crew's instructions
in an orderly fashion!
[explosion]
[ALVIDA]
Fire!
Coby!
Yes, ma'am?
[ALVIDA] Who is the most
beautiful of all on these seas?
Well, uh... That would be,
the captain of our ship,
--Lady Alvida, of course.
--[ALVIDA laughs]
[ALVIDA laughing]
Good answer.
That means a lot to me.
It's been a while...
We're finally gonna
see a little action.
That's right!
So make it count!
Hit 'em with all
--you got, boys!
--[PIRATES yell]
[PEOPLE scream]
[GIRL panting]
[gasps]
[GIRL screams]
[PIRATES grunt]
Here we go!
Time to show them the
terror of Iron Club Alvida,
lady pirate of the seas!
[PIRATES yelling]
[whimpering]
Coby! What are you doing?!
I'm not... real good
at this stuff.
[scoffs] You're telling me.
Maybe it's 'cause
you're too busy
backtalking me all the time.
Oh, no! Not the club!
Anything but the club!
Please!
Then get your ass in gear!
[screams]
[COBY sobs]
--[ALVIDA] Move it, you brat!
--[gasps]
[ALVIDA yells]
[screams]
[ALVIDA groans]
[PIRATES laughing]
We're not gonna take
your lives, we swear...
But we will take everything
else you got on you.
[ALVIDA] And anyone who fights
back'll be eating their dinner
off the bottom of the ocean.
[PIRATES laughing]
[COBY]
Uh, hello...?
[COBY] I really hope
there's no one in here.
[sighs] That's a relief...
Huh?
[COBY]
Wow, that's one big barrel.
I wonder what's inside of it.
[GIRL grunts, pants]
--[PIRATE L growls]
--[GIRL gasps]
[PIRATE L]
Huh? Who are you?
--I ain't seen you before!
--[GIRL laughs nervously]
--[GIRL grunts]
--[PIRATE L screams]
[whimpers]
[giggles]
[COBY groaning]
It's our favorite coward.
You trying to hide in here and
duck out on all
the action again?
No way!
I was just trying to haul
this big barrel of beer
over to you guys!
[laughs]
Why don't you let us
lighten your load?
I was just startin'
to get thirsy.
You can't!
Lady Alvida will kill us
if she ever found out!
She won't if you
keep your trap shut.
Right?
Boy?
Yeah... Right.
[laughs nervously] Okay.
This sucker's heavy.
Hah, perfect.
Hold on, boys...
I'll open her the
old fashioned way.
[PIRATE B growls]
[growling continues]
[PRATE B yells]
[LUFFY yells]
[ALL scream]
[LUFFY]
I...
slept...
so...
great...!
Hm?
Who's that?
Who the hell are you guys?
[PIRATES]
Who the hell are you?!
Your friend'll catch
colds sleeping like that.
[PIRATES] You're the one
who knocked him out!
[LUFFY]
Hm?
Hold up!
Are you messing with us
when you know good and well
that we're vicious
pirates?! Huh?!
--[gasping]
--[LUFFY] I'm starving.
You got any food?
I'm talking to you!
[growls] You damn kid!
--[PIRATES yell]
--[COBY screams]
[LUFFY]
Hm?
[PIRATES growl]
Die!
[COBY whimpers]
--[metal clinks]
--[PIRATES gasp]
[COBY whimpers, gasps]
[PIRATES gasping]
What is wrong with you two?
[PIRATE C]
Wh-Who are you?!
[LUFFY]
Me? Oh...
My name's Monkey D. Luffy.
Hi! [laughs]
[PIRATES scream]
So... What just happened?
You got me.
[gasps] Quick!
You've got to run!
If those guys come back
here with their buddies,
then they'll kill
you on the spot!
I don't care about that.
I'm hungry.
How can you just blow
this off like that?!
There are hundreds
of them up on deck
and they're waiting for the
opportunity to kill anything!
--[LUFFY grunting]
--[COBY groans]
[COBY mumbles]
You're going the wrong way!
No!
--Wait!
--[LUFFY growls]
[screams]
[laughs]
It's a goldmine!
Food! Food! Food! Food! Food!
--[LUFFY laughing]
--[COBY] Who's knows...
Maybe we'll be safe in here as
long as no one else gets hungry.
[LUFFY]
...box looks promising!
Apples! Excellent! [laughs]
Heh, tasty!
[COBY]
Uh... Hey! My name's Coby!
You're Luffy, is that right?
That was pretty neat when you
jumped out of that
barrel back there.
These are awesome!
[LUFFY] So are we on
a pirate ship or what?
[COBY]
No...
It's a passenger ship that's
being raided by pirates,
pirates under the
command of Lady Alvida.
[LUFFY]
Aw, who cares anyway?
What I wanna know is if
there are any boats on board.
[COBY]
I think there are a few.
[LUFFY] Great, 'cause mine got
sucked into some big whirlpool.
[COBY]
That one outside? No way!
No one could have survived that.
[laughs] Yeah! I gotta say,
it was a big surprise!
[laughs nervously]
[LUFFY]
So are you one of the pirates
or one of the passangers?
[gasps]
[COBY] It was on a
fateful day, long ago...
That day...
I stepped out onto
a small fishing boat
on the outskirts of town
to go catch my dinner.
[gasps]
[COBY whimpers]
[COBY]
Turned out that particular boat
was actually headed
for a pirate ship.
That was two years ago.
[COBY] In exchange for
them letting me live,
I'm forced to live the
life of a cabin boy.
You're pretty stupid,
you know that?
[COBY]
Gee, thanks for your honesty.
If you hate it, then leave.
Are you kidding?!
I can't do that!
No way! Nuh-huh! Not a chance!
Just the thought of
Alvida finding me
scares me so bad,
I wanna throw up.
[laughing] You're a
moron and a coward!
I hate people like you!
--[LUFFY laughs]
--[COBY sobs]
[ALVIDA] All right, quit your
lollygagging around, boys!
We gotta load up everything
before the Marines get here.
I catch anyone dawdling,
and they'll get a real
mouthful of my iron club!
[PIRATE I]
I love hitting a rich ship.
[PIRATE J]
Let's get back to it!
She'll break our asses
if she catches us slacking off.
[PIRATE H]
One hit from that club of hers
is enough to have you
beggin' for death! [laughs]
[PIRATES screaming]
[BOTH]
Captain!
[ALVIDA growls]
[BOTH]
This is bad!
[ALVIDA]
Yeah...? Then out with it!
[PIRATE M]
It came from inside the barrel!
[PIRATE C]
Such a horrible monster!
[ALVIDA growls]
Huh?
[PIRATES whimper]
[ALVIDA grunts]
Who are you...
--[PIRATES scream]
--[PIRATE B groans]
[ALVIDA]
...calling a monster?!
[PIRATE B screams]
[PIRATES scream]
Uh... we weren't... talkin'...
'bout... you, my lady.
Some guy was hiding in a barrel!
He could be a bounty hunter!
What?!
Yeah, you're right.
If I had the courage,
I could drift alone in a barrel
and be rid of these pirates.
I actually have my own dreams.
Some day... I'd like to
live out all of them.
So... What about you, Luffy?
What was it that first got you
to set sail on these seas?
[LUFFY]
Hm?
Well, I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!
[gasps]
--The King?!
--Yep.
--Are you serious?
--Yeah.
But... But that would mean
that you're a pirate, too!
Right.
Your crew?
Don't have one yet,
but I'm lookin' for 'em.
[COBY gasps]
[yelps] King of the Pirates
is a title given to one who
obtains everything this
world has to offer.
You're talking about seeking
the great treasure of
wealth, fame, and power.
The treasure that you
seek is the One Piece!
Yeah!
Yeah?! That's it?!
Pirates from all over the world
are looking for that
treasure, ya know?!
Yeah? So?
No way! It's impossible,
impossible, impossible!
There's no way anyone like you
could ever reach the pinnacle
during this great pirate age!
There's just too many out there
that are meaner and better!
[COBY yelps]
[COBY]
Ow... Why did you hit me?
'Cause I felt like it.
[COBY groans]
Oh, well... I'm used
to that stuff...
My shipmates smack
me around a lot...
...all the time, in fact.
It's not about if I can.
[COBY]
Huh?
I'm doing this 'cause I want to.
I decided long ago that I'm
gonna be King of the Pirates.
If I have to die fighting
for that... then I die.
[COBY gasps]
All right...
Now that my belly's full,
I'm gonna go get me
a brand new boat.
They might even just give me
one if I ask nice enough.
Maybe they're generous people.
I guess I never
thought of it like that.
[COBY]
If I put my mind to it,
if I'm prepared to die for it,
could I do something like that?
Like what?
[COBY]
Do you think...
Do you think I could
ever join the Marines?
[LUFFY]
Marines?
Yes! Catching bad guys is
the only thing I've
ever wanted to do!
It's been my dream
since I was a child!
Do you think I can do it?
How should I know that?
[COBY]
Then I'm gonna do it!
I'm not gonna get stuck here
as a cabin boy for
the rest of my life!
I'll break out,
then I'll turn right around,
and catch Alvida myself!
[screams]
[ALVIDA] Who is that you
plan on catching, Coby?
And you actually think
this twig is gonna help you?
Well?
--[COBY whimpering]
--[ALVIDA] Answer me!
[ALVIDA growls]
[COBY whimpers]
[ALVIDA chuckles]
My guess is that you're
not Zoro, the pirate hunter.
[COBY gasps]
Zoro?
--[ALVIDA] Coby!
--[screams]
[ALVIDA] Who is most beautiful
of all on these seas?
[COBY]
Well... I... Um...
Give me a sec... I know this...
Hey, Coby, who's the fat lady?
[PIRATES whimpering]
Oh, no...
Not good...
[ALVIDA growls]
You...
...runt!
[COBY whimpers]
--Let's go.
--[gasps]
[ALVIDA growls]
[screams]
[PIRATES gasp]
[LUFFY grunts]
[laughs]
[PIRATE A growls]
--[PIRATE A yells]
--[PIRATE A groans]
[PIRATE N yells]
[COBY screams]
[PIRATES yell]
Missed me!
[LUFFY grunts]
[COBY gasping]
[LUFFY laughs]
[screams]
[PIRATE S yells]
[LUFFY] It's not fair
to attack from behind.
[PIRATE S screams]
[PIRATES scream, groan]
[PIRATES growling]
--[PIRATES yelling]
--[LUFFY screams] And it's even
--more not fair to gang
--[PIRATES yelling]
--up on a guy!
[LUFFY yelling]
[PIRATES gasping]
[PIRATES scream]
Gotcha!
[PIRATE screaming]
[LUFFY]
Gum...
...Gum...
[PIRATES screaming]
[ALVIDA growls]
[LUFFY]
...Rocket!
[PIRATES scream]
[gasps]
--[PIRATES groaning]
--[footseps]
[COBY]
Luffy...
What are you?
Oh...
I'm a rubber man.
So you're... made of rubber...?
I... [gasps]
[COBY screams]
So... You've eaten
of the Devil Fruits.
Yeah. I ate the Gum-Gum one.
Ah-ha...
I heard rumors they existed,
but I'd never seen any
evidence of them before today.
You're more skilled than
the average deck swabber.
Are you a bounty hunter?
[LUFFY]
I'm a pirate!
[ALVIDA]
Pirate? Ha!
All by yourself
on these waters?
[LUFFY]
Today, it's just me.
But I'll find my crew tomorrow
or next week or something.
I need... I dunno,
like ten guys. Yeah, ten.
[ALVIDA]
Hah!
Tell me...
If we're both pirates,
and we're not
under the same flag,
then that would make us enemies.
Am I right?
Uh, Luffy?
--Let's go.
--But why?
You saw how powerful
her club is.
And of all the villainous
cheats in all these waters,
she's easily the most--
I decided long ago
that I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates.
If I have to die
fighting for that...
...then I die.
[COBY gasps]
Go on...
Tell me...
[COBY whimpers]
You're the most...
...ugliest thing on the sea!
[ALVIDA growls]
[whimpering]
[laughs]
What'd you say?!
--[laughing]
--[COBY] I'm leaving and
I'm gonna join the Marines!
Then I'm gonna spend
the rest of my life
beating up dirty
pirates like you!
Do you have any clue what
you're saying to me right now?!
[COBY]
Of course I do!
And I'm gonna do what I want,
and no one's gonna stop me!
And when I join the Marines,
I'm gonna join them!
And I'm gonna catch
your lousy ass first!
You're dead, kid!
[ALVIDA yells]
[COBY]
No regrets! No regrets!
I did it! I said what I wanted
to and fought for my dream!
Well said! [laughs]
[yells]
[COBY gasps]
[LUFFY]
Heh. That won't work.
What?!
[LUFFY]
I'm rubber!
[LUFFY growls, grunts]
[LUFFY]
Gum...
...Gum...
[grunts]
...Pistol!
[ALVIDA screams]
[PIRATE B] The sky's so
pretty and blue out here.
[PIRATE B]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Hey, you!
[PIRATES]
Yes?
Go find a boat and
give it to Coby.
He's leaving your ship
to join the Marines;
you're not gonna don't stop him.
[PIRATES]
Uh... Yeah, sure!
[COBY gasps]
Thanks, Luffy.
[BOTH scream]
[BOTH gasp]
[COBY]
Look! It's the Marines!
[LUFFY]
Ooh!
Perfect timing!
Head over there and
tell 'em you wanna join.
--[COBY] Huh?
--But I'm a pirate,
so I'm outta here!
No, wait! You can't be serious!
I approach them like this,
they'll just capture me
like another pirate!
[GIRL screams]
[GIRL groans]
[GIRL gasps]
[COBY]
We actually managed to get away!
[sighs]
What fun! [laughs]
So, Luffy.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
If you're searching for
the elusive One Piece,
then you have to be headed
for the Grand Line, right?
You know, the people
I've talked to
call that place the
pirate graveyard.
Right. And that's why I need
an extra-strong crew.
You guys mentioned
some pirate hunter.
So what's he like, Coby?
Oh, you mean Zoro?
Last I heard was that
he's being held prisoner
at some Marine base.
Oh, well...
A weakling, huh?
No, you're so wrong!
He's as violent as a demon,
and three times as horrifying!
Why are you asking
about him anyway?
I figure if he's good enough,
I'd ask him to join my crew!
[COBY gasps]
[COBY] Chasing him down
is just plain reckless!
[LUFFY]
You never know!
He might jump at the
chance to join me!
[COBY] He's a bad enough guy
that the Marines caught him!
No way! Not a chance!
Forget it! No no--
--[thud]
--Ow!
Why'd you hit me?
[LUFFY]
'Cause I felt like it.
As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...
[LUFFY]
Tell you what.
I untie your ropes,
you join up with me.
I refuse to team
up with a pirate!
[LUFFY]
Come on!
Everybody already thinks of
you as an evil bounty hunter.
[ZORO]
Screw that!
I've never done anything
I regret and I never will!
So I'm not gonna be a pirate!
[LUFFY] I already decided
that you're joining me.
[ZORO] Would you stop
making decisions for me?!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
"Enter the Great Swordsman!
Pirate Hunter Roronoa Zoro!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!