[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever dared
to imagine! This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!
[KRIEG growls]
[KRIEG]
You're just like a little bug!
[LUFFY yelping]
[KRIEG yells]
Chore Boy!
[LUFFY groaning]
[LUFFY grunts]
No, you're wrong.
Even with a hundred
thousand more weapons,
our chore boy can still
bring him to his knees...
... because he
does not know fear.
[KRIEG, LUFFY yell]
When he's fighting...
he's not afraid of anything.
Not even death!
Is it just instinct,
or all a plan?
We'll know soon, if he lives.
[SANJI gasps]
[SANJI]
What plan? Killing himself?
[KRIEG]
Today is your funeral!
I am invincible!
[KRIEG]
Huh?! What? my Battle Spear!
What the hell did you do?
I just punched it in
the head five times.
It looks tired,
maybe it needs a rest.
[growling]
Chore Boy's pretty good, huh?
He might be able to pull it off.
This is terrible!
He just shattered the
Mighty Battle Spear!
[SANJI grunting]
It's a miracle he's still alive
after that many explosions.
There's no way he can hold up!
[LUFFY] "The Conclusion
of the Deadly Battle!
A Spear of Blind Determination!"
[LUFFY]
Heh!
You ready for this?
[KRIEG]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
Because that was all I needed.
Now that your little toy's
broken, you're nothing to me.
[KRIEG grunts]
Oh yeah?
[LUFFY]
Yeah.
Without the blade,
it's just a bomb on a
stick and let's face it,
that's pretty lame.
[KRIEG]
You think so?
[LUFFY]
Sure do!
[KRIEG] Heh. Fine, so what if
it is just a bomb on a stick?
You're in sad shape, kiddo.
I think it'll be more than
enough to blow you to pieces.
Ya know, it sounds to me
like this is some sort of
pathetic attempt at a bluff.
Okay, but you're wrong.
Just give up.
Your defeat is imminent.
You see, when you defied me...
You signed your
own death warrant!
Nuh-uh!
[KRIEG yells]
[LUFFY, KRIEG grunt]
[LUFFY]
Hey! Up here!
Bastard.
You monkey!
[LUFFY gibbers]
Bounce outta that!
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY yells]
Nice try!
How many weapons
does that guy have?
[chuckles]
Now, Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
[LUFFY yelling]
[PIRATES gasp]
What's that kid doin'?
It's like there's
arms everywhere!
All right, Chore Boy!
Yeah, get him!
[LUFFY yelling]
[KRIEG laugning]
[KRIEG]
Weakling!
What exactly did you
expect to happen, Boy?
I'm wearing Wootz
Steel Body Armor.
This stuff is practically
indestructible!
[LUFFY inhales]
[LUFFY yells]
We'll see about that!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
[LUFFY, KRIEG grunting]
[KRIEG groaning]
[PIRATES]
Don!
[grunting]
[KRIEG]
How dare you!
[LUFFY yells]
[LUFFY grunts]
[chuckles]
It's useless.
You'll never defeat me!
This armor could take a million
more of your monkey punches
and it wouldn't have
so much as a dent!
[LUFFY grunts]
Well, we'll just see about that.
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
He's gone!
[KRIEG]
I'm right here!
[LUFFY gasps]
[KRIEG]
You don't stand a chance, Boy!
Real power comes
from deadly weapons.
They're the source
of true strength!
See, only the strong
are meant to live.
And that's me!
[LUFFY grunting]
Yeah? That's what you think!
Gum-Gum...
Heh. It's useless!
Foolish pride will
only get you so far!
... Bazooka!
[grunting]
[laughing] That's it?
After all that big talk,
that's all you've got? Ha, ha!
[KRIEG]
Huh? No!
I don't believe it,
my armor's cracking!
[grunting]
[KRIEG]
Heh! Doesn't matter.
You're done for, chore boy!
It's a trap! Get out!
Chore Boy!
[COOKS screaming]
[PIRATES screaming]
[ZEFF]
He's not afraid of anything.
Not even death.
Is it just instinct,
or all a plan?
[ZEFF laughs]
We'll know soon, if he lives.
[LUFFY]
Gum-Gum...
What the...
[yelling]
[LUFFY]
...Bazooka!
[KRIEG yells]
[KRIEG grunting]
[LUFFY grunting]
[KRIEG groans]
[KRIEG yells]
[PIRATES shout]
[COOKS cheer]
--[COOK A] All right!
--[COOK L] Way to go chore boy!
[KRIEG groaning]
I totally win!
[KREIG]
This isn't over yet, Boy!
Whoah, he's alive!
[LUFFY grunts]
[LUFFY]
Oh, no!
[LUFFY grunting]
[KREIG laughing]
You can't escape!
It's a steel net!
[laughs]
[LUFFY grunting]
[SANJI gasps]
[KRIEG laughs]
It's over! That's the ocean
down there below us!
It looks like I'll be getting
the last laugh after all,
Chore Boy!
--[PIRATES cheering]
--[PIRATE E] Take him down Don!
[PIRATE F]
Make that little brat pay!
[PIRATE G]
Yeah, get him!
[LUFFY grunts]
Now, I got that jerk
right where I want him!
[SANJI]
He hasn't even flinched.
How can he stay so calm?
[yells]
[LUFFY] Time for me
to end this, right now!
[KRIEG yelping]
Now, Gum-Gum...
[screaming]
[yelling]
... Giant Hammer!
[screaming]
[yelling]
... Giant Hammer!
[KRIEG grunts]
[groaning]
[chcukles]
[PIRATES gasp]
[COOKS gasp]
[gasps]
--[COOKS cheer]
--[PIRATE CC] No!
Don Krieg was defeated!
[PIRATE J]
How could this have happened?!
[COOK L]
You're awesome, Chore Boy!
[COOK M]
Yeah, you kicked his ass!
--[CARNE laughs]
--He won! He really won!
Oh, wow!
I gotta be dreamin'!
That's Don Krieg
we're talking about!
[PATTY] I know! Who'd a thought
that kid had it in 'im?
[PATTY laughs]
[GHIN] What is it?
What's going on?
Hey! Rise and shine!
Krieg was beaten!
Betcha you never thought
you'd see the day!
What?!
[SANJI gasps]
Are you done daydreaming, yet?
Go on, save that kid!
[SANJI]
Huh?
[ZEFF]
He can't swim!
What?
[ZEFF] Those with the
power of the Devil Fruit
are hated by the sea, so they
lose their ability to swim.
What're you sayin'?
He'll just sink?!
You could've told
me that sooner,
you worthless old geezer!
What if it's already too late?!
[ZEFF]
Heh...
[SANJI]
Where is he?
[coughs]
[SANJI]
Hey! Hang in there!
You said you wouldn't die.
You truly believe that, right?
Well?!
[LUFFY] You'll have to
do better than that...
... if you want to beat me.
Because, I don't think it's
time for me to die just yet.
[SANJI]
These guys...
Zoro!
[SANJI] How this fight would
end was clear from the start.
Why choose death?
Don't be stupid! Give up
your ambition and live!
[SANJI]
They're all...
[ZORO] I don't know...
but, I will not run.
Even if I retreat a single step,
I would be shattering
the promises I've made.
I can't run.
I would lose my honor.
You see, without that,
there would be nothing
left for me, here.
[ZEFF] Even with a hundred
thousand more weapons,
our chore boy can still
bring him to his knees,
because he does not know fear.
Krieg may have more
pirates at his command,
he may have terrible weapons
that cause mass destruction
to everything in his path,
but he will never
have that kid's heart.
[SANJI gasps]
[SANJI]
The All Blue...
[SANJI] Hey, Chore Boy,
don't you die on me!
[GHIN gasping]
--[PIRATES whimper]
--[PIRATE G] Don! Are you okay?!
[PIRATE H]
Please, tell us it's an act!
[GHIN]
Don Krieg has been defeated.
This can't be happening.
He's the mighty rule
of the East Blue.
It can't be...
It's impossible...
Impossible!
He's just too strong!
[PATTY] Yeah? Well, now
he's down for the count!
Have a look at him
and see for yourself!
[CARNE] That fancy armor
of his got all busted up,
and he was out as soon
as he hit the deck!
What? Do you think
we're lying to ya'?
Go ahead and look!
[GHIN gasping]
He was the only man
I ever really admired.
How foolish, now he's lost.
[GHIN coughs]
[groans]
[PATTY]
Hey! Hold on!
If you move now,
the poison'll set in!
[CARNE] Be still!
It's for your own good!
[SANJI]
Chore Boy!
Chore Boy, can you hear me?!
Don't die!
You still have a lot of
things to do with your life!
Get up, right now!
Please, please!
Just open your eyes!
Please, don't die!
[LUFFY snoring]
[gasps]
[snoring]
Are you kidding?
You really are something else.
[KRIEG]
No! I'm the strongest!
I win! I'm the greatest!
I'm the best!
No one defeats me!
No! Just stay down!
Stop him! He's not
even conscious!
[KRIEG yelling]
--[PIRATE J] Please Don, stop!
--[PIRATES yell]
I have to win! I have to!
[PIRATES shout]
--[KRIEG yells]
--[PIRATES scream]
[KRIEG howling]
Kill!
Enemy!
[KRIEG yells]
I'll fight until
victory is mine!
[KRIEG groans]
[PIRATES gasp]
[GHIN]
Don Krieg...
We lost.
[PIRATES]
Commander?
[GHIN] Let's leave now, while we
still have a shred of dignity.
Thanks for everything, Sanji.
[SANJI] Sure, now leave
and don't ever come back.
[GHIN]
Hey, Sanji.
You don't owe me any favors,
but when the kid wakes up...
[LUFFY snoring]
[GHIN] Tell him I said I'll
see him on the Grand Line.
[SANJI]
But, you...
That's where I wanna go
with the time I have left.
It's the only
thing I care about.
The only thing that
keeps me going.
Heh. It would seem that
Don Krieg's obsession
with the Grand Line, has
become mine as well.
[coughing]
It's silly...
I know that.
But, It's my dream.
With this poison in my veins,
I may only have a
few hours to live.
But, I feel free somehow,
like now I can live those last
few moments on my own terms.
[snoring]
[PATTY,CARNE panting]
[GHIN] To hell with
loyalty to Don Krieg.
My devotion to him
was just an escape from
forging my own destiny.
Once you heart is set,
and you pursue all your dreams
with every last fiber
of what you are,
you will never again feel lost,
or hopeless, or afraid.
I learned all that fro
a brave chore boy.
Hey, you guys!
Give him the boat we use
to go grocery shopping!
C'mon! Are you
stupid or somethin'?!
Why do we have to give
a perfectly good boat
to a bunch of pirates?
And what's gonna happen to all
our grocery shopping, Jackass?
Patty's right. Let 'em swim
wherever they're goin' to!
Go get that grocery boat, now!
[PATTY, CARNE sob]
All right, fine.
Stop shouting.
[PATTY, CARNE]
Okay, okay, we'll go get it!
--[PIRATES yelling, grumbling]
--[PIRATE J] It's gonna sink!
[GHIN]
Why did I hesitate?
What was I so worried about?
When I think about it,
I can't help but feel stupid.
--[LUFFY snoring]
--[GHIN, SANJI] Huh?
[snoring continues]
[GHIN]
Hm.
[SANJI]
Heh.
[GHIN]
Well then.
We gratefully accept this boat.
Am I right to assume there's
no need to return it?
[SANJI]
It's yours.
Don't ever come back here.
Not for anything.
Not even to return this boat.
[PATTY]
He's right!
And don't you ever forget,
this is the restaurant
where the cooks fight!
The Baratie!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[GHIN] Heh. The cooks
there sure mean business.
[snoring]
They sure were nice guys.
But, I wonder...
Well...
I wonder if they would
let me join them again?
[NAMI sobbing]
I hope I see them.
Free. I just wanna be free.
Bellemere...
As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...
[LUFFY]
I guess I can leave now,
since me and pops
made that deal.
[SANJI]
That's right!
[LUFFY]
So, you wanna--
[SANJI] I'm not gonna run
away to become a pirate!
[LUFFY]
Well, okay.
[SANJI]
Haven't you given up yet?
I mean, I am hoping to go
to the Grand Line someday.
[LUFFY]
Then, let's go now!
[SANJI]
It's not the right time, yet!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
"Set sail!
The Seafaring Cook
Sets off With Luffy!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!