[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit of
dreams greater than they've
ever dared to imagine!
This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!
[GHIN] I'll spare him,
but you have to leave.
Please, don't make this any
harder, Sanji. Just leave.
Not a chance.
[PEARL]
Pearl... Cymbals!
[groans]
[PEARL]
Surprise!
[SANJI] There's no way to repay
the old geezer for his kindness,
unless I risk my life for him!
I've already taken everything
else that man holds dear.
His power...
His dreams...
[SANJI] He gave up his leg
so that I could live!
[grunting]
[SANJI ] This restaurant
is that old man's life!
So, while I'm around,
I'm not gonna let anything
else get taken from him!
[LUFFY growls]
Now, Gum-Gum!
No! Don't!
Ghin'll shoot the old man!
Battle-Axe!
[LUFFY] "Cool-headed,
Cold-hearted, Demon!
Pirate Fleet Chief
Commander, Ghin!"
[ZEFF]
Hm...
[PIRATE A]
He destroyed the fin!
[PIRATES]
Whoa!
[KRIEG]
He's trying to sink my ship.
You dare defy me!
Ghin, blow his
head off right now!
[grunts]
[KRIEG]
What are you waiting for?
But... he...
He saved our lives
when we were starving.
He gave us food!
[growling]
Ghin, kill him!
[LUFFY]
Hey!
I don't see why
you're all so upset.
I didn't sink it.
[grumbling]
Back off, Chore Boy.
It's not your fight!
[LUFFY]
But, I will.
What?!
I'm going to sink it.
[COOKS]
Huh?
[PIRATE groan]
Aw, Cmon!
[PIRATES yelling]
[SANJI] You bastard,
that's what you're doing?
You can't sink this ship!
But, if the restaurant's gone,
there's no reason to
attack then, is there?
[SANJI]
No!
[ZEFF]
Hm.Hm.
This ship saved my life.
I owe everything to her and
you will not take that away!
You're gonna die for a
dumb, old restaurant?
Are you stupid?
What'd you say?!
Getting killed?
That's how you wanna
repay your debt?
The old man didn't save you so
that you could kill yourself!
He did it so you could do
something with your life!
Not to die like a fool!
And so your big idea is
to help them attack us?
[BOTH growling]
[GHIN grunting]
[PEARL] Boys, there's no
need for friends to fight.
Especially when there's
nothing either of you can do.
Not while there's a big shotgun
pressed right up against
the old man's chef hat!
Your problem began
when you decided
to come up against
the Krieg Pirates.
Nothing can stop us.
[laughing]
[PEARL]
FIRE PEARLS!
Now, you will burn!
[PEARL laughing]
[PEARL wheezing]
[LUFFY gasps]
Ghin!
[groaning]
What did... you do... Ghin?
I'm sorry, Pearl.
You're in my way.
Ghin, you have betrayed
your captain and your ship!
[GHIN]
I know.
I'm sorry, Don Krieg,
but he saved our lives.
I can't kill him.
Not like this.
He deserves better.
He deserves to face
death standing up.
But I promise you...
...he'll still
die by my hand.
[SANJI grunts]
Oh, great...
My Chief Commander has now
completely lost his marbles.
You just hang in
there, Old Zeff.
[CARNE]
A-Are you alright, Boss?
He's their chief commander?
I guess...
Did ya' see him crush
that guy, though?
One blow and his
shield was in pieces.
Now, that's power!
[LUFFY]
Hmm.
Ha! My plan worked perfectly!
And now, he's out in the open.
You liar!
There's no way you thought
that this would happen!
[LUFFY]
Uh...
[GHIN]
Sanji.
Look, I'm just following orders.
I don't want to ruin this ship,
but I think it's
too late for that.
[SANJI] Ha. Maybe.
But, if you think that
you're going to get to this
restaurant without killing me,
you got another thing coming.
Sounds fair.
Then it will be an absolute
pleasure to kill you...
...my good friend.
Gee... that's comforting...
Asshole.
[GHIN]
You as well, Chore Boy.
[LUFFY]
Gee... thanks!
But, I'm not afraid
of any Krieg pirate.
[GHIN grunts]
[PIRATES grumble]
[PIRATE B]
Ya' little twerp!
[PIRATE C] Get ready
to die, little man!
I'm gonna stuff that
stupid straw hat
right down your throat!
[PIRATE D]
We're the Krieg Pirates!
Rulers of the East Blue.
Only 'cause you outnumbered the
other pirates in the East Blue.
[PIRATES growling]
Oh, boy... now you
really pissed 'em off.
Guess I was right.
[PIRATE]
You're dead meat!
Let's get him!
Hold your place!
[PIRATE E]
But, Don Krieg!
[PIRATE F]
He can't say that.
[KRIEG]
You only prove his point
when you lose control or
whine like little babies!
You see me trembling with anger?
Only the weak react
to mere words.
Don Krieg Pirates
run from no man!
[PIRATES]
Yes, sir!
[KREIG]
Ghin!
[GHIN]
Hm?
[KRIEG] It's your job to
take care of that cook!
I'll handle the little boy.
That brat is all mine.
I understand.
Yes, Don Krieg.
[KRIEG]
Hey, Boy!
[LUFFY]
Hm?
You can try your Devil
Fruit magic against me,
but I've seen it all before
and have never been
defeated by such trickery.
When you experience
the full force
that conquered the
entire East Blue,
then you'll understand the
meaning of power, Chore Boy!
Your voice is getting
on my nerves.
I'm gonna to kick your ass!
It's as simple as that.
[grunts]
Hold on just a second.
I'll be right there.
[KRIEG growls]
The impudence!
[PIRATE G]
That cook is done for  now.
[PIRATE H] Yeah man, when
Ghin takes out his weapons,
he's through screwing
around. Just look at him.
[PIRATE I] They call him,
"The Cold-Hearted Demon."
[PIRATE J K] He's our
cool-headed, cold-hearted,
pirate fleet chief
commander, Ghin!
It doesn't matter if
you beg for mercy,
he'll still laugh in your
face while he kills you.
[GHIN] I'm sorry, Sanji,
but I can't be defeated.
Yeah, go ahead...
tell yourself that.
[SANJI gasps]
[GHIN]
Here I come.
--[GHIN grunts]
--[SANJI grunts]
[GHIN]
Ha!
[GHIN grunts]
--[SANJI grunts]
--[GHIN chuckles]
[SANJI grunting]
[SANJI]
You son of a--
[GHIN]
Ha. Ha.
[SANJI gulps, grunts]
Sanji!
[SANJI grunting]
[GHIN]
I warned you,
but you just wouldn't listen,
would you?
[SANJI huffs]
[GHIN]
Heh. And now...
[SANJI gasps]
...it's time for you
to accept defeat.
[PIRATES cheering]
[COOK WALLA gasping]
Die!
[GHIN grunts]
[GHIN growling]
[GHIN yells]
[SANJI grunts]
[SANJI groans]
[BOTH grunt]
[CREWS chattering]
[PIRATE L] That cook...
kicked Ghin in the head!
[PIRATE M]
Yeah, I couldn't believe it.
Do you think he's still alive?
[KRIEG]
Enough!
After all this time,
you should know a hell of a lot
better than that, you idiots.
There's a reason I trust him
above any of my
other pirate crew.
Ghin is always a cool-headed,
cold-hearted Demon
and he never quits!
[GHIN grunts]
[SANJI groaning]
I can't believe
Sanji is getting up!
He should lie back down.
After what he's been through,
his ribs must be
completely smashed!
Well... that... wasn't...
too bad... Chief Commander.
[SANJI] Lemme know when
you're ready to really fight.
[GHIN]
Hm?
Hmph.
[gasps]
[LUFFY]
He's just sitting there.
[laughs]
Now, it's ass kickin' time!
[KRIEG]
Hm?
[LUFFY yelling]
Don't hurt yourself.
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[LUFFY yells]
[LUFFY gasps, screams]
[LUFFY grunts]
[laughing]
You're a bastard!
Don't you want to fight me?
Fight you?
Do I really have to?
If all I want to do is kill
you, that's enough for me.
I really don't have any patience
for your stupid games,
little fool.
Oh, yeah?
How about I bite your head off!
--[thudding]
--[PIRATES laughs]
[laughing]
[PIRATES cheering]
[LUFFY gasps]
Sanji!
[coughing]
Pfft.
[PIRATE N]
Woo hoo!
Pulverize the rest of him!
[PIRATE O]
Yeah, what he said!
Crap! If only he hadn't
fought that Pearl guy first!
Yeah, I don't think
he'll survive another hit
from those balls.
[SANJI grunting]
[SANJI] Go ahead... you
hit like a girl, anyway.
[GHIN chuckles]
[SANJI grunting]
[SANJI]
He's too strong for me.
Now, die!
Bye, Sanji.
[GHIN yells]
[SANJI, GHIN grunting]
What was that? Your pity?
[GHIN]
Huh?
--[GHIN yells]
--[SANJI] I'm not dead yet.
[PIRATE P]
Chief Commander!
--[bones cracking]
--[SANJI groaning]
Oh, no!
[SANJI grunting]
Ah! No!
He can't take it!
He's gonna kill himself
just trying to fight!
[SANJI gasping]
[GHIN grunting]
--[bones crackling]
--[SANJNI groaning]
[KREIG chuckles]
[PIRATES chattering]
[SANJI]
You damn bastard.
[SANJI grunts]
[LUFFY gasps]
[PATTY, CARNE gasp]
[whimpers]
[GHIN]
I can't...
I can't obey your order.
[whimpering continues]
[GHIN]
This man saved my life.
I can't, Don Krieg!
I won't do it!
[SANJI gasps]
Woah.
I can't!
I'm sorry, Captain.
What did you say?!
I won't... do...
what... you want!
[GHIN]
Take it and leave me alone!
I won't accept charity,
it doesn't matter how
down and out I may be,
just take this stuff away, now!
Stop your whining
and eat it already.
I don't care what
they say in there.
To me, if anyone's hungry,
they're a customer.
[GHIN] Sorry, but I'm
not your customer.
[SANJI] You can die for
your pride, if you want.
But listen, if you
and eat and survive,
won't that give you the
opportunity to fight for pride
truly worth having,
now and in the future?
[GHIN gasps]
[GHIN]
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry... thank you, so much.
I thought it was over, I truly
thought I was going to die.
[GHIN sobs]
[GHIN]
This food... it's delicious.
I've never eaten food
this good before.
Of course it is.
[sobbing contiues]
Sorry. You'll probably
get yelled at, or fired
'cause you gave me
that food for free.
Now there's not proof,
so there's no way for
me to get yelled at.
[GHIN whimpers]
[GHIN] He treated me
with such respect,
and decency, and kindness.
That's why... I can't
bring myself to kill him.
Don't get caught again.
[GHIN]
I've always been loyal to you.
Up till now, I've believed
in what we've done.
I respect you and appreciate
all you have given me.
Trusting me as your
Chief Commander
was the honor of my life.
Until this moment,
I have obeyed every single
order you have given me
without ever questioning it.
I can't live with myself
if I kill this man...
...and I cannot break my oath.
Please, I beg you.
Let me disobey
just this one order!
Please!
[GHIN]
Don Krieg...
Listen...
Can't we just leave?
They can keep the
restaurant for themselves.
[Yelling] You little
son of a bitch!
You think you can defy my orders
and then tell me what to do?
[KRIEG]
It's pathetic.
Morality, sympathy...
Weaknesses I never
expected to see from you.
You are not my Chief
Commander anymore!
Pirates?
Step aside.
No! Not the gas!
[PIRATES yelling]
[PIRATE Q]
He's going to use the MH5!
[PIRATE R]
We're all gonna die!
--What?!
--Poison gas!
[PIRATE S yelling]
Where's my mask?!
[PIRATE T]
Masks on!
[PIRATE U]
Move it, move it!
[PIRATE V]
He's using MH5!
[PIRATE A]
Gas is a coward's weapon!
[PIRATE B]
You bastard, you'll kill us all!
The only thing that
matters in a battle
is who ends up winning,
even if more have got to die.
Poison gas is just
a means to an end.
Victory is all that decides
what's right and what's wrong.
If you are dead, nobody's
gonna hear you complain anyway.
When you don't hesitate
to do unspeakable,
horrible things...
that, is true power.
[LUFFY growls]
He's insane.
[GHIN grunts]
Might as well throw
that gas mask away!
You're no longer worthy
to be a Krieg Pirate.
Die!
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY] I'm not going to let
that happen, you bastard!
You're wasting your
time, Chore Boy!
[LUFFY yelping]
[LUFFY gasps]
[LUFFY yelling]
[LUFFY grunting]
[LUFFY]
Aw, crap!
Ghin!
You don't have to
listen to that blowhard,
because I'm gonna kick his ass!
[GHIN growls]
No! My captain
cannot be defeated!
Don Krieg is the
strongest man alive
and I respect his punishment.
Will you please snap out of it?
He's going to kill you!
I deserve it.
Obeying my emotions meant
betraying my captain.
If I were in his position, then
I would've done the same thing.
And now, death is the
only honor I have left.
Don't!
[SANJI]
Why? No...
Heh. So, you've
remembered your place.
But, it's much
too late for that.
Now, you will both die together.
It's the MH5
Poison...
Gas Bomb...
Fire!
[PIRATES chattering]
[COOK Z]
Dive! Dive!
[PATTY]
Get inside the restaurant!
--[LUFFY] Thank you!
--[PIRATES gasp]
Sanji, Ghin, catch!
Now, for mine.
Ah! Where'd they go?
[yelling]
As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...
[LUFFY] I'll show you
whose grave this is!
Your weapons can't stop me!
[SANJI]
How come you don't flinch?
[LUFFY]
What are you, stupid?
[SANJI]
Say that again, I dare you!
[LUFFY]
What are you, stupid?
[SANJI]
Shut up!
[LUFFY]
Told me to say it again!
On the next One Piece,
"I Won't Die! Fierce
Battle, Luffy vs. Krieg."
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!