[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit of
dreams greater than they've
ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!
[NAMI]
What the hell is that?
[explosion]
[ZORO]
Hm?
[LUFFY]
That was way off the mark!
Hey, What's so loud down there?
Cannon firing practice!
[LUFFY] Awesome! You hit
that thing on the first try!
Whatcha think?
I'm pretty awesome
when it comes to aiming!
Are you impressed yet?!
[LUFFY]
Yeah! You better believe it!
So it's all settled.
[JOHNNY] Get out here,
ya damn pirates!
[ZORO]
Mm? That voice...
Hey, what the hell?
Who are you?
And now you guys think that
you can kill my partner?!
[LUFFY screams]
Just stop wrecking our ship!
[JOHNNY screams]
[JOHNNY groaning]
[JOHNNY]
Lost by a hair.
[LUFFY] "Famous cook!
Sanji of the Sea Restaurant!"
So, dearest... 'Fess up.
Where are you taking me?
Darling. This place is
great, trust me, 'kay?
[WOMAN]
So mysterious.
Well, it's not a restaurant in
the middle of the ocean, is it?
[FULLBODY chuckles]
Here's to your beauty.
[FULLBODY] Just wait
until you see this place.
[ZORO]
Hm?
What are you doin'
here, Johnny?!
[JOHNNY]
Huh?
[JOHNNY grunting]
What?! Big Bro?! It's you!
[LUFFY grunts]
Hm?
[JOHNNY]
Why are you on a pirate ship?!
What's goin'
on around here?!
Hey relax! Is everything
okay? Where's Yosaku?
[JOHNNY]
Well...
[inaudible]
Hey, Look. Zoro
knows that guy.
What's going on here?
[cries] He's been sick.
[ZORO]
What is it?
[YOSAKU panting]
[JOHNNY]
Up until a few days ago,
he was healthy
and full of life.
And now...
He keeps fainting!
And getting really pale!
I have no idea
what's causing it!
[JOHNNY] His teeth
have been falling out,
and his old wound opened
up and started bleeding!
He just got worse and worse! I
didn't know what to do!
So I thought...
Maybe we'd just rest on a
little island. But, then...
[JOHNNY] A cannonball came
flying from this ship!
[LUFFY, USOPP whimpering]
[LUFFY, USOPP]
We're very sorry!
[JOHNNY]
Sorry isn't good enough.
[LUFFY, USOPP gasping]
[YOSAKU panting]
[JOHNNY]
Isn't that right...
partner!
[JOHNNY] Big Bro. Give it to
me straight. Is he gonna die?!
[ZORO gasps]
[NAMI]
So dumb.
Watch it!
Stop it! Whatever
you're doing, stop!
You're mocking his death!
Dammit! You'll--
[NAMI] Luffy! Usopp! We have
some limes in storage.
What're you doing?!
Bring them here! Now.
[USOPP, LUFFY gasp]
[USOPP, LUFFY arguing]
He's got scurvy.
[JOHNNY]
Scurvy?
[NAMI]
Mm-hm. If we weren't too late,
he'll be just fine
in a few days.
[JOHNNY gasps]
Really, Big Sis?! Really?!
Thank you, Big Sis!
Please. Don't call me that.
It sounds so dumb.
Besides, I'm not a magician.
This used to be a hopeless
disease that plagued sailors,
and we just know how
to deal with it now.
--[LUFFY] Here,
--[USOPP] There you go,
--drink up sick guy.
--have some more.
[NAMI] This is caused
by a simple deficiency
of plant-derived
nutrients like Vitamin C.
Back in the old days,
they couldn't carry fresh
fruits and vegetables
because they couldn't store
them. We know better now.
[LUFFY] If a little is
good, a lot is gooder.
[USOPP]
You're gonna be just fine.
[LUFFY]
You're smart!
You're like... a doctor!
Well, now. How 'bout that.
--I was right. She isn't dumb.
--[YOSAKU groaning]
[LUFFY]
Nope. She's smart as a tack!
You guys, are morons. Every
sailor should know about scurvy!
[YOSAKU coughs]
[USOPP, LUFFY]
Huh?
[YOSAKU grunts]
[NAMI gasps]
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU]
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
[YOSAKU]
The nutrients cured me!
[JOHNNY]
Now you're all better!
You can't heal
that quickly!
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU]
Allow us to introduce ourselves!
My name is Johnny.
And I'm Yosaku.
Together, we're the baddest
pirate bounty hunting
duo in the world.
[JOHNNY] Big Bro Zoro
there used to be one of us.
[YOSAKU] Glad to make
your acquaintance.
Small world. I never thought
I'd see you guys again.
[JOHNNY] Well if you think
you're surprised...
[YOSAKU] We never imagined
that the pirate hunter Zoro
became a pirate himself.
[ZORO]
Tell me about it.
[JOHNNY]
Big Bro.
[YOSAKU]
Ah!
[YOSAKU groaning]
[ZORO]
Huh?
Uh... Hey... Partner?!
[YOSAKU groaning]
[NAMI]
Let this be a lesson to you.
[ZORO] Yeah. This is the
kind of trouble you run into
when you choose a
life on the sea.
[USOPP] Which means,
when we're at sea,
we really gotta think
about how we can get
the right amount of nutrients
with very little food.
It's absolutely necessary
that someone on this ship
knows how to do that.
[LUFFY]
It's necessary?
Right! The ship needs a cook!
[NAMI, USOPP]
Hm?
[LUFFY]
Let's go find us a cook!
I'm in! Good idea!
We'll have yummy food,
even while we're out at sea!
That's right.
You got it. Ha, ha!
A cook? I know just the place.
And the food is gonna
blow your mind.
All right!
Let's go! Where to?
[JOHNNY]
Consider yourselves warned.
This place is close
to the Grand Line.
And I've heard a lot
of rumors lately,
that a certain hawk-eyed man
you're looking for is there.
Set a course.
North-Northeast!
[NAMI]
Yes!
[USOPP]
Awesome!
[ZORO grunts]
[LUFFY chuckles]
[JOHNNY]
Our destination is...
...the sea restaurant...
Baratie!
[LUFFY, NAMI, USOPP]
Ooooh!
So, heh, what do you think?!
[LUFFY]
Wow. It's a big fish!
[NAMI]
How lovely!
[USOPP] This is the
coolest place ever!
[LUFFY, USOPP cheer]
[JOHNNY]
Just like I told ya, right?!
[horn blares, bell rings]
Ah! What the...?!
A Marine ship?!
All the way out here?
Hey, Luffy. They're not gonna
start firing at us, are they?
It's just my luck! Of course
the marines would show up.
But. How did that ship...?
[FULLBODY] I've never
seen that pirate flag.
So, do you think he
knows that you and I
aren't a couple of pirates?
[YOSAKU]
Ah...
[FULLBODY]
I am Iron Fist Fullbody!
But, you can just
call me "Sir"!
You there! Who's the
Captain?! Identify yourself!
My name is Luffy!
My name is Usopp.
Got it?!
We only made our flag
the day before yesterday!
That's right marine!
And I drew it!
Heh. You did?
Is that so...?
Hey! You two! Right there!
I've seen you before.
You're that bounty
hunter duo that goes
after the small fish, right?
Uh, well, we...
[FULLBODY] So, you've finally
been caught by pirates.
Uh. Well... Actually we...
[FULLBODY laughs]
Now that's a laugh.
Hey, c'mon baby,
let's get going.
Sure.
[JOHNNY]
Hey! Wait a minute!
You think small time
bounty hunters
would go after these guys?!
[NAMI]
Huh?
Now. Let's go to
that restaurant.
[FULLBODY]
They're an eyesore. Sink 'em.
[BOTH]
Sir!
[JOHNNY]
He ignored us!
Next time we see him,
he'd better have a little
more respect for us.
[NAMI]
Hm. What are these things?
Well those are all wanted
pirates, Big Sis Nam-- Uh!
[JOHNNY coughs]
In other words, if we defeat
them, we get the reward money.
Pretty lucrative business,
huh, Big Sis--?
[NAMI grunting]
Hey you guys, look! They're
pointing a cannon right at us!
Leave it to me!
Now Gum-Gum...!
[ALL groaning]
[LUFFY]
...Slingshot!
[LUFFY screams]
[LUFFY groaning]
[ZEFF groaning]
[COOK A]
Sir!
[COOK B] Are you all
right, Head Chef Zeff?!
[COOK C]
Sir, are you okay?!
[FULLBODY]
I wonder what that was.
I hope our reservation is okay.
[COOK D] Head Chef are
you sure you're okay?
[ZEFF]
No! Nothing is "okay"!
[COOKS whimper]
[ZEFF] Never mind, just get back
to the restaurant already!
But... but, Sir!
Aren't you, I mean...
[ZEFF] You maggots!
Do you want to see me angry?!
[COOKS whimper]
[ZEFF] Feeding the
customer is a cook's job!
What are you trying to do?
Put me out of business?!
[COOK C]
This is the guy!
[COOK D] He's the one
responsible for this!
[ZEFF]
Hm?
[LUFFY]
Sir, I'm very sorry!
[LUFFY gasps]
[screams] Your leg!
[ZEFF]
Idiot!
[FULLBODY]
Heh.
[ZEFF] Don't worry; you
didn't do this to my leg.
Oh. I see. Good to know.
[LUFFY groans]
But... I'm all banged up...
The medical fees
and repair charges for the
ship are gonna cost you.
[LUFFY grunts]
[ZEFF sighs]
[LUFFY] I won't ask you
to cut me any slack.
Oh?
[LUFFY]
But...
I'm flat broke!
[ZEFF]
Mm.
Well. You're pretty direct, huh?
If you don't have money,
you've no choice but to work.
Fine. I wanna make it right!
Then you'll work, unpaid,
for a whole year.
Right! I'll work,
unpaid, for a year!
[ZEFF] I'll let you off
the hook with that.
Uh! A year?!
Did you just say a year?!
A whole year?!
[USOPP sighs]
What's taking Luffy so long?
[NAMI]
Yeah...
[USOPP] They'll probably
make him work without pay
for like a whole month.
[NAMI] He should've just said
it was the Marine's fault
instead of being so
freakin' honest.
Oh wow. That guy sitting over
there is Lieutenant Fullbody.
Well, what do you know.
Hey, look kids.
A big shot from HQ.
Oh wow... He's so elegant.
You're famous. Everybody
in here is looking at you.
No, you're wrong.
They're all admiring you.
[FULLBODY]
Mm.
So good!
This... flavor...
And yes... the aroma...
It is the unmistakable scent
from the soil of Micquo
of the North Land.
Bitter with plenty of body,
and just a tad sour.
This wine... must be...
the famous Iturutz
Burger Stein.
Tell me waiter,
am I right?!
Uh-uh. Not even close, sir.
[FULLBODY gasps]
Eat up. This dish
is best when hot.
[FULLBODY]
Uh.
And, sir. My name's Sanji,
I'm the Sous Chef.
All the waiters ran
off as of yesterday.
[WOMAN laughs]
[PATRONS laughing]
[MAN A]
You really shouldn't laugh.
[WOMAN A] I can't help it!
He looked so confident!
Do you know a lot?
[FULLBODY gasps]
About wine?
Well, yes... I thought...
But it seems my sense of
taste isn't working today.
[WOMAN laughs]
[FULLBODY] What's going on?!
I'm certain I requested
that the owner serve
that particular wine
when I made this reservation!
And what does that mean?
I can only work... for one week!
Yeah. Right.
A week, get real!
Fine then. Two!
Hey! You wrecked my restaurant
and seriously injured the Head
Chef. That's a serious offense!
You can't just settle that up
with one or two
weeks of unpaid work!
That's ridiculous!
[LUFFY]
You win! Three weeks!
Talk to me...
...with respect!
--[ZEFF yells]
--[LUFFY gasps]
[ZEFF grunts]
[LUFFY]
No deal.
[ZEFF]
Hm?
I waited ten long years
to become a pirate. So...
I'm not gonna
waste another year
stuck in this restaurant!
[ZEFF]
Mm?
'Kay. Listen.
I'm gonna get you to let
me off the hook in a week.
That's my decision!
If you value your
time so much,
I'll tell you what you can do
to settle your debt quickly.
Ya runt!
[LUFFY groans]
It'll cost you... a leg, my boy.
[LUFFY grunts]
That's pricey.
Heh. Good, I got your attention.
[JOHNNY]
Tap, tap... Tap!
[JOHNNY, YOSAKU]
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
[FULLBODY]
Uh!
Waiter! Hey! Get over here!
[SANJI]
Hm.
[SANJI] I believe I've already
told you, I'm not a waiter.
What an irresistible
beauty you are.
My lady.
Would you care to join me
elsewhere for a glass of wine?
[SANJI]
Hm?
Hey! What is this?!
Is "bug soup" on the menu today,
or did you make it just for me?
Bug soup?
That's right. What's this
bug doing there, waiter?
[FULLBODY] This is gonna ruin
their restaurant's reputation.
Sorry, sir. Don't know, really.
Looks like he's floating.
[FULLBODY grunts]
Then again. It kinda
looks like he's drowning.
But it's hard to say for sure.
[WOMAN laughs]
[PATRONS laughing]
[FULLBODY seething]
Don't you mess
with me! Waiter!
[NAMI, ZORO]
Hm?
[USOPP]
Mm?
[SANJI] You could've eaten it if
you had just taken the bug out.
It would've been wonderful.
It took three full
days of hard cooking
to prepare that soup for
you, and you wasted it.
[FULLBODY] Can't you see
that you're biting off
more than you can chew?
I'm the customer here!
Do you understand me?!
I'm paying you!
Stop it! Fullbody!
Shut up!
[WOMAN gasps]
No... Fullbody... No...
Can your money truly
satisfy your hunger?
Whadya mean?
[SANJI] I'm asking...
Can it satisfy your hunger?
[LUFFY groans]
[ZEFF grunts]
[LUFFY]
No!
No! No!
This is getting old.
You're never gonna
make it if you don't
just give in sometimes!
[panting] It's still no!
[growls] No respect!
[PATRONS whimpering]
[WOMAN]
Fullbody?
It-It's Sanji.
What's going on here?
[ZORO]
Hm.
A fight...
[FULLBODY groaning]
Don't ever waste
food around me again.
[FULLBODY choking]
At sea, if you ever
provoke your cook,
you're signing your own
death warrant. Remember that.
[LUFFY groaning]
As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...
[USOPP] I wonder if
Luffy's working hard?
[NAMI] I bet he's just
causing trouble.
[USOPP] Yeah, he doesn't seem
like a productive kinda guy.
[USOPP laughs]
[LUFFY] What'd you say?!
That's not nice!
[ZORO] Hey, have you found
a cook who'll join us yet?
[LUFFY] Yeah! I found him all
right! It has to be him!
On the next One Piece!
"Unwelcome customer!
Sanji's food and Ghin's debt!"
I'm gonna be King
of the Pirates!