[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
[NARRATOR] These words lured men
to the Grand Line in pursuit of
dreams greater than they've
ever dared to imagine!
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!
So this is it...
Will it be the
world's strongest...
...or death?
[ZORO] Three-Sword
Style Secret Technique!
[ZORO]
Now you die!
Three Thousand Worlds!
[ZORO grunts]
[LUFFY]
Zoro!
[LUFFY] "The Deadly Foot
Technique Bursts Forth!
Sanji vs. The Invincible Pearl!"
[KRIEG groans]
[LUFFY]
All right!
[LUFFY laughs]
They wanna fight, too, huh?!
Now this'll be fun!
Okay, Pops!
You promised me, remember?
If I run those pirates off,
then my debt to you is cleared.
No more chores.
That's the deal...
There's no telling how
much more of my restaurant
you could screw up
if you stick around.
[LUFFY laughs]
Yeah!
So, kid, you said you were going
to be King of the Pirates...
Were you serious?
Well, yeah, of course!
I'm definitely going to be
King of the Pirates someday.
Heh, I've seen a whole
lot of pirates in my day.
But you're the first to state
your desire so clearly
and without a doubt.
I heard, that back in the day,
you were a pretty
awesome pirate, yourself.
So did you wanna be
King of the Pirates, too?
[ZEFF]
Hm...
I do my best to forget
about the past.
I'm the owner of Baratie now,
and that's quite enough for me.
[KRIEG]
Men!
If we can capture that ship,
the Grand Line will be
ours for the taking!
No more pretending
to be Marines...
Or raising the white
flag of surrender.
None of our enemies
will suspect that
we're a threat with
a ship like that.
In that boat, it'll
always be a sneak attack.
He's right. That boat
would come in handy.
No one would think that pirates
were on such a
ridiculous-looking ship.
Right, but Don...
Even if we enter the Grand Line
again using that vessel...
What if we come across someone
like Hawk-Eye Mihawk again?!
--Then what'll we do?
--[KRIEG growls]
[PIRATE C groans]
I really appreciate the input,
Sailor, anything else? Huh?!
N-No!
Do you think an
ordinary man could
cut up a sailing
ship like that?!
That man probably has
the power of the Devil Fruit.
Although those with
Devil Fruit powers
are rare and legendary to us...
I assure you they're
commonplace on the Grand Line.
Mihawk must've used some
sort of strange power
when he sliced our
ship to ribbons.
When we're on the Grand Line,
those powers won't be special.
Even the straw hat freak
will be considered normal.
[KRIEG]
That old geezer, Red Foot Zeff,
sailed those seas for a year.
[KRIEG] It stands to reason
that he had strategies
for dealing with
those monsters.
The techniques for surviving
that parade of weirdoes
must be written in the
old man's logbook...
...along with clues
to the One Piece.
I see... You're a genius!
All we have to do is get
that logbook and the ship,
then we'll be able to find our
way to the One Piece again!
[KRIEG]
Ya hear that, boys?!
Now let's get to it!
That restaurant will be ours!
[PIRATE cheer, yell]
You pirate scum are gonna
hafta get through us first!
[CARNE]
We must protect the ship!
No matter what happens!
[PATTY stammering]
How does this thing work?!
Hurry up!
This restaurant...
will be a battlefield.
[ZEFF] Times like these make
you reflect on your life.
I think I was meant
for something else.
I think if I can make
it out of this alive...
I'll build a restaurant
as my final purpose...
A restaurant as
my final purpose...
Go to the control room,
and open up the fins.
What?! No! That's a bad idea!
If we do that, we'll be
giving the enemy a foothold!
And that's just fine.
We gotta do whatever it takes
to keep those guys
out of this place.
If they destroy the inside, then
the old man'll complain forever.
Did you just say
something, you brat?
Yeah... I said you're whiney!
Now go.
Yes, sir!
[PIRATES yelling]
That's right... Bring it on!
I'm comin' for ya!
Gum-Gum... Rocket!
[PIRATES gasp, yell]
He's flying over this way!
[LUFFY]
And Gum-gum...
--...Giant Scythe!
--[PIRATES scream, groan]
[KRIEG growls]
[LUFFY laughs]
Didja see that?! Go, Kid!
[PIRATE C] What's the
heck's up with that guy??!
[PIRATE A]
Yeah! He's crazy!
It's hard to believe...
The Grand Line is crawling
with guys like these?
Sanji...
Pay special attention
to how this one fights.
Don't take your eyes
off him for a moment
until this fight is over.
Is that clear?
So Let me get this straight...
You're attacking the
restaurant that gave you food?
I got no choice but to beat
some manners into you!
[KRIEG laughs]
So you wanna fight on the water
where there's no
place to stand, huh?
A bold move for
someone like you.
The Devil Fruit has taken your
ability to swim, hasn't it...
...Chore Boy!
Yeah, but now... I'm stretchy!
[COOKS gasp, cheer]
Sanji... Here come the fins!
[KRIEG]
Huh?
[LUFFY]
What's up?
[LUFFY chuckles]
[KRIEG growls]
[PIRATES scream]
[PIRATE H]
What is this?!
[PIRATE I] Now we have
somewhere to fight 'em!
Whoa! That's so cool!
My cooks and I will never give
up defending this place...
Prepare to die.
I see...
Good plan, bringing up all
that extra decking, genius.
Now we don't have to
take the fight inside.
I'd hate to damage
my future ship...
And make no mistake,
it will be mine!
[COOK I] We will never let
you have the restaurant!
[PATTY]
That's right! We mean business!
[CARNE]
We're battle cooks now!
Set sail, Mackerel Head One,
the Baratie's secret weapon!
So If you wanna live,
I'd suggest running away now!
[KRIEG]
What is that thing?
That thing is so... cool!
[PATTY]
Paddle faster!
[CARNE]
You paddle faster!
[PATTY]
Fire!
[PIRATES scream]
[LUFFY screams] Those guys
are gonna sink me, too!
Yeah! Get 'em!
Yeah!
[COOK Z] Get 'em guys! Get 'em!
Blow 'em away! You can do it!
Nice!
[PATTY laughs]
Keep your eyes on
the prize, Patty!
This one counts!
[PATTY]
Right! Krieg! Say your prayers!
Little did you know that
the Sea Restaurant Baratie
had such a powerful weapon
just waiting to be unleashed!
[PATTY, CARNE gasp]
[PATTY] What happened?!
Did we bump into something?
[CARNE]
We're not moving!
I am Don Krieg...
...the man who will
rule... the oceans!
Oh no, you're not... I am!
I don't have time for
these stupid games!
Get outta here!
[growls]
[PATTY, CARNE shudder]
No way! He's so strong!
[KRIEG growling]
[KRIEG yells]
[COOK D]
It's coming straight for us!
The restaurant...! Oh no!
[PIRATES gasp]
[LUFFY gasps]
[COOKS]
Sanji!
[KRIEG gasps]
No way!
He's got legs of steel!
He kicked back that crazy boat
just like it was nothing!
Very impressive.
Sanji, good job!
Nice kick!
What's the deal?!
Are you trying to
crush your friends?!
[SANJI]
Yeah, yeah.
Don't "yeah, yeah" us,
You crazy fool!
Stop acting so cool!
You wouldn't be so smug
if we'd been killed,
you bucket of backwash!
[PIRATE F]
All right, ladies,
you think you could wrap
this up another time?
We have business to attend to.
[PATTY, CARNE growl]
Get them!
[PIRATES, COOKS grunting]
[PIRATE J]
You guys still don't get it.
Even well armed,
you're still just cooks,
and we're expert fighters that
are way out of your league.
So why don't you be
good little cooks,
and run along to
a safer restaurant?
Maybe one on land, huh?
C'mon, guys, why are you lettin'
'em beat you up so easily, huh?
And you still call
yourselves fighting cooks?!
Well, these pirates
are really good!
They're totally different from
the ones we've fought before!
[PIRATE J]
It's insulting to lump us in
with that average riffraff...
We are the great Krieg Pirates!
And we're the absolute
rulers of the East Blue!
Let it be known to all...
...that this garish
boat already belongs...
...to the great and
powerful Krieg Pirates!
I'm afraid you're mistaken...
You and your cronies will never
set foot in our restaurant.
[ZEFF]
He's right, men!
[PATTY] You know what,
I've been a cook all my life!
I've worked at a
lot of restaurants,
and gotten fired from them all
for scuffling and livin' hard!
And after years of wandering,
we finally found a home here!
[PATTY]
Anybody here!
This is the restaurant that's
owned by a guy name
Red Foot Zeff, right?!
Hey! We found this "Damn Cooks
Wanted" sign, is it true?!
[ZEFF]
Yeah... It's true.
But you need to understand
that this is no
ordinary restaurant.
It really doesn't matter
who they are...
...or where they come from...
...if someone comes in hungry...
...we will feed them
until they're stuffed!
Do I make myself clear?!
Can you handle that?
[BOTH]
Sir!
I wouldn't serve
anyone slop like this!
Hey! What'd you go
and hit me for, huh?!
Share victory! Share defeat!
We like fighting and cooking,
so this place is perfect for us.
That's right! There's
no other place like this!
You hear that? Now that's
true fighting spirit!
[PATTY] Committing ourselves
to cooking fine cuisine
day in and day out
is a fierce battle...
Compared to that,
these pirates are nothing!
He's right. Yeah.
Let's fight!
--[COOKS] Yeah!
--[PATTY] Protect Zeff!
Protect the restaurant!
[PIRATES scream]
[PIRATES, COOKS grunting]
[PATTY screams]
[PATTY grunts]
Huh? The hell was that?!
[CARNE groans]
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[PEARL sighs]
[PEARL] Just what do you
guys think you're doing?
Who's that? Huh.
[PEARL laughs]
So... let's do this...
But... before we begin...
It's only fair I
give you a warning.
I am Pearl,
the Invincible Shield.
Hey, it's Pearl!
Patty! Carne! Are you boys okay?
I'd say that pair
is far from okay.
Those two just experienced
my Pearl Surprise,
one of my signature punches,
you bumbling, pathetic idiot!
[PIRATE L laughs]
Hey! Look at that...
Nice knife...
I think I'll take it.
Wha? Give it here...
C'mon, let it go!
I said, give it to me!
Huh?
[SANJI yells]
[PIRATES groan]
[PIRATES groan, grunt]
That guy knows how to
kick some serious butt.
I knew there was a reason
I liked him so much
right off the bat.
A kitchen knife
is a cook's soul!
How dare you filthy pirates
try to desecrate one
with your grubby little hands!
Sanji...
Just stay down
and hang on to this.
[PATTY grunts]
I'm gonna teach
these bozos a lesson.
--[PIRATES yelling]
--You must be out of your mind
if you think we're gonna
be beaten by a mere cook!
[PIRATES groan]
I'll show you "mere cook" after
I fillet every one
of you bastards.
Hah! How very imputative of you
to defeat them all
using only your kicks.
Am I to be impressed by that?
I'm a cook, remember?
I couldn't do my job very well
if I ruined my hands in battle.
So I'll be taking you
down with my feet.
Is that so? I think not.
I'm invincible, you see.
I've won all 61 of
my battles completely
and totally unscathed.
It's quite remarkable, really.
No one has ever shed a single
drop of my blood in battle.
No one.
Now do you realize my power?!
I may be a gentleman,
but I'm not gentle...
Got it?
Was that supposed to be a joke?
'Cause it wasn't even
a little bit funny.
Dropping your guard is a good
way to end up dead, you brat!
[LUFFY screams]
[LUFFY grunts]
[PEARL] Even battleship
cannons don't work on me.
I come out of any
attack unharmed!
[SANJI gasps]
[LUFFY grunts]
Boy, that could've
been really bad.
Good thing I didn't
fall into the ocean...
[LUFFY gasps]
[PEARL]
H-Huh?
[KRIEG growls]
This isn't good...
Blood?! No!
Hey, Pearl, don't worry!
It's only a nosebleed, Pearl!
Look, we know it's
not a battle wound!
[PIRATE P]
So just keep calm, okay?!
What's this?
These people aren't just
mean; they're dangerous!
So... Uh.. Wanna tell me
why everyone's freakin' out?
They're worried
about a nosebleed?
[PEARL gasping]
Calm down!
It's just a nosebleed!
Don't lose your cool! Relax!
[PEARL screaming]
[SANJI]
Geez... What is that guy doing?!
Danger...! Danger...! Danger!
Oh no! It's started!
When he gets upset,
he catches fire!
Uh... Wait, what?
[PEARL screaming]
Fire Pearls...
...Special...
...Treat!
[PIRATES screaming]
Perish in my flames!
With my shields and this
inferno, I am invincible!
[KRIEG]
That moron!
We need that ship, and
he's gonna destroy it!
--[LUFFY] Ow! My butt's on fire!
--[SANJI] Crap!
[PIRATE I] Oh, no! We're
either gonna burn or drown!
He's destroying our only ship!
[PIRATE B]
This isn't good!
The restaurant's
gonna catch fire!
[SANJI]
Not on my watch!
[PEARL]
Burn!
[SANJI]
You son of a bitch!
--Wait! No! You'll get burned!
--[CARNE screams]
[SANJI] There's no way I'm
gonna let you torch our dreams!
That guy's either brave or dumb.
That cook is gonna burn!
[PEARL] But... but... these
flames scare everyone away!
Well... if I was
scared of fire...
...I wouldn't be much of a cook.
[PEARL gasps]
I hate him!
I hate that refined gentleman!
[SANJI chuckles]
[PEARL  screams]
Whoa! He got him good!
Yeah, he just broke through
Pearl's invincible wall!
[PIRATES screaming]
[PEARL]
You stupid cook.
You're totally insane!
I'll... kill... you!
Fire! Need more fire!
Fire Pearls!
[COOK AA]
No! The whole boat's gonna burn!
[COOK D] If the blaze
gets to the kitchen,
the ship will explode!
Run, Zeff! Get outta there!
Run!
[ZEFF grunts]
[PIRATES, COOKS gasp]
What? No way...
He put out my Fire Pearls?!
Fire Pearls, eh?
That's kid's stuff.
Wow! The gust from his kick
put out all of those flames!
Impossible! I don't believe it!
Red Foot Zeff is still
just as strong as ever!
Way to go, Pops! I'm impressed!
So then, it's finally
come down to this, huh?
I've got no choice-- Smash
the fins or the boat burns!
[PATTY]
Sanji! Watch out!
[COOK Z] He can't escape!
He's surrounded by fire!
[SANJI gasps]
[PEARL screams]
[LUFFY]
Ouchie!
The chore boy!
Gum-Gum... Bazooka!
[KRIEG]
Huh?
--Ow! Hot! Hot! Hot!
--He tossed that thing
--Ow! Fire! Hot! Ow! Ah!
--right back!
[LUFFY gasps, screams]
[PEARL groans]
[thud]
Pearl is down! And he's not
gonna get up this time!
[PIRATES]
No! Pearl!
[SANJI]
So weird...
Yeah, that guy sure is goofy.
[bones crack] You want
something done right...
...you got no choice
but to do it yourself.
--[ZEFF groans]
--[LUFFY, SANJI gasp]
[GHIN]
The battle ends right here...
[LUFFY, SANJI gasp]
[KRIEG]
Shoot him! Do it now!
All we have to do
is kill the geezer!
Then the restaurant
will be ours!
As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...
[SANJI] There's no way I'm gonna
let them take this restaurant!
[LUFFY] Taking a hostage!
That's fighting dirty!
He's just asking for
a good beat down!
[SANJI] Butt out, Chore Boy!
Keep your hands out of this!
[LUFFY]
Can I use my legs?
[SANJI] I'm gonna cut
you to pieces, Straw Hat!
I can't let the old man's
purpose in life be taken away!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
"Zeff and Sanji's Dream!
The Illusory All Blue!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!