[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever dared
to imagine! This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!
You'll never be anything more
than the son of a filthy pirate.
A filthy pirate?
I sympathize with you.
I really do.
You must hate your
great idiot of a father
for abandoning his
family and his village,
all because of his
mindless lust for treasure.
Don't you dare insult
my father ever again!
I'm just a normal guy.
You must hypnotize
the rich girl.
Then and only then will
I have undisputed control
of her enormous fortune.
Hey, bad guys!
You better stay away
from that girl!
[USOPP yelping]
Okay.
Don't look, we gotta run.
Hey, be careful!
You're gonna fall!
It'll all sound like lies.
[LUFFY]
"Expose the plot!
Pirate Butler, Captain Kuro!"
[CARROT] Our captain's been
gone for quite a while.
Yeah, Luffy too.
He probably just
needs some time.
Whenever he gets
really upset like this,
you can count on him
hanging out by the shore.
[CARROT]
Uh...
Ah!
[ALL yelling]
[ALL]
Captain!
[NAMI]
Huh?
Hold on.
I thought Luffy was
supposed to be with him.
[ALL]
Captain!
[ALL yelp]
Hey, where's Luffy?
Is he still at the shore?
Wow, he looked really upset.
But why? Still mad
at the butler?
[ZORO]
Who knows.
No! That wasn't just a mad face!
That look was different!
It was the tragic face
of sheer desperation!
Hey.
Why don't you guys show us the
way to get down to that shore.
[CARROT] This smells
like an adventure to me!
Yeah! Something
happened at the shore!
[ONION] I think this calls
for the Usopp Pirates!
Enough already! How do
we get to this place?!
[panting]
[USOPP]
Terrible news.
Pirates! Pirates are coming!
Everybody run!
We don't stand a chance!
Everybody run! Run!
[USOPP] Tomorrow morning they're
gonna attack the village,
we gotta get outta here!
What're you doing?! Run!
Is anyone even listening
to me?! Pirates!
[chuckles]
[VILLAGERS murmuring]
[VILLAGER D]
All right, Usopp.
Enough is enough.
[VILLAGER E]
We can't take it anymore.
We're putting a stop
to this here and now.
It's for your own good.
[USOPP]
No! It's not like that!
It's the truth this
time! I promise!
Stop it! We all know that
you're nothing but a liar.
It would do you some good
to follow Klahadore's example
of hard work and honesty.
[KURO] Everything he could
say would sound like lies.
[USOPP]
Oh no.
This is exactly what
Klahadore's counting on.
He ignored me because he
knew no one would believe me.
[MERRY]
Are these to your liking, miss?
[MERRY] Custom made to
your exact specifications.
It was quite a trip to get them.
[KAYA]
They're just perfect.
Thank you so much for traveling
so far to get them for me.
They're a gift aren't they?
Yes.
As of tomorrow, it will be
exactly three years to the day
since Klahadore arrived here.
He's always taken
such good care of me.
[MERRY] He'll be delighted
to receive such a lovely gift.
[KAYA]
I hope so.
Please hear me out everyone!
Our lives depend on it!
Listen!
Pirates are gonna attack
the village in the morning!
If we believed every
story you ever told us,
we would've run
screaming from the village
hundreds a times already.
[USOPP] Please, believe me!
We don't have time!
I'm not lying
this time. I swear!
Don't you get it?!
They'll murder you all!
[VILLAGER E] You'll be lucky
if we don't murder you!
[USOPP]
I'm not lying!
[VILLAGER E] Get him!
Don't let him escape!
[CARROT]
This is the place.
[PEPPER]
Our captain always comes here
to be alone and think.
[ONION]
It is nice.
I don't think that
straw hat guy is here.
[ZORO]
Hm.
[NAMI]
The rocks sure are loose here.
Nami, be careful.
[NAMI]
Right.
Look! Down there!
Luffy?!
--Whoa!
--Hey! It's that straw hat guy!
And his butt.
[gasps]
[NAMI] Luffy, what did you do?!
How did this happen?!
[CARROT]
He fell.
[ONION]
He's a goner!
[PEPPER] So that's why our
captain looked so upset.
[LUFFY snoring]
[ZORO]
Hm?
Wait a minute.
Ha. Lazy bum.
[LUFFY groaning]
[ALL scream]
[yawning]
Good morning, guys.
[USOPP panting]
Usopp.
Oh, good. I was worried
you wouldn't come back.
Quick! Run, Kaya!
They're gonna kill you!
Huh?
Someone's going to kill me?
He's tricked the entire village!
Klahadore's really a
deadly pirate captain!
Is this a story?
Well, I don't like this one.
[USOPP]
Uh.
This isn't one of my stories!
It's the truth! I heard
it with my own ears!
[USOPP]
Klahadore is a pirate captain
who weaseled his way
into your family's home
so he could steal your fortune.
He's pretended to be
your butler for three years
so he can kill you
and inherit your money!
[KAYA] What are you
talking about, Usopp?
His crew is gonna raid
the village at dawn
and in the process,
you're gonna get killed!
Klahadore is a very bad man,
your life is in danger!
You have to escape!
[KAYA]
He did treat you harshly earlier
and I understand that you're
hurt, but lying like this,
it's not like you.
Kaya, please.
I'm telling you the truth.
[USOPP]
Please believe me!
[KIDS]
What?!
Pirates are going to
attack the village?!
Then they're gonna kill Kaya?!
Yep. That's what they said.
No question 'bout it.
[ALL yelping]
So, what made you think
it'd be a good time for a nap?
That's the thing,
I don't remember going to sleep
or getting down here at all!
This proves it!
Klahadore is a bad guy!
Usopp saw right though him!
I bet he's on his way
to warn the villagers
so they'll have
time to run away.
Well, that's perfect.
Those stupid pirates
won't hurt anyone
because the town
will be abandoned
by the time they get there!
Yeah, that's right!
We'd better run away
too if we wanna live!
[PEPPER] All right, let's
pack our treasure and--
[KIDS]
Run like the wind! Ah!
[ALL screaming]
Oh no!
What's up?
[LUFFY screaming]
We need to stock up before
the meat shop guy leaves!
[ZORO] C'mon, that's not
really the issue at hand here.
[KAYA]
Hello, Usopp. So...
What adventure are you
going to tell me about today?
[USOPP]
Hmm. Well, let's see.
Oh, I know!
What about the story of
me fighting a giant gold fish?
At the south pole, when
I was only five years old.
That's a good one!
[KAYA] A goldfish?
You fought a goldfish?
[USOPP] A giant goldfish!
It was so huge,
a fish tank the size
of this mansion
wouldn't be able to hold it!
[KAYA]
Oh my!
[USOPP laughing]
[USOPP]
What first astounded me
was the immense
size of its poop!
I thought it was solid ground!
It was so big, that
when I landed on it,
I thought it was
some kind of island.
[KAYA]
Uhh... That sounds fake.
[USOPP] Believe me,
I know it sounds fake,
but every word of it is true.
[KAYA, USOPP laughing]
[USOPP] My first mistake
was lighting the bonfire
to dry my clothes off with.
That was just plain dumb.
[KAYA]
Why's that?
[USOPP]
Well, the next thing I knew,
there was a giant gold fish
with his rear end on fire
--and guess who he was mad at!
--[KAYA] Oh, dear!
[USOPP]
Well, I can't say I blame him!
As far as he knew,
I trying to turn him into
a giant grilled gold fish!
[USOPP laughing]
I loved them.
Every... one.
All those lies you told me.
They brought joy to my heart.
But... this is just
vengeful poison.
Kaya, please.
Listen to me, I'm not just
trying to get back at Klahadore.
Why would you do
that? It's wrong.
Kaya... I...
[USOPP, KAYA laughing]
Miss Kaya, is everything
okay up here?
[gasps]
[USOPP grunts]
Let's get out of here!
Right now!
Usopp! Stop it!
Unhand her immediately,
you villain!
[USOPP]
Please, trust me, Kaya.
You gotta get out
of this village
before that butler gets back.
Stop it!
[USOPP]
C'mon!
I promise this'll all
make sense tomorrow,
but right now we need to go.
Kaya, please.
--Please... Trust me.
--[KAYA gasps]
[slap]
You're pathetic.
Leave Miss Kaya
alone, you maniac!
No!
[USOPP grunts]
[gasps]
[VILLAGERS yelling]
Don't let that lunatic get away!
He broke in and tried to
kidnap the lady of the house!
[VILLAGERS yelling]
[USOPP]
Why?
Why won't anyone believe me?
[VILLAGERS yelling]
Usopp...
There, there, ma'am,
everything's going to be fine.
[KURO] After three
long years of absence,
I made the call for
my men, and you came.
Your loyalty will be
richly rewarded.
I intend on being more than
generous when I divide the take.
At dawn tomorrow, destroy the
village to your hearts content.
[PIRATES yelling, cheering]
[KURO chuckling]
[KAYA]
Who're you?
[USOPP] I'm Usopp,
brave warrior of the sea!
I've heard you've been
a little down lately
so I thought I'd tell you
a story to cheer you up.
[KAYA] You would do well
to mind your own business!
Please leave or I'll call
someone who will make you leave!
[USOPP]
Hey, calm down.
You're right, I should leave.
I'm sorry, I've always been
meddlesome like this.
Ha, ha. It's not always
a bad thing though.
One time, when I
was three years old,
my meddling led me
to saving a sick whale!
[KAYA]
What? A whale?
[USOPP]
You bet!
A whale of a whale even, and
it had a really sore throat.
So, I walked into his
mouth to check it out,
but he thought I was food.
[KAYA laughs]
[KIDS]
Captain!
Hey! How's it going guys?
--[CARROT] Hey, captain!
--[PEPPER] Look he's back!
Hey!
[squeaks]
Wait! You're alive again?!
Alive?
Yeah! And I had
a pretty good nap!
He was sleeping the whole time!
Captain, we heard all
about those pirates
and their evil plan!
We'd better hurry and warn
the people in the village
so they have time to get away!
Warn the people...
You're pathetic.
Stop it.
We all know you're
nothing but a liar.
It would do you some good
to follow Klahadore's example
of hard work and honesty.
[laughing]
Well, obviously,
I'm lying like usual!
That butler made me
so mad with what he said,
I thought I'd get him back and
say that he was a pirate!
[KIDS, USOPP laughing]
[ONION]
Oh, I get it!
You put the straw hat
guy up to it, too!
[ALL laughing]
Hey. Where ya goin'?
[CARROT] Honestly, you've
really disappointed me.
Yeah.
Even though that
butler guy is a jerk,
I thought you were better
than lying to hurt someone,
and I admired you for being
such a kind-hearted person.
[ONION]
And to think,
we respected you
this entire time.
[CARROT]
I was wrong about him, guys.
[PEPPER]
So was I.
[CARROT]
Let's go home.
[PEPPER]
Yeah, it's suppertime anyways.
[ONION]
Wonder what we're having.
[USOPP yelping]
There. All done.
So, how come you lied to them?
Because all I do is lie.
[USOPP] There's no way
anybody was gonna believe
what I had to say.
Why should they?
Because what you were telling
them was the honest truth.
They are coming. And they're
gonna level this whole town.
Yeah, but what am
I supposed to do?
They'll think I'm lying
if I try to warn them.
Everyone in the village thinks
that tomorrow's just gonna
be another normal day.
They think I'm lying and
that's all they need to think.
I'm gonna stop those pirates
at the beach tomorrow myself!
This is all my fault
for being such a liar.
I don't care anymore
if they drive me away with
brooms or shoot me in the arm.
This is my village.
It's my home... and
I love everyone in it!
I have to protect them.
You're a hell of a good guy,
sending your cronies away
and going into battle alone.
[NAMI]
Just so you know,
I have dibs on all the
pirate treasure, you got it?
So, you want a little
help or what?
You guys...
You're gonna help me fight
all these pirates?
I don't get it?
Well, you said there's a whole
buncha bad guys, right?
And you look scared
out of your mind.
Ugh. For your information,
I have nerves of steel!
I'm perfectly okay
with tons of bad guys!
After all, you're looking at
the legendary Captain Usopp,
brave warrior of the high seas!
Damnit! All right,
fine, I'm scared!
Why shouldn't I be?!
They're Captain Kuro's men!
These guys mean business!
I don't need pity!
If you guys are sticking
around cause you pity me,
just leave! I don't need
you laughin' at me!
We're not laughing at you.
We're helping because
you are honorable.
You really think we'd
risk our lives out of pity?
Aw... You guys!
As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...
[LUFFY] Huh. Why did Usopp
cover this slope in oil?
[ZORO]
It's part of his plan.
[NAMI]
That's a weird plan.
[LUFFY]
So, where are these pirates?
[ZORO] What?! They're
at the north shore!
[LUFFY]
I'll go on ahead!
[NAMI] They better not lay
a finger on my treasure!
[LUFFY] North! North!
Which way is north?!
[ZORO]
I'll get you for this, Nami!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece:
"Clash with the
Black Cat Pirates!
The Great Battle on the Slope!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!