[NARRATOR]
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King
of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
[GOLD ROGER]
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now, you just have to find it.
[NARRATOR] These words
lured men to the Grand Line
in pursuit of dreams greater
than they've ever dared
to imagine! This is the time
known as the Great Pirate Era!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One Piece!
Compass left behind
It'll only slow us down
Your heart will be your guide
Raise the sails
and take the helm
That legendary place that the
end of the map reveals
Is only legendary
until someone proves it real
Through it all, through all
the troubled times,
through the heartache,
and through the pain
Know that I will be there
to stand by you
Just like I know
you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend
We are, we are on the cruise
We are!
Now! Light the fuse, Nami!
[HENCHMEN]
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
[NAMI gasps]
[Henchmen]
Fire! Fire! Fire!
[LUFFY laughs]
[Henchmen]
Fire! Fire! Fire!
[LUFFY gasps]
[BUGGY growls]
[gasps]
[NAMI gasps]
[BUGGY laughs]
[ZORO grunts]
[ZORO grunting]
Zoro!
[ZORO grunts]
[ZORO gasps]
Stabbing him in the back was
a cowardly move, you Big Nose!
[ZORO grunts]
You okay, Zoro?
How bad are you injured.
Just shut up and don't
worry about how I'm doing.
I need to concentrate if
I'm gonna get us outta this.
[ZORO grunting]
Who is... this guy?
[panting]
Hey, Luffy, who's this?
Who's the girl?
Oh, right. She's
our new navigator.
[ZORO grunts]
I'm not so sure about that.
Who are you guys, anyway?
[ZORO]
Move...[grunts]
You're in the way.
[ZORO grunting]
[LUFFY]
"Desperate Situation!
Beast Tamer Mohji vs. Luffy."
[ZORO grunting]
I guess even a lowly pirate...
...can still rescue his friend.
[BUGGY] Those three
think they can mock me?
Screw that!
I consider this act of
aggression a declaration of war.
[BUGGY]
There you are, Mohji.
I hope you wouldn't mind if
I take the Pirate Hunter's head.
[BUGGY laughs]
Be my guest.
[ZORO grunts]
[ZORO grunting]
[ZORO pants]
[LUFFY laughs]
[ZORO gasps]
[LUFFY]
Huh?
[ZORO grunts]
[ZORO]
Huh?
[Zoro]
What's with this dog?
[LUFFY]
Huh?
Doggie!
[LUFFY grunting]
Zoro, it looks like
this dog is frozen.
[ZORO]
I don't give a damn.
He could sit there
forever, for all I care.
I wonder if it's dead.
[DOG barks]
[LUFFY screams]
--[DOG growling]
--[LUFFY groaning]
[LUFFY] Get off!
Get off! Get off! Get off!
Luffy, please, quit goofing
around and get serious!
[LUFFY]
Damn dog...
[ZORO]
I don't feel good...
[NAMI]
Huh?
Oh! Hi, navigator.
I guess you can have this.
You got me out of a
pretty sticky situation.
Great! The key to the cage!
Did you go and
steal if for me?
Thanks, Nami!
I only did it so we'd be even.
And now, I don't owe you
anything. So we're square, okay?
Heh...
Ya, sure.
[DOG barks]
[gasps]
[DOG gulps]
[NAMI]
Uh...
[ZORO grunts]
[LUFFY growls]
--[LUFFY growling]
--[DOG howls]
[LUFFY]
Stupid, stupid, stupid, dog!
Give it back. That's not food!
Give me my key!
Give it, give it, give it, give
it, give it, give it, give it!
[BOODLE]
Hey! Stop that!
[NAMI]
Huh?
Stop picking on poor Chouchou!
Leave him alone!
[barking]
And who might you be old man?
Old man? Why, I'm the
mayor of this town!
Who are you and why are
you hurting Chouchou? Huh?
My, my... that's quite an
injury you have there.
I take it that ya' had a
run in with Captain Buggy.
We need to get you to a doctor.
How's Zoro?
I told him he really
should see a doctor,
but he insisted that
he didn't need to
and just wanted to sleep it off.
[snoring]
[yawns]
[NAMI]
So this dog's name is Chouchou?
[LUFFY laughs]
Why is he just
sitting there like that?
He sure is a lazy dog.
He's guarding the store.
He's guarding it?
[BOODLE]
Yes.
Huh?
Oh! I see. It's a pet food shop!
[BOODLE]
That's right.
And the man who
used to run this store
was a very close friend of mine.
[BOODLE]
There ya' go.
When he passed,
I assumed the responsibility
of taking care of Chouchou.
[NAMI]
He died?
[BOODLE]
Yes.
Three months ago,
after fighting his illness
for a very long time.
[NAMI] Don't tell me
he's been waiting
for his master to
return all this time.
[BOODLE]
That seems to be the consensus.
[NAMI]
Huh...
But I find that
very hard to believe.
Chouchou is a smart dog.
He's probably known for a while
that his master
isn't coming back.
Then... why does he
stay here at the store?
I guess because he has
a connection to it.
It's his... treasure.
He's guarding it.
His master left
him with this shop
and that's why he protects it.
I've tried to bring
him back to my place,
so he won't be out
in the elements,
but he won't take so much
as a step away from here.
[roaring]
[NAMI]
Huh? What's that sound?
[BOODLE]
It's him!
Beast Tamer Mohji!
We gotta go! Run!
[NAMI] What do you mean
by "Beast Tamer"?
--[NAMI] Wait! Hold On!
--[BOODLE] Get outta here!
[LUFFY sighs]
C'mon puppy, something's here.
Why don't you just
give me that key back?
[LUFFY]
Uhh...
[LION GROWLING]
I see that your friends
have deserted you.
And after you just escaped.
[LUFFY]
Who the heck are you?
I'm known as the
"Beast Tamer Mohji,"
a member of the Buggy Pirates.
Woah, that's a weird
animal suit you got on.
[LION roaring]
That was rude!
This is manly hair!
'K, That's even weirder.
You shouldn't assume that you're
safe
just because
you're in that cage.
You must not know of
my terrifying skill!
There is no animal
in this world
that Beast Tamer Mohji
can't bend to do his bidding.
Shake...
--[MOHJI screaming]
--[CHOUCHOU growling]
Why does it hurt so bad?!
You nameless thief, I've
no interest in killing you!
But tell me where
Roronoa Zoro is
before I change my mind.
No way!
Richie, Attack!
[RICHIE roars]
[LUFFY laughs]
Yes! I'm finally out!
[LUFFY grunts]
Nice work.
Good boy, Richie!
Now let's go find Zoro
so I can defeat him and
strengthen my reputation.
What's, wrong?
Oh, it's a pet food store.
Make it quick, then let's go.
[RICHIE roars]
[MOHJI]
Huh?
Don't tell me this
pathetic little thing
really thinks he
can guard the shop.
[barking]
[LUFFY]
Whew, that was intense!
At least now, I'm
out of that cage.
[LUFFY]
He.He.
Now, first thing, I teach
those Buggy Pirates
a lesson and then
I convince Nami
to be the navigator for my crew.
[NAMI]
Huh?
How'd you survive that attack?!
You're alive?!
I just got lucky, I guess.
Surviving an attack
like that isn't normal.
I figured you'd be
scattered all over.
[LUFFY]
It's not normal?
Why exactly did you decide
to come to this town,
and how'd you get involved
with those pirates?
All I'm doing is searching
for a chart of the Grand Line
and a good navigator
to join my pirate crew.
[NAMI gasps]
[LUFFY] I think that
guy in the animal suit
said he was looking for
Zoro, so, I gotta go!
[RICHIE ROARING]
[CHOUCHOU growls]
[CHOUCHOU yelps]
[CHOUCHOU growling]
[OWNER] Chouchou? This shop
belongs to the two of us now.
[barks]
Ha. Ha. That bag is way
too big for you, Chouchou.
[RICHIE growls]
[CHOUCHOU snarling]
[CHOUCHOU barking]
[OWNER grunts]
[CHOUCHOU grunts]
[OWNER laughs]
Be careful, Chouchou.
Don't hurt yourself.
Leave this to me!
[barking]
[OWNER]
Hmm. Bad Chouchou!
I told you not to
eat the merchandise.
Now, let's chow down!
[CHOUCHOU yelps]
[CHOUCHOU, RICHIE growling]
Well... Not ready
to give up yet?
[CHOUCHOU growling]
[OWNER] Chouchou, I'm
getting on in years now.
I gotta go see the
doctor for a checkup.
But I'll be back, so guard
the shop until I return.
I'm counting on you, Chouchou.
Hold down the fort!
[CHOUCHOU, RICHIE growling]
[CHOUCHOU barks]
[CHOUCHOU yelps]
[barking]
[barking continues]
[OWNER laughs]
That tickles, Chouchou!
[CHOUCHOU whimpers]
[BOODLE]
He has a connection to it.
It's his treasure.
He's guarding it.
His master left
him with this shop
and that's why he protects it.
[howls, barks]
[barks, howls]
[MOHJI]
Damn it!
I can't believe that
annoying little dog bit me.
[grunts]
Wait, I thought I killed you.
What are you still doing alive?
I'm afraid you can't get
rid of me that easily.
This time crush his head
into the ground, Richie!
[RICHIE roars]
I'm not gonna be
beaten by a lion.
Gum-Gum...
[LUFFY]
Hammer!
[LUFFY grunts]
[MOHJI whimpers]
[MOHJI]
What are you?!
Well... I ate the
Gum-Gum Devil Fruit!
[MOHJI gasps]
So then you have...
...Devil Fruit powers
like Captain Buggy,
but yours make you rubber?
Sorry! I apologize
for attacking!
I don't want any trouble!
[LUFFY] There's no reason
for you to apologize to me.
Because of you, that dog will
never get his treasure back.
[barking]
And now... because of that,
I'm gonna kick your ass.
[MOHJI whimpers, gasps]
[LUFFY grunting]
--[LUFFY yells]
--[MOHJI grunts]
Pirates are all the same.
They're all just a bunch
of heartless bastards.
They destroy everything
that people hold dear,
without giving it
a second thought.
Oh, you're alive, Pirate!
You know, I thought
for sure that lion
was gonna tear your
head off and end it all.
And I wish he had,
'cause then there'd be one
less pirate in the world!
Maybe I should
kill you right now
before you can gather a crew
and destroy everything else!
[BOODLE]
Come now,
there's no need for violence.
[LUFFY]
As if you could ever kill me.
[NAMI]
Well, maybe I'll try it and see!
[BOODLE]
I said stop!
What's with you people?!
[NAMI gasps]
[NAMI]
Huh?
[LUFFY sighs]
Sorry, but that's all
that I could save for ya'.
That bastard lion ate
all the rest of it.
[NAMI]
He...
He fought the lion...
...in order to save
the dog's food?
[LUFFY]
You fought well.
Course I didn't actually
see you defend the store,
but I can tell you
gave it your all.
[CHOUCHOU barks]
Heh! Thanks!
Good luck to you, too, doggie!
[barking]
[NAMI giggles]
[BUGGY]
You were defeated?!
How?!
Uh, I'm very sorry, Captain.
Sorry, I failed.
Mohji, I can't believe you
were defeated by Zoro.
No, it wasn't Zoro.
It was that straw hat.
What?!
There's no way that
skinny little punk
could have gotten
the better of you!
[MOHJI]
He's eaten the Gum...
Now I'm really pissed off!
Alright, Prepare all the
remaining Special Buggy Balls.
I'm gonna blow this entire,
miserable town to smithereens!
[NAMI]
Sorry about earlier.
I didn't mean to yell at you.
That's okay, you've been
under a lot of stress lately.
But hey, no need to apologize.
I'm pathetic!
Chouchou and this young
one have fought so hard,
and yet I, the mayor, have done
nothing but sit back and watch
our town be obliterated by
Buggy and his despicable crew.
Calm down! It's not that bad!
Forty years ago,
this whole area was nothing
but barren, rugged land.
We all worked together to
create fields for our crops.
We opened stores, and built
everything from the ground up.
This town is a treasure
to me and all its citizens!
From here on out,
I refuse to let Buggy and his
crew terrorize us any more!
[BUGGY]
Fire a Special Buggy Ball.
Blow this town away!
[BOODLE gasps]
He'll destroy it all.
Ah! Zoro was sleeping in there!
[BOODLE]
I'm sure he's dead now.
[LUFFY]
Zoro, you in there?!
Are you still alive?!
[ZORO] That's one hell of
a way to wake a guy up.
[LUFFY laughs]
[ZORO]
I coulda used a few more z's.
How did you survive that blast?
All right! You're alive!
[BOODLE] I refuse to let
him get away with this.
I won't stand for it.
I can't let this
scumbag destroy
all that my townspeople worked
for these last forty years.
[BOODLE]
I am the mayor of this town!
I will protect it
and it's inhabitants!
I swear... to my dying breath!
[NAMI]
Stop! You can't defeat Buggy!
[BOODLE]
Perhaps...
...but there are some fights
that a man can't run from!
Isn't that right?!
That's right, old man!
Shut up! Don't egg
him on, Luffy!
It's dangerous for
him to fight Buggy!
I know that it's dangerous!
[BOODLE] I'm coming for
you, Buggy the Clown!
[NAMI]
The mayor was crying.
[LUFFY]
He was? Huh, I didn't notice.
[ZORO] Looks like the
party's getting more exciting!
[LUFFY laughs]
Sure does.
This is no time for laughter.
Don't worry. I started to
grow fond of that old man.
There's no way I'd let him die.
[ZORO]
Well, In that case ...
You're gonna go too?
You're wounded!
Yeah, so what?
the injury to my reputation's
a lot worse than the
injury to my gut.
Well, if we want to get
to the Grand Line....
...we better go steal
that chart back!
Ha! Are you gonna
join our crew or what?
Huh?
Come on.
I'll never sink so low
as to become a pirate.
[LUFFY gasps]
But I suppose we
could team up,
in order to achieve
our common goal.
[LUFFY laughs]
[HENCHMAN J]
The second shot is ready, sir.
All right then, fire.
[BOODLE]
Come out, Buggy the Clown!
[panting]
I'm Mayor Boodle and this
town is my treasure!
I won't let you terrorize
my people any longer,
so come out and fight me!
You idiot! This town
is no treasure!
Treasure is gold,
silver, and jewelry.
So cut the crap, old man,
and get outta here
before I kill you.
You could never
understand how I feel!
[BUGGY laughs]
[BUGGY] Soon I'm going to
conquer the Grand Line and
flashily obtain all
the world's riches,
and there's nothing
you can do to stop me!
All the world will belong to me.
Now, if this town
means so much to you,
then perhaps I'll do you a
favor and kill you first,
that way you won't
have to see me
destroy your precious village.
[BOODLE grunting]
Shut up... and fight me already!
Don't get cocky!
I'll never let you
destroy this town,
if it costs me my very life!
[BUGGY laughs]
So be it!
[gasps]
That straw hat! Not again!
I'm here to kick your ass, just
like I promised I would, Buggy!
As a kid, I never stopped
Searching for a great treasure
I had a map in my mind
That I knew would lead me
I had to find my way
to that place
Before someone could beat me
The promised land
was in my grasp
And I wouldn't let go
My only dream...
I won't stop chasing it
until it comes true
But if the world ever changes
I'll call out your name
We could return to the time
When everything's the same
As long as I'm with you
My memories won't fade
Waiting for that
one true dream...
[LUFFY]
Huh?
Now we have to take on
one of their swordsmen?
[ZORO]
I'll clash swords with him!
[LUFFY]
Are you sure? You're injured.
[ZORO] Huh. I'll show you
how superior my skills are.
[LUFFY]
Ooh! Cool!
[ZORO] My ambition is to be
the world's greatest swordsman!
I can't afford to
lose to anyone
who calls himself
a swordfighter!
[LUFFY]
On the next One Piece,
"Epic Showdown!
Swordsman Zoro
vs. Acrobat Cabaji!"
I'm gonna be
King of the Pirates!